<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CASology on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/casology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CASology on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/casology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #407*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-06-casology-407/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-06-casology-407/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month which means there is a new CASology challenge. Our cue for this month is HAPPY!
The cue is easy for me as the majority of the cards I make are for birthdays&amp;hellip; I pulled out some rainbow colours and an alphabet die set and created this for you!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Poppy Parade, Daffodil Delight, Granny Apple Green, Pacific Point, Highland Heather</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #406*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-02-casology-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-02-casology-406/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology and the cue for this month is SAND. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check out what the rest of the design team has created and maybe even share a creation of your own!! You&amp;rsquo;ll find the CASology blog HERE
Despite loving the beach, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of a things that are beach themed&amp;hellip; so I had to think about how to create something with this cue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #405*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-05-casology-405/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-05-casology-405/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology... our cue for you for July is WINDY.
I have a funny wind story&amp;hellip; last fall we put up some security cameras over our garage. Since the trees have leafed this year, we often get alerts from the cameras of &amp;ldquo;motion&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the other day we had hundreds of alerts in the morning when we work up&amp;hellip; each one of them was the leaves on the trees thanks to the wind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #404*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-07-casology-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-07-casology-404/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pop by the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done with the cue of RIDE. We love to see your clean and simple creations too&amp;hellip; share them HERE!
I almost skipped this challenge but then remembered this cute set from My Favorite Things and decided I&amp;rsquo;d give it a go. It&amp;rsquo;s not really my &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I pushed myself a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #403*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-03-casology-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-03-casology-403/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends&amp;hellip; I saw my surgeon yesterday and as expected, the plaster splint was removed and I now have a removable brace. I can wear the brace when I&amp;rsquo;m up and about or if the arm/wrist is fatigued. I have some stretches thatI&amp;rsquo;ve started doing that are really tough but I am told it will all get easier&amp;hellip; I am to use my arm and wrist as tolerated for anything non-weight bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
