<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spellbinders on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/spellbinders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spellbinders on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/spellbinders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card is a mix of some extras fro my bin and some other things I cut especially for this card. I knew I wanted a wreath like card so I cut the knotted circle and then dug through my bin of extras for some flowers and leaves that might work. I then foiled my sentiment and cut it out to finish off the card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black and others from my stash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #488*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; we have some wonderfully fall colours to challenge you with this week. I will admit I was even thinking about some Christmas card ideas when I was first looking at these colours.
I decided to create a fall wreath and added a little hot foiling to finish it off.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Merry Merlot, Calypso Coral, Mossy Meadow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a no layer card challenge with AAACards&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;hellip; just the card itself! The optional twist is to make it a sympathy card.
Sympathy cards are not a card anyone wants to make&amp;hellip; but they are necessary to have in our stash. I personally like to make my sympathy cards subdued&amp;hellip; I was curious to see how the silver foil would look on grey cardstock so that&amp;rsquo;s what I played with for my challenge card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</guid>
      <description>The new challenge at Less is More is to use vellum. There are so many different ways to use vellum in your creations and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you all come up with! I had a few ideas in my head about how I wanted to use vellum and I decided I wanted to try foiling on it to see if it would work. I&amp;rsquo;m here to report that it works pretty well, although there are some splotchy spots so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t line art or sentiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #706*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-19-color-throwdown-706/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-19-color-throwdown-706/</guid>
      <description>I had to play along with the latest challenge at Color Throwdown because I really love the look of blue and green together. I usually choose the brighter forms of these colours to go together but I strayed from that with this card to use up a scrap of very old patterned paper I had in my stash.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Marina Mist
*Paper: My Mind&amp;rsquo;s Eye
*Images: Spellbinders Sentiments for Your</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In Color Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I just love the 2022-24 Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours&amp;hellip;. but I don&amp;rsquo;t find I use all of them much. I am really drawn to the red, green and light blue but not the two darker colours as much. So I grabbed all five for this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, Parakeet Party, Tahitian Tide, Orchid Oasis, Starry Sky
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge over at the Less is More blog&amp;hellip;. we are looking to see your one layer cards (which means the one layer is your card base) with your favourite flower! Be sure to head over to the Less is More blog to see the beautiful creations by the rest of the design team and to share your creations with us.
You knew this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a difficult challenge for me&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #481*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; and for the month of August, I am the host! We are staring off this month with a colour challenge. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what everyone creates using these great colours! Be sure to check out the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches blog to see what the rest of the design team created!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Floral Best Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-01-floral-best-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-01-floral-best-wishes/</guid>
      <description>Why do the months of June, July and August seem to fly by while December, January and February go by at a snails pace? I am in awe that summer in already half over! I know there&amp;rsquo;s still lots of warm sunny weather to come, but it feels like it&amp;rsquo;s going by so fast!
I saw a card using this layout on Pinterest and wanted to play with it. For some it would still be considered clean and simple, but for others it is not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*When It Rains...*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</guid>
      <description>My blog title has nothing to do with my card today&amp;hellip; but it has to do with what&amp;rsquo;s going on in my world. As you know, I broke my right wrist in April. While I am getting mobility and strength back in that wrist, it would appear that the muscles around my right shoulder don&amp;rsquo;t like that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the arm in awkward ways and they have now seized up making it near impossible to sit upright at my desk, let alone create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations Trees*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still some time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations June theme of TREES! This is a great challenge to help you get a few Christmas cards made throughout the year. I had promised myself to make more Christmas cards before October and while I&amp;rsquo;ve done that, it&amp;rsquo;s really only been for this challenge! Maybe I should make one day a month where I make only Christmas cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</guid>
      <description>I am so happy that Samantha chose some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for our challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches this week. I just love the new colours and especially these three! I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with this colour combination this week!
These colours are just so happy! They make me think of popsicles, and beach balls, and shovels and pails&amp;hellip; all those wonderfully fun things in the summer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Thoughts*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back without another washi tape creation. The stamp and die with this Pink Fresh Studio set are one piece so it makes more sense to stamp it all and then cut it all&amp;hellip; the same goes with the washi tape. When I cut out the wreath for the card a few days ago, it only made sense to do it all. These were the other pieces I had so I threw them all on a panel to create a card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; and this week it&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge. For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</guid>
      <description>Now that I have a little more mobility (and I do mean a little) with my right hand, I decided to try making a card on yesterday afternoon. Fine motor skills are still a bit of a struggle and I had to take a break part way through, but I managed to get a card done in time for the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches challenge for this week. It&amp;rsquo;s a sketch challenge this week&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations following the sketch below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #211*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</guid>
      <description>Happy Thursday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at Time Out Challenges is back with a new photo inspiration challenge. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you create using the photo below as inspiration.
Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to not only be chosen to play along as a Guest Designer in an upcoming challenge but to win a $15 credit to shop at our sponsor, Poppystamps!
I used a layered diamond die cut pieces that I cut in half to create some blue and green and grey mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAA Cards #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-03-aaa-cards-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-03-aaa-cards-212/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at AAA Cards&amp;hellip; we are a clean and simple challenge blog with challenges every two weeks. For our current challenge, we want to see your clean and simple cards that are decorated &amp;ldquo;along the edge&amp;rdquo; with the optional twist of &amp;ldquo;your country&amp;rdquo;. Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a guest designer for an upcoming challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
