<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pink Fresh Studio on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/pink-fresh-studio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pink Fresh Studio on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/pink-fresh-studio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</guid>
      <description>October is Breast Cancer Awareness Month and the team at Time Out had originally had our challenge today as a Breast Cancer challenge&amp;hellip; as a colon cancer survivor (x2), I respectfully asked if we could change it to a cancer awareness challenge&amp;hellip; everyone knows about and talks about breast cancer, but no one talks about colon cancer (and many other cancers). It&amp;rsquo;s SO important to me that we talk about all forms of cancer, that we not be embarrassed about talking about our health, our bodies and the changes we are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Free Form Frame*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</guid>
      <description>Another card from the bin of extras&amp;hellip;. I used a die as a guide to draw a rectangle on my card front with pencil&amp;hellip; and then went over it a few times with a thin black marker, not even trying to make straight lines. Once it had set for a bit I erased the pencil lines and then added in the hash marks and dots. I stamped my sentiment and added to my ink blended butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #489*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the sketch this week at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! My card went together pretty quickly once I decided on what elements I wanted to use. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
My card uses a few pieces from my bin of extras that I kept overlooking. I had used just two of the layering stencils and these two pieces had very little colour on them&amp;hellip; so I grabbed my Copics and gave them a bit more colour before adding them to my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*So Very Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 09:12:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</guid>
      <description>I took a few days off from blogging&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of non-design team cards to share and honestly haven&amp;rsquo;t been feeling very creative lately. I am in my creative space for a while today and after I post this card I hope to have a little mojo flowing to create some stuff to share with you. I&amp;rsquo;m struggling to find my own ideas and am not feeling inspired by any of the cards I&amp;rsquo;ve pinned and saved to try to put my own spin on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</guid>
      <description>October 1st is World Cardmaking Day and here at Less is More, we are celebrating a little early with a friendship themed challenge! We think making a card for a friend is a great way to celebrate World Cardmaking Day! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of very good friends who are always there for me&amp;hellip; to listen, to provide support, to make me laugh, to distract me, to do social things with&amp;hellip; so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make a card that I could give to one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-12-simple-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 08:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-12-simple-thanks/</guid>
      <description>One thing I don&amp;rsquo;t love about the Pink Fresh Studio washi tapes is that when you use them, you kind of need to use the entire panel which means you always end up with pieces you don&amp;rsquo;t need right away. These pieces go in to my bin of extras and I pull them out when I have a need for them. Sometimes it means I have several cards in a row that look similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #552*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</guid>
      <description>I got home from work yesterday and sat down in my creative space, hoping to make a card. I saw the latest sketch at Freshly Made Sketches and decided to try my hand at it&amp;hellip; I really hope my mojo shows up on the rest of my days off this week&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Paper: MFT Party Time
*Images: Pink Fresh Studios Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #239*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</guid>
      <description>I am playing along with the STRIPES challenge at CAS on Friday&amp;hellip;. this started out being a card for last weeks Freshly Made Sketches but I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to finish it in time to play along with this. I also liked the stripes on the side instead of the bottom better so I switched things up!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, glitter paper
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Foiled Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a no layer card challenge with AAACards&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;hellip; just the card itself! The optional twist is to make it a sympathy card.
Sympathy cards are not a card anyone wants to make&amp;hellip; but they are necessary to have in our stash. I personally like to make my sympathy cards subdued&amp;hellip; I was curious to see how the silver foil would look on grey cardstock so that&amp;rsquo;s what I played with for my challenge card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Washi Floral*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</guid>
      <description>I am running out of cards to share with you! I lost some time with card making first with my broken wrist in the spring and then again in August with Covid. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good these days but I feel like life has been busy and the mojo is harder to come by! I sit at my craft desk but get nothing accomplished! I hope my creative block doesn&amp;rsquo;t last too long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Super Simple*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-01-super-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-01-super-simple/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the simplicity of this card&amp;hellip; a little foam tape to make the white on white layer pop a little and voila! And who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love that sparkly paper?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*I Share Everything*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-31-i-share-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-31-i-share-everything/</guid>
      <description>I like to share everything I make with you guys&amp;hellip; even if I don&amp;rsquo;t really like how it turned out. Some of the creations that I am not impressed with have had the most &amp;ldquo;likes&amp;rdquo; on social media. You never know what others like, so I share everything in hopes of inspiring someone else.
This is one of those cards&amp;hellip;. I keep pushing it back to share because I&amp;rsquo;m just not thrilled with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</guid>
      <description>The new challenge at Less is More is to use vellum. There are so many different ways to use vellum in your creations and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you all come up with! I had a few ideas in my head about how I wanted to use vellum and I decided I wanted to try foiling on it to see if it would work. I&amp;rsquo;m here to report that it works pretty well, although there are some splotchy spots so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t line art or sentiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #484*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another sketch challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. You can rotate the sketch if you like, but we need to be able to see the essence of the sketch in your creation. And those rectangles? You can use any shape you want!
My card was going to be one layer&amp;hellip; until I messed up the place of my splats so I trimmed down a front panel and adhered it to a new card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #549*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time before work yesterday to play along with the current challenge at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to use a piece I did with my Glimmer Hot Foil machine&amp;hellip;. used the solid foiling plate to use the left over foil from another project.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Hammermill Premium Color Copy; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; Scrapbook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge over at the Less is More blog&amp;hellip;. we are looking to see your one layer cards (which means the one layer is your card base) with your favourite flower! Be sure to head over to the Less is More blog to see the beautiful creations by the rest of the design team and to share your creations with us.
You knew this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a difficult challenge for me&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Circle in the Square*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of square cards&amp;hellip;. there&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with them, they look great, but I just don&amp;rsquo;t stray from my usual size very often. But for some reason, when I was designing this card, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working on a regular A2 card so I changed things up and LOVE how it looks on the square! I added two extra pieces from the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral Washi tape to the wreath for a little something &amp;ldquo;extra&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Your Day Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-31-your-day-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-31-your-day-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>I really love this glitter paper from Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! It&amp;rsquo;s in all of the new In Color colours that I love and I love that I can use one tone of it or the ombre effect. It adds a great little &amp;ldquo;something extra&amp;rdquo; to my cards!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Sweet Sorbet, In Color ombre sparkle paper
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #479*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! Two of these colours are not my favourites&amp;hellip; one of them I honestly only have two sheets of thanks to my friend Bonnie giving them to me! But I will admit&amp;hellip; this is a great colour combination and I am pretty happy with how my card turned out!
As I don&amp;rsquo;t have many Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! ink pads any more and I struggle with trying to find suitable matches with the inks I do have, most of my colour challenges will have cardstock as the colours instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Ombre Stripes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-15-ombre-stripes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-15-ombre-stripes/</guid>
      <description>Another quick post from me as I am dealing with a seized muscle in my back and sitting at my desk might kill me&amp;hellip; thankfully I have a few cards made and ready to share since I can&amp;rsquo;t sit here long enough to craft (and creating while in pain isn&amp;rsquo;t easy&amp;hellip; creativity doesn&amp;rsquo;t flow)
I have a die by Pink Fresh that does slimline strips and I like to use that when making thin strips because I know they will be accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Offset Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</guid>
      <description>I find myself always leaning towards the same layouts when I am using a circle element on my card (and squares too) so I consciously made an effort to do something different with this rainbow floral wreath.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral washi tape; foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Addicted to CAS! We are playing with the code word GRID for this challenge. I will admit that I struggled with this challenge. I had no idea how to interpret this word. But then I remembered I had some patterned papers that had a grid-look to them&amp;hellip; and I went with the one that was more delicate looking to create my card for today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</guid>
      <description>Is it good or bad that this Pink Fresh Studio stamp is one stamp with several images that you stamp, stencil and cut all at once? It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s bad because you get stuck with several cards that look similar.
The good news is that this is a LOVELY set and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create with it! And I get to play along with Color Hues again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling in the craft room in the last few days&amp;hellip; I sit there, wanting to create but nothing comes. Thankfully I have some cards already made to be able to share with you&amp;hellip; and it just so happens to fall in to the color challenge at Color Hues!
For the card today, I used the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral stamp, die and stencils&amp;hellip; but instead of using all of the layers of the stencil, I only used two to create the bit of blue on the flowers and the bit of green on the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for popping by today! I&amp;rsquo;m sharing with you, my card for the current clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards. We want you to use only 1 of the 9 rectangles on the front of your A2 card when you divide it up evenly (or 1/9 of any card size you like to use) with the optional twist of Butterflies.
The 1/9th is the hard part for this card&amp;hellip; I decided to use a little ink blending to create the rectangle to help me envision it&amp;hellip; to create a little dimension, I used glue along the body of the butterfly and foam adhesive on the wings to make them pop up a bit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #539</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</guid>
      <description>I created a quick card to play along with the current sketch at Freshly Made Sketches&amp;hellip; I had the card all put together and ready to photograph and I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it. So I used my stitched rectangle die to cut off the front of the card and layered it on to another card and I like it so much better. The extra panel and the stitched lines really helped to make this card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Thoughts*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back without another washi tape creation. The stamp and die with this Pink Fresh Studio set are one piece so it makes more sense to stamp it all and then cut it all&amp;hellip; the same goes with the washi tape. When I cut out the wreath for the card a few days ago, it only made sense to do it all. These were the other pieces I had so I threw them all on a panel to create a card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</guid>
      <description>Samantha is the host for the month of June at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches and she chose some great colours for our first challenge of the month! For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Craft Crew #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling Pinterest yesterday and found a card sketch I liked&amp;hellip; clicked the link and found a new to me challenge page called Paper Craft Crew. I had a little mojo this morning so I decided to play with their sketch.
I dipped in to my bin of extra die cuts and put together this card&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Balmy Balmy Blue
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Belated Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</guid>
      <description>On this day, 31 years ago, my hubby and I stood in front of family and friends and said &amp;ldquo;I do&amp;rdquo;. I know we&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot, seen a lot, made it through a lot&amp;hellip; but I have no idea where 31 years have gone! Happy Anniversary, Babe!
In other news, I saw my surgeon on Monday and he says my wrist is healing well. He says my progress is a little ahead of what he&amp;rsquo;d expect at this point and while I think he said that because I said I was frustrated with how slow it all is, I will try to remember that I am improving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #216*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at AAACards! AAA Cards is a clean and simple challenge blog that posts a new challenge every two weeks. We love to share our ideas on the cue cards and, more importantly, love to see what others come up with for our challenges! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
Let me explain our graphic a bit&amp;hellip; for challenge #216, we want you to use the colours that you see in the graphic&amp;hellip; and *optionally* we&amp;rsquo;d like to see a shaker card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a colour challenge over at the Less is More blog. For this challenge we are playing with my favourite colour combination&amp;hellip; RAINBOW! There is some wonderful inspiration to be seen created by the rest of the design team.. click HERE to check them out!
I absolutely love creating with rainbows&amp;hellip; they can be bright, muted, pastel, jewel toned&amp;hellip; whatever you feel like! I received my new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Sympathy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</guid>
      <description>I have guidelines (for myself, not for others) as to what a sympathy card should look like. I don&amp;rsquo;t judge what others create, but I do like to keep the cards I create simple and &amp;ldquo;toned down&amp;rdquo;. I needed a card for friends who recently suffered a loss and managed to create this card using some extras that were in my dish.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Old Olive
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; and this week it&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge. For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</guid>
      <description>Challenge #220 at Addicted to CAS is all about flowers&amp;hellip;. we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see your beautiful flower creations!
You get a bonus card from me today&amp;hellip;. I created my alcohol ink background and fit two flower dies on it &amp;hellip; and since they are so similar I decided to share them both in one post
I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your cards HERE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Special Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday the 13th crafty friends! If you&amp;rsquo;ve been here for a while, you know that my hubby and I celebrate Friday the 13th as we met (at a bar in the late 80s) on a Friday the 13th and got engaged on a Friday the 13th (our oldest son was born on the anniversary of the day Bruce proposed but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a Friday). We&amp;rsquo;ve been married 31 years (or it will be on June 1) so we figure it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty good day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip;. the challenge at Time Out Challenges is spring! I love spring and how the world seems to come back to life. I chose butterflies as they will be gracing our gardens soon!
I played with some white embossed Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and the awesome Birthday Brights rainbow paper from MFT on a slimline card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</guid>
      <description>The team at Addicted to CAS is playing with just one layer for challenge #218. To me, a one layer card means there is no other cardstock on the card other than the card itself. You can add a few embellishments (pearls if you need to) but there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any layers or dies (unless you do an inlaid technique). It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to do&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get depth and movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Cheers On Your Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Some more fun with those Pink Fresh Studio small butterflies and Tim Holtz inks. While I love how easy it was to get a lot of butterflies stamped and cut out at once, I wonder if I should have bought a stamp set with individual stamps and dies instead so that I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the need to overload on them all at once like I did with the flowers and now the butterflies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>Some more of those Pink Fresh Studio rainbow butterflies that I cut out &amp;hellip; I added a few matted layers and a strip of black and white stripes.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Orange Marmalade, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners; Perfect Layers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches is back with another sketch challenge to inspire you. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
I stamped up a sheet of those wonderful Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and embossed them in white this time. I used a finger dauber to add colour to this butterfly after I&amp;rsquo;d cut it out, trying to keep colours in specific areas&amp;hellip; it helped that I used similar colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Butterfly Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Some more love to Pink Fresh Studio and their products&amp;hellip; but lucky for you, I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to butterflies from flowers LOL! This is a great stamp that stamps up about a dozen butterflies all at once and the die cuts them all out at once as well. I stamped up a sheet of them with black ink and then blended some Tim Holtz inks over the top before cutting them all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You Make My Heart Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</guid>
      <description>This is the last of the cards using this stamp set&amp;hellip; at least for a few days. I will admit I did something else with a few of the dies a few days ago so there will be more coming. I hope I haven&amp;rsquo;t played with them too much in the last bit and will find that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pull the set out again!
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Another Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not quite done with the images from that Pink Fresh Studio stamp and die set&amp;hellip; I think there&amp;rsquo;s still a few more coming up. Can you tell how much I enjoyed playing with them?
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Concord Crush
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Birthday
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; MFT Stitched Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #211*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</guid>
      <description>Happy Thursday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at Time Out Challenges is back with a new photo inspiration challenge. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you create using the photo below as inspiration.
Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to not only be chosen to play along as a Guest Designer in an upcoming challenge but to win a $15 credit to shop at our sponsor, Poppystamps!
I used a layered diamond die cut pieces that I cut in half to create some blue and green and grey mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Daisy Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>I really had a lot of fun with these floral images by Pink Fresh Studio&amp;hellip; they are quick and easy to colour which makes them perfect for me. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I could do more with them to make my cards less clean and simple &amp;hellip;. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to challenge myself on that one sometime.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Lot More Fabulous*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; just a quick post from me today to share another card with this gorgeous floral stamp set by Pink Fresh Studio.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Seaside Spray
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Memento Tuxedo Black; Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners
*Embellishments: Nuvo Aqua Shimmer; Pink &amp;amp; Main Rainbow Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*May All Your Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</guid>
      <description>This is another card that I created after stamping up these wonderful floral images by Pink Fresh Studio. After I had finished the card, I decided it needed &amp;ldquo;something&amp;rdquo; so I pulled out a black marker to create the scattered dots around the image&amp;hellip; I have stamps that do this however I chose to do it after everything was already put together.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expression Simple Strips Birthday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Beautiful Blooms Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my friend Bonnie and I went to one of our favourite local stamp stores after I was done work. I will admit I bought a few things I didn&amp;rsquo;t need&amp;hellip; but I am so happy I did! This fabulous floral set from Pink Fresh is perfect for my colouring preferences&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ll see a few cards using this set in the next several days as I stamped them up at once and spent some time colouring.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
