<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spellbinders Hot Foil Glimmer Machine on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/spellbinders-hot-foil-glimmer-machine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spellbinders Hot Foil Glimmer Machine on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/spellbinders-hot-foil-glimmer-machine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Foiled with Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-07-foiled-with-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-07-foiled-with-tulips/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not honestly sure about this card&amp;hellip; it looks better in person than it does in this photo, but I&amp;rsquo;m still not sure about it. I had these white tulips cut out from a different project and had originally thought I&amp;rsquo;d blend ink on them. I had them laid out on a white piece of paper and I kind of liked how they looked so I went with it.
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Gold and Black Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</guid>
      <description>I am loving my new Glimmer Foil Machine and I just know I&amp;rsquo;m going to use it a lot during my Christmas card making season (which I think will begin very shortly!). The plate I used for this card is supposed to go across the card to create &amp;ldquo;lights&amp;rdquo; but I liked how it gave a neat background to play with going vertically instead.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #489*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the sketch this week at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! My card went together pretty quickly once I decided on what elements I wanted to use. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
My card uses a few pieces from my bin of extras that I kept overlooking. I had used just two of the layering stencils and these two pieces had very little colour on them&amp;hellip; so I grabbed my Copics and gave them a bit more colour before adding them to my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card is a mix of some extras fro my bin and some other things I cut especially for this card. I knew I wanted a wreath like card so I cut the knotted circle and then dug through my bin of extras for some flowers and leaves that might work. I then foiled my sentiment and cut it out to finish off the card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black and others from my stash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #488*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; we have some wonderfully fall colours to challenge you with this week. I will admit I was even thinking about some Christmas card ideas when I was first looking at these colours.
I decided to create a fall wreath and added a little hot foiling to finish it off.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Merry Merlot, Calypso Coral, Mossy Meadow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a no layer card challenge with AAACards&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;hellip; just the card itself! The optional twist is to make it a sympathy card.
Sympathy cards are not a card anyone wants to make&amp;hellip; but they are necessary to have in our stash. I personally like to make my sympathy cards subdued&amp;hellip; I was curious to see how the silver foil would look on grey cardstock so that&amp;rsquo;s what I played with for my challenge card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*I Share Everything*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-31-i-share-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-31-i-share-everything/</guid>
      <description>I like to share everything I make with you guys&amp;hellip; even if I don&amp;rsquo;t really like how it turned out. Some of the creations that I am not impressed with have had the most &amp;ldquo;likes&amp;rdquo; on social media. You never know what others like, so I share everything in hopes of inspiring someone else.
This is one of those cards&amp;hellip;. I keep pushing it back to share because I&amp;rsquo;m just not thrilled with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</guid>
      <description>The new challenge at Less is More is to use vellum. There are so many different ways to use vellum in your creations and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you all come up with! I had a few ideas in my head about how I wanted to use vellum and I decided I wanted to try foiling on it to see if it would work. I&amp;rsquo;m here to report that it works pretty well, although there are some splotchy spots so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t line art or sentiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #549*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time before work yesterday to play along with the current challenge at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to use a piece I did with my Glimmer Hot Foil machine&amp;hellip;. used the solid foiling plate to use the left over foil from another project.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Hammermill Premium Color Copy; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; Scrapbook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge over at the Less is More blog&amp;hellip;. we are looking to see your one layer cards (which means the one layer is your card base) with your favourite flower! Be sure to head over to the Less is More blog to see the beautiful creations by the rest of the design team and to share your creations with us.
You knew this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a difficult challenge for me&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
