<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Catherine Pooler on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/catherine-pooler/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Catherine Pooler on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/catherine-pooler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; we are playing with a one layer card which means we want ONLY ink on paper&amp;hellip; no added die cuts, no layers. The twist for this challenge is to draw your own frame. Please share your creations with us HERE!
I shared my first creation for this challenge a few days ago&amp;hellip; but then realized that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use the die cut butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #230*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS that starts today. The code word is Autumn. Play along with us by sharing you clean and simple cards HERE!
I had fun doing a little ink blending on a piece of cardstock and then stamping and cutting out these fun leaves. I don&amp;rsquo;t use a lot of brown in my cards but an autumn theme and these colours called for some brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Quick Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 09:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</guid>
      <description>When I did a stencilled background a while back I did an entire card front size and since I only used a portion of it, I had some more to play with for another card. I pulled out the leftover piece on a day I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of ideas in my head and this is what resulted.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Ink: Catherine Pooler Glitz, Over Coffee, Martini</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Hello*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-21-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-21-hello/</guid>
      <description>Recently I saw a card that was similar to this and I wanted to make one for myself&amp;hellip; I love the embossed polka dots in the background and then this simple but colourful greeting.
Card Info
*Ink: Catherine Pooler Fiesta Blue, Something Borrowed, Flirty Fuchia
*Dies: Concord &amp;amp; 9th Say Hellow
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! polka dot embossing folder</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Fall Failure*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</guid>
      <description>I was trying to do a more fall looking card with this but my colours (especially the yellow) were too bright. Of course I did a full 6X6 panel so I will be sharing another card with my too bright for fall flowers in the coming days.
I did a get well card because these colours looked so happy.
Card Info
*Images: MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Glitz, Martini, Over Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*TIme Out Challenges #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a word prompt challenge at Time Out Challenges. We have a $25 gift card to Lawn Fawn up for grabs for one lucky player!!
This is such a beautiful quote by Maya Angelou&amp;hellip;. and it&amp;rsquo;s something I try to do when I&amp;rsquo;m at work. I work at the front desk of a chiropractic clinic and we often see people who are in a lot of pain. I try had to be a bright spot in their day, maybe help them feel a little better for a few minutes while they have to interact with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #486*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new host this month at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; Patricia has chosen these fun colours to play with this week! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
As you will often see me say, I struggled with these colours. I don&amp;rsquo;t often put yellow on a card and certainly not with these other colours! I wanted to play with ink for this challenge so I had to pull some similar colours from my stash and I added the Mango Melody in a layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Subdued Thank You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Back in early July we lost a very good friend after a short illness&amp;hellip; it was devastating to lose a friend that we loved so much. She was one of my regular customers in terms of card orders. Her husband approached me after her funeral, asking if I would please make him some thank you cards to send out to people who helped out so much during her brief illness and after her death&amp;hellip; and I said &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #228*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Addicted to CAS. This challenge was difficult for me&amp;hellip;. because I don&amp;rsquo;t like birds! I have a few in my stash but they don&amp;rsquo;t really get used. But something different happened when the current Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! catalogue came out and I NEEDED these sweet bird stamps and the punch that goes with it!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Bermuda Bay, Pumpkin Pie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #238*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time earlier this week to play along with the current TAG challenge at CAS on Friday. I have had this idea in my head for a bit and finally put it together for this card. I wanted to do it with just the tag on the card front to keep it more CAS but it just didn&amp;rsquo;t look right&amp;hellip; I had this piece of embossed cardstock on my desk, the leftovers from a previous creation, so I tried it and loved it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-11-time-out-challenges-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-11-time-out-challenges-220/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back as part of the design team at Time Out Challenges with a new challenge to get your creative juices flowing! This is one of two non-clean and simple blogs that I design for so let your creativity flow as much as you want with these challenges!
For the next two weeks, we want to see you create your own backgrounds! We have an awesome prize from Stamplorations available to be won as well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencilled Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I am back to work this afternoon after my week of isolation thanks to Covid. I am feeling really good except a lingering tiredness but I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will get better with time. I really need to just take planned holidays from work instead of illness and injury!!
A friend asked for some thank you cards recently so I did up a few different designs for her. I really liked the look of using the last bit of ink on the blending brush to go over the white spots left behind by stencilling so I did a few like this one&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Softened the Look*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</guid>
      <description>I will admit that I love stencils&amp;hellip; and I have a few dozen&amp;hellip; but I hardly use them because I feel intimidated by them. I think it&amp;rsquo;s because I prefer the clean and simple style for my creations and stencils tend to be pretty busy. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to pull them out to play with a little more often&amp;hellip; For this card I used the ink through the stencil and then the same colours of inks over top without the stencil to soften the look a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We want to see your cards with the design only along the edge (you can choose which edge) with the optional twist of &amp;ldquo;in the sea&amp;rdquo;.
This was tough for me because I had two design team obligations that were a similar theme back to back! And the themes aren&amp;rsquo;t something I find easy to do in the first place!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-23-addicted-to-cas-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-23-addicted-to-cas-225/</guid>
      <description>The code word at Addicted to CAS is Nautical&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along. The design team has created some fun ideas that you can see HERE.
I had a bit in my stash that would have been ok for this challenge but nothing that was speaking to me&amp;hellip; so I used some dies to create my nautical themed card instead.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, Starry Sky</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #478*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday my friends&amp;hellip; and a BIG happy birthday to my big sister! It&amp;rsquo;s a milestone birthday for her today and I&amp;rsquo;m sad to not be celebrating it with her. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. Patricia came up with this fun sketch for us all to try this week! I really look forward to seeing what *you* create!
I tried a few different things with this sketch and tossed them all in the bin&amp;hellip; until I decided to turn the sketch and then I came up with something I liked on my first try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Welcome Little One*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</guid>
      <description>I had a bunch of extra white flowers sitting in my bin of extras (that makes it sound huge&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s just a Gladware sandwich sized container) and I decided to colour them up with some soft ink blending to create a little wreath of flowers to go with this new sunburst embossing folder that I purchased.
Card Info
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Limoncello, All That Jazz, Sixteen Candles, It&amp;rsquo;s a Girl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We have a sketch for you this week with the added optional twist of flowers. Of course I did both (because I love florals!) Share your card with us HERE for a chance to be chosen as a guest designer in an upcoming challenge!
I always struggle with the placement of things like the sketch shows so I wanted to do something different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new one layer card challenge over at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; a one layer card means there are no other pieces of cardstock other than your card base. If you want to use dies, they have to be inlaid. For me, the best way to achieve a one layer card is some simple stamping.
*you may add words as well*
I had a thought in my head but had trouble getting all of the pieces together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #695*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</guid>
      <description>I pulled out a stencil that I purchased right before I broke my wrist. Ink blending still isn&amp;rsquo;t easy (and honestly it can hurt) but this was quick and I was able to get through it. I loved the look of the colours in the current Color Throwdown Challenge so that&amp;rsquo;s what I went with for this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; silver mirror
*Images: MFT Big Birthday Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More! We want to see your &amp;ldquo;masculine&amp;rdquo; themed cards for the next two weeks! Share them with us HERE!!!
I always struggle with masculine cards. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much for masculine images and I tend towards purples and reds in my colour selections. I will admit, I almost skipped this challenge! I was poking around Pinterest and searched for &amp;ldquo;masculine colour combinations&amp;rdquo; and something similar to what I used popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; for challenge #215 we have a wonderful prize available to be won thanks to our generous sponsor, STAMPlorations. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
For this challenge, we want you to be inspired by the photo in the card below. You can take anything from this inspiration photo and translate it on to your creation. I struggled with this photo&amp;hellip; until I remembered that inspiration can come from anything in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #216*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at AAACards! AAA Cards is a clean and simple challenge blog that posts a new challenge every two weeks. We love to share our ideas on the cue cards and, more importantly, love to see what others come up with for our challenges! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
Let me explain our graphic a bit&amp;hellip; for challenge #216, we want you to use the colours that you see in the graphic&amp;hellip; and *optionally* we&amp;rsquo;d like to see a shaker card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #403*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-03-casology-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-03-casology-403/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends&amp;hellip; I saw my surgeon yesterday and as expected, the plaster splint was removed and I now have a removable brace. I can wear the brace when I&amp;rsquo;m up and about or if the arm/wrist is fatigued. I have some stretches thatI&amp;rsquo;ve started doing that are really tough but I am told it will all get easier&amp;hellip; I am to use my arm and wrist as tolerated for anything non-weight bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #462*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less is More. As you can see from the graphic below, the prompt is &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo;. As always, we hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with our challenge and share your creations with us HERE!
I struggled a bit with the challenge as I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any stamps that scream &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip; so I had to think outside the box a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</guid>
      <description>Bhavya is the host at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches for the month of April. She has chosen a great &amp;lsquo;garden&amp;rsquo; themed set of colours for us to use as her first colour challenge this month. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how others interpret these colours!
For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
