<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lawn Fawn on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/lawn-fawn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lawn Fawn on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/lawn-fawn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*TIme Out Challenges #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a word prompt challenge at Time Out Challenges. We have a $25 gift card to Lawn Fawn up for grabs for one lucky player!!
This is such a beautiful quote by Maya Angelou&amp;hellip;. and it&amp;rsquo;s something I try to do when I&amp;rsquo;m at work. I work at the front desk of a chiropractic clinic and we often see people who are in a lot of pain. I try had to be a bright spot in their day, maybe help them feel a little better for a few minutes while they have to interact with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #486*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new host this month at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; Patricia has chosen these fun colours to play with this week! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
As you will often see me say, I struggled with these colours. I don&amp;rsquo;t often put yellow on a card and certainly not with these other colours! I wanted to play with ink for this challenge so I had to pull some similar colours from my stash and I added the Mango Melody in a layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #485*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 5th Tuesday of the month so we have a double challenge for you at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! We&amp;rsquo;ve taken some retired Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! colours and an old sketch and want to see you combine the two to create something beautiful!
I had to move the sentiment on my card as it just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right floating up there in the left corner like in the sketch. I even made a square card, which I don&amp;rsquo;t do very often!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #484*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another sketch challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. You can rotate the sketch if you like, but we need to be able to see the essence of the sketch in your creation. And those rectangles? You can use any shape you want!
My card was going to be one layer&amp;hellip; until I messed up the place of my splats so I trimmed down a front panel and adhered it to a new card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #478*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday my friends&amp;hellip; and a BIG happy birthday to my big sister! It&amp;rsquo;s a milestone birthday for her today and I&amp;rsquo;m sad to not be celebrating it with her. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. Patricia came up with this fun sketch for us all to try this week! I really look forward to seeing what *you* create!
I tried a few different things with this sketch and tossed them all in the bin&amp;hellip; until I decided to turn the sketch and then I came up with something I liked on my first try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards Challenge#219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s July, it must be Christmas in July season! AAACards has an anything CAS Christmas challenge for this week with the optional twist of pets. Pull your Christmas stash out of storage and play along with us HERE!
You know I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy colouring so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go out for my animal&amp;hellip; so I chose this cute little birdie and coloured him up very simply. I love the mostly white card with just a hint of colour on the birdie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #698*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with the current challenge at Color Throwdown. I loved the look of the inspiration photo!
I have seen a few people do this idea of layering their die cuts to show the rainbow of colour&amp;hellip; it was harder to do than I expected, but I think it turned out OK!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Parakeet Party, Real Red, Yoyo Yellow, Pink Passion
*Dies: MFT Celebrate; Lawn Fawn Everyday Sentiment Banners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</guid>
      <description>I am so happy that Samantha chose some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for our challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches this week. I just love the new colours and especially these three! I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with this colour combination this week!
These colours are just so happy! They make me think of popsicles, and beach balls, and shovels and pails&amp;hellip; all those wonderfully fun things in the summer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #539</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</guid>
      <description>I created a quick card to play along with the current sketch at Freshly Made Sketches&amp;hellip; I had the card all put together and ready to photograph and I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it. So I used my stitched rectangle die to cut off the front of the card and layered it on to another card and I like it so much better. The extra panel and the stitched lines really helped to make this card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Craft Crew #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling Pinterest yesterday and found a card sketch I liked&amp;hellip; clicked the link and found a new to me challenge page called Paper Craft Crew. I had a little mojo this morning so I decided to play with their sketch.
I dipped in to my bin of extra die cuts and put together this card&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Balmy Balmy Blue
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Wish Big*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</guid>
      <description>Well *you* can&amp;rsquo;t see that this card says &amp;ldquo;wish big&amp;rdquo;, but it does. I used black ink on the blue cardstock and it&amp;rsquo;s really subtle but it&amp;rsquo;s there. I should have done something different, but honestly, the card was all put together when I decided to stamp on the strip. It was a bad decision LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Berry Burst, Lemon Lime Twist, Starry Sky
*Images: MFT Bitty Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another sketch with the team at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We look forward to seeing what you create this week following the sketch below. Remember to keep your creations clean and simple! You can share your cards with us HERE!
I will admit, this sketch had me scratching my head for a little bit. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what I wanted to do. I was flipping through my bin of dies and saw the balloons and decided to see what I could come up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another clean and simple challenge with the team at AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; with the optional twist of Easter or Spring. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations with us HERE!
I did a quick and easy card thanks to this wonderful Lawn Fawn strip of flowers. I stamped them, coloured them quickly with a few spring colours of Copics, stamped my greeting and then put the flowers on the card with some foam adhesive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Unicorn Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-15-unicorn-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-15-unicorn-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>I knew when I bought this Whittle Unicorn die that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t all that &amp;ldquo;whittle&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; but I sure wish it was. This is just a little too large for me, but as you can see, I bought it anyway!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! shimmer white, Basic Black; Lawn Fawn holographic
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versamark; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Mustard Seed, Spiced Marmalade, Twisted Citron, Salty Ocean</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Butterfly Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Some more love to Pink Fresh Studio and their products&amp;hellip; but lucky for you, I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to butterflies from flowers LOL! This is a great stamp that stamps up about a dozen butterflies all at once and the die cuts them all out at once as well. I stamped up a sheet of them with black ink and then blended some Tim Holtz inks over the top before cutting them all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Tuesday, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches. As it is the fifth Tuesday of a month, our challenge is a double&amp;hellip; Jeanne has chosen a past sketch and some retired colours to play with this week! Please make sure to have these three colours as the prominent colours of your clean and simple creation (but you can add neutrals as well). You are welcome to flip or rotate the sketch as long as the essence of the sketch remains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
