<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Taylored Expressions on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/taylored-expressions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Taylored Expressions on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/taylored-expressions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook and as always, we thank them for their generousity!
This is such a lovely image to get inspiration from. I used the tree along the side of the photo along with some silver and grey for my inspiration
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; Lawn Fawn Silver Holograpic
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a black and white clean and simple challenge this week at Less is More&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I used a portion of a great Poppy Stamps frame die to create the focal point on my card. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I feel about the uneven white mat around my focal point&amp;hellip; hmmmm Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #549*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time before work yesterday to play along with the current challenge at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to use a piece I did with my Glimmer Hot Foil machine&amp;hellip;. used the solid foiling plate to use the left over foil from another project.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Hammermill Premium Color Copy; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; Scrapbook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Bright on Black*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-04-bright-on-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-04-bright-on-black/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the look of bright colours on black&amp;hellip; I just love how they POP with brightness!! These new In Color colours from Stampin&#39; Up! are perfect for this!! Card Info
*Carstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Tahitian Tide, Sweet Sorbet, Parakeet Party
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #481*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; and for the month of August, I am the host! We are staring off this month with a colour challenge. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what everyone creates using these great colours! Be sure to check out the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches blog to see what the rest of the design team created!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #406*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-casology-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-casology-406/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology and the cue for this month is SAND. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check out what the rest of the design team has created and maybe even share a creation of your own!! You&amp;rsquo;ll find the CASology blog HERE
Despite loving the beach, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of a things that are beach themed&amp;hellip; so I had to think about how to create something with this cue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;. our theme for this challenge is Butterflies! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us and share your creations HERE! The design team has some beautiful butterfly cards for you to see&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to check them out!
I cut some of those gorgeous little butterflies out of glitter paper to create my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Prayers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</guid>
      <description>I found a little relief from my shoulder issue thanks to a visit to my physical therapist and a treatment of IMS. She uses accupuncture needles to poke in to the muscles to try to get them to release. I&amp;rsquo;m still hurting but not nearly as much as I have been over the last two weeks. I see her again early next week for another treatment&amp;hellip; until then I am trying to use my right arm &amp;ldquo;properly&amp;rdquo;, stretching, using heat and ice and trying to relax that arm as much as I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*When It Rains...*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</guid>
      <description>My blog title has nothing to do with my card today&amp;hellip; but it has to do with what&amp;rsquo;s going on in my world. As you know, I broke my right wrist in April. While I am getting mobility and strength back in that wrist, it would appear that the muscles around my right shoulder don&amp;rsquo;t like that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the arm in awkward ways and they have now seized up making it near impossible to sit upright at my desk, let alone create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Offset Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</guid>
      <description>I find myself always leaning towards the same layouts when I am using a circle element on my card (and squares too) so I consciously made an effort to do something different with this rainbow floral wreath.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral washi tape; foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Welcome Little One*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</guid>
      <description>I had a bunch of extra white flowers sitting in my bin of extras (that makes it sound huge&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s just a Gladware sandwich sized container) and I decided to colour them up with some soft ink blending to create a little wreath of flowers to go with this new sunburst embossing folder that I purchased.
Card Info
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Limoncello, All That Jazz, Sixteen Candles, It&amp;rsquo;s a Girl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #178*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 14:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</guid>
      <description>The current challenge at CAS on Friday is to make a thank you card. I love these open daisies by A Jillian Vance Design. I paired them with some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours to create my card for the challenge.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tahitian Tide, Parakeet Party, Sweet Sorbet, Starry Sky
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Designs Open Daisy; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Addicted to CAS! We are playing with the code word GRID for this challenge. I will admit that I struggled with this challenge. I had no idea how to interpret this word. But then I remembered I had some patterned papers that had a grid-look to them&amp;hellip; and I went with the one that was more delicate looking to create my card for today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*The Best Day Ever*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</guid>
      <description>I worked on this card a few weeks ago while my wrist was still pretty sore and useless (instead of kind of sore and useless like it is now) and decided to play with a design that featured patterned paper. Doing this made it all a little easier for me and my wrist but still allowed for me to feel like I was being creative.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Night of Navy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</guid>
      <description>Samantha is the host for the month of June at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches and she chose some great colours for our first challenge of the month! For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Craft Crew #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling Pinterest yesterday and found a card sketch I liked&amp;hellip; clicked the link and found a new to me challenge page called Paper Craft Crew. I had a little mojo this morning so I decided to play with their sketch.
I dipped in to my bin of extra die cuts and put together this card&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Balmy Balmy Blue
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Belated Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</guid>
      <description>On this day, 31 years ago, my hubby and I stood in front of family and friends and said &amp;ldquo;I do&amp;rdquo;. I know we&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot, seen a lot, made it through a lot&amp;hellip; but I have no idea where 31 years have gone! Happy Anniversary, Babe!
In other news, I saw my surgeon on Monday and he says my wrist is healing well. He says my progress is a little ahead of what he&amp;rsquo;d expect at this point and while I think he said that because I said I was frustrated with how slow it all is, I will try to remember that I am improving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Sympathy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</guid>
      <description>I have guidelines (for myself, not for others) as to what a sympathy card should look like. I don&amp;rsquo;t judge what others create, but I do like to keep the cards I create simple and &amp;ldquo;toned down&amp;rdquo;. I needed a card for friends who recently suffered a loss and managed to create this card using some extras that were in my dish.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Old Olive
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*More Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been doing a lot of crafting as my wrist has been sore again but I hope to sit in my craft room for a while today&amp;hellip; and maybe some mojo will flow.
Just a quick post from me today with more of those lovely Crafty Meraki tulips. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</guid>
      <description>Challenge #220 at Addicted to CAS is all about flowers&amp;hellip;. we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see your beautiful flower creations!
You get a bonus card from me today&amp;hellip;. I created my alcohol ink background and fit two flower dies on it &amp;hellip; and since they are so similar I decided to share them both in one post
I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your cards HERE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You Make My Heart Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</guid>
      <description>This is the last of the cards using this stamp set&amp;hellip; at least for a few days. I will admit I did something else with a few of the dies a few days ago so there will be more coming. I hope I haven&amp;rsquo;t played with them too much in the last bit and will find that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pull the set out again!
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Another Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not quite done with the images from that Pink Fresh Studio stamp and die set&amp;hellip; I think there&amp;rsquo;s still a few more coming up. Can you tell how much I enjoyed playing with them?
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Concord Crush
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Birthday
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; MFT Stitched Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</guid>
      <description>Bhavya is the host at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches for the month of April. She has chosen a great &amp;lsquo;garden&amp;rsquo; themed set of colours for us to use as her first colour challenge this month. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how others interpret these colours!
For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*May All Your Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</guid>
      <description>This is another card that I created after stamping up these wonderful floral images by Pink Fresh Studio. After I had finished the card, I decided it needed &amp;ldquo;something&amp;rdquo; so I pulled out a black marker to create the scattered dots around the image&amp;hellip; I have stamps that do this however I chose to do it after everything was already put together.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expression Simple Strips Birthday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Tuesday, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches. As it is the fifth Tuesday of a month, our challenge is a double&amp;hellip; Jeanne has chosen a past sketch and some retired colours to play with this week! Please make sure to have these three colours as the prominent colours of your clean and simple creation (but you can add neutrals as well). You are welcome to flip or rotate the sketch as long as the essence of the sketch remains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scraps for a Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-27-scraps-for-a-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-27-scraps-for-a-birthday/</guid>
      <description>I reached in to the bin of extras for the card today&amp;hellip; a little strip of patterned paper, an even smaller strip of cardstock and some flowers I&amp;rsquo;d cut out for something else. I love it when these cards can come together like this.
That strip of bright green cardstock was literally in my recycling bin&amp;hellip;.. it was a long skinny strip that I trimmed off for another card and I just made it the right length for the front of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
