<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Build Your Stash Holiday Cardmakers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-05-build-your-stash-holiday-cardmakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-05-build-your-stash-holiday-cardmakers/</guid>
      <description>I am very excited to announce that I have joined the design team at the Build Your Stash Holiday Cardmakers blog!! This is an awesome sketch challenge blog that has a new sketch each month, encouraging you to create Christmas cards each month. I will be sharing two cards each month with the monthly sketch. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check them out and join in the fun!
This is the sketch for October&amp;hellip; I LOVE that they include measurements!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a 1 of 9 rectangles challenge at AAACards with the optional twist of gnomes&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your cards where you use only one of the 9 rectangles found if you divide a rectangular card in 9ths. Be sure to keep it clean and simple and share it with us HERE!
You KNEW I&amp;rsquo;d have to use the optional twist! I used a non-Christmas gnome stamp set but added a tiny holiday wish to it to make it a Christmas card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook and as always, we thank them for their generousity!
This is such a lovely image to get inspiration from. I used the tree along the side of the photo along with some silver and grey for my inspiration
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; Lawn Fawn Silver Holograpic
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #487*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. This is a great sketch to showcase a little bit of patterned paper or an embossed panel&amp;hellip; or keep it just a solid colour. There are so many options!
I saw this sketch and immediately wanted to use this beautiful Stampin&#39; Up! paper from last year. It took a while for me to decide what to do with the other element on the card but I landed on the gnome and I like how it turned out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Perfectly CAS #30*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-29-perfectly-cas-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-29-perfectly-cas-30/</guid>
      <description>Happy Monday crafty friends! I am playing along with the challenge at Perfectly CAS today that wants to see a CAS card with embossing. I love the look of a hint of dry embossing on my creations and my first thought was to add a little sweater texture to a Christmas card. I embossed an entire panel and used this strip for this card and the rest on the card I posted yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations July*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-27-christmas-craft-creations-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-27-christmas-craft-creations-july/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the July theme of Patterned Paper at Christmas Craft Creations. This is a monthly challenge that helps you get at least one Christmas card made every month. The design team always has such wonderful creations&amp;hellip; you should check them out!
I got this one sheet of patterned paper at a garage sale and I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know why I bought it. I don&amp;rsquo;t scrapbook and honestly the design on it is really not suited to cutting down for Christmas cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; and that challenge is traditional Christmas. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll dig out some of your Christmas stash and play along with us!
To me, the traditional colours of Christmas are red, green and gold&amp;hellip;. and I think &amp;ldquo;sparkle&amp;rdquo; should be a Christmas colour as well LOL! I just love sparkly things, especially for Christmas cards!
Card Info
*Cardstock: assorted glitter papers
*Images: Simon Say Stamp Good Cheer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards Challenge#219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s July, it must be Christmas in July season! AAACards has an anything CAS Christmas challenge for this week with the optional twist of pets. Pull your Christmas stash out of storage and play along with us HERE!
You know I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy colouring so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go out for my animal&amp;hellip; so I chose this cute little birdie and coloured him up very simply. I love the mostly white card with just a hint of colour on the birdie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations April 2022*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations April challenge! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your Christmas cards using plaid or tartan!
When plaid first started being popular (again), I resisted it. I honestly wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan. But over the years it&amp;rsquo;s grown on me! There&amp;rsquo;s just something about a good old red and black buffalo check&amp;hellip;.
I had fun with some Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up plaid papers and the L&amp;rsquo;il Gnome from Simon Says Stamp</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
