<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CAS on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/cas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CAS on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/cas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; we are playing with a one layer card which means we want ONLY ink on paper&amp;hellip; no added die cuts, no layers. The twist for this challenge is to draw your own frame. Please share your creations with us HERE!
I shared my first creation for this challenge a few days ago&amp;hellip; but then realized that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use the die cut butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Foiled with Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-07-foiled-with-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-07-foiled-with-tulips/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not honestly sure about this card&amp;hellip; it looks better in person than it does in this photo, but I&amp;rsquo;m still not sure about it. I had these white tulips cut out from a different project and had originally thought I&amp;rsquo;d blend ink on them. I had them laid out on a white piece of paper and I kind of liked how they looked so I went with it.
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</guid>
      <description>October is Breast Cancer Awareness Month and the team at Time Out had originally had our challenge today as a Breast Cancer challenge&amp;hellip; as a colon cancer survivor (x2), I respectfully asked if we could change it to a cancer awareness challenge&amp;hellip; everyone knows about and talks about breast cancer, but no one talks about colon cancer (and many other cancers). It&amp;rsquo;s SO important to me that we talk about all forms of cancer, that we not be embarrassed about talking about our health, our bodies and the changes we are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #490*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how you all create with the colours below!
I&amp;rsquo;ve said it before&amp;hellip; I struggled with these three colours. This was a new level of struggle for me. If I wasn&amp;rsquo;t on the design team, I probably would have passed it up. I just could not do anything that I liked with these colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Gold and Black Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</guid>
      <description>I am loving my new Glimmer Foil Machine and I just know I&amp;rsquo;m going to use it a lot during my Christmas card making season (which I think will begin very shortly!). The plate I used for this card is supposed to go across the card to create &amp;ldquo;lights&amp;rdquo; but I liked how it gave a neat background to play with going vertically instead.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #230*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS that starts today. The code word is Autumn. Play along with us by sharing you clean and simple cards HERE!
I had fun doing a little ink blending on a piece of cardstock and then stamping and cutting out these fun leaves. I don&amp;rsquo;t use a lot of brown in my cards but an autumn theme and these colours called for some brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Striped Corners*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</guid>
      <description>How on earth is it the end of September already? I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling to write the word September at work and now, tomorrow, I have to write October?! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a great month here weatherwise and so far haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any snow fly (we often get the first snow in September). We actually hit 28C (82F) earlier this week which is unheard of at this time of year! I worry that winter will be a lot less kind than fall has been so far!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Free Form Frame*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</guid>
      <description>Another card from the bin of extras&amp;hellip;. I used a die as a guide to draw a rectangle on my card front with pencil&amp;hellip; and then went over it a few times with a thin black marker, not even trying to make straight lines. Once it had set for a bit I erased the pencil lines and then added in the hash marks and dots. I stamped my sentiment and added to my ink blended butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Quick Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 09:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</guid>
      <description>When I did a stencilled background a while back I did an entire card front size and since I only used a portion of it, I had some more to play with for another card. I pulled out the leftover piece on a day I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of ideas in my head and this is what resulted.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Ink: Catherine Pooler Glitz, Over Coffee, Martini</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #489*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the sketch this week at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! My card went together pretty quickly once I decided on what elements I wanted to use. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
My card uses a few pieces from my bin of extras that I kept overlooking. I had used just two of the layering stencils and these two pieces had very little colour on them&amp;hellip; so I grabbed my Copics and gave them a bit more colour before adding them to my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*So Very Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 09:12:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</guid>
      <description>I took a few days off from blogging&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of non-design team cards to share and honestly haven&amp;rsquo;t been feeling very creative lately. I am in my creative space for a while today and after I post this card I hope to have a little mojo flowing to create some stuff to share with you. I&amp;rsquo;m struggling to find my own ideas and am not feeling inspired by any of the cards I&amp;rsquo;ve pinned and saved to try to put my own spin on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</guid>
      <description>October 1st is World Cardmaking Day and here at Less is More, we are celebrating a little early with a friendship themed challenge! We think making a card for a friend is a great way to celebrate World Cardmaking Day! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of very good friends who are always there for me&amp;hellip; to listen, to provide support, to make me laugh, to distract me, to do social things with&amp;hellip; so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make a card that I could give to one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-23-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card is a mix of some extras fro my bin and some other things I cut especially for this card. I knew I wanted a wreath like card so I cut the knotted circle and then dug through my bin of extras for some flowers and leaves that might work. I then foiled my sentiment and cut it out to finish off the card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black and others from my stash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Hello*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-21-hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-21-hello/</guid>
      <description>Recently I saw a card that was similar to this and I wanted to make one for myself&amp;hellip; I love the embossed polka dots in the background and then this simple but colourful greeting.
Card Info
*Ink: Catherine Pooler Fiesta Blue, Something Borrowed, Flirty Fuchia
*Dies: Concord &amp;amp; 9th Say Hellow
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! polka dot embossing folder</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #488*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; we have some wonderfully fall colours to challenge you with this week. I will admit I was even thinking about some Christmas card ideas when I was first looking at these colours.
I decided to create a fall wreath and added a little hot foiling to finish it off.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Merry Merlot, Calypso Coral, Mossy Meadow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Fall Failure*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</guid>
      <description>I was trying to do a more fall looking card with this but my colours (especially the yellow) were too bright. Of course I did a full 6X6 panel so I will be sharing another card with my too bright for fall flowers in the coming days.
I did a get well card because these colours looked so happy.
Card Info
*Images: MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Glitz, Martini, Over Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 09:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</guid>
      <description>We have a colour challenge for you at AAACards this week&amp;hellip; with the optional twist of spots and dots. Use the graphic below to get your colour inspiration for your clean and simple cards.
The colours were a bit tough for me because while they look fine on this graphic, I had trouble getting them together on a card. I tried three different things before this one stuck&amp;hellip;
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #229*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another Addicted to CAS challenge&amp;hellip;
Just a quick post for me before I head off to work. I usually do my blogging on Wednesday mornings before work and I lost Wednesday morning to Urgent Care (see yesterdays post) so I am feeling more than a little behind!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Yupo
*Images: Studio Katia Birthday Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Alcohol Inks in Raspberry, Glacier, Alchemy (pearl)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Peekaboo Flowers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-16-peekaboo-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-16-peekaboo-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Have today off after picking up my coworkers shift on Tuesday. Feels strange. I do go back for a half day tomorrow. I am off in a few minutes for a massage and to head to one of my favourite creative stores to pick up a few things I ordered. A few other things might also make it in to my basket! I hope to come home and create as I&amp;rsquo;m way behind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Just Under The Wire*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-15-just-under-the-wire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 08:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-15-just-under-the-wire/</guid>
      <description>I had every intention of getting this post up yesterday but after a fall on Sunday (I missed the last step) I decided to take myself to Urgent Care yesterday before work. I managed to break the 5th metatarsal in my left foot and am now in a fancy boot/air cast. Sigh&amp;hellip;. If I didn&amp;rsquo;t have bad luck I&amp;rsquo;d have no luck at all!
Anyway&amp;hellip; I found a new to me challenge and decided to play along!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #487*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. This is a great sketch to showcase a little bit of patterned paper or an embossed panel&amp;hellip; or keep it just a solid colour. There are so many options!
I saw this sketch and immediately wanted to use this beautiful Stampin&#39; Up! paper from last year. It took a while for me to decide what to do with the other element on the card but I landed on the gnome and I like how it turned out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-12-simple-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 08:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-12-simple-thanks/</guid>
      <description>One thing I don&amp;rsquo;t love about the Pink Fresh Studio washi tapes is that when you use them, you kind of need to use the entire panel which means you always end up with pieces you don&amp;rsquo;t need right away. These pieces go in to my bin of extras and I pull them out when I have a need for them. Sometimes it means I have several cards in a row that look similar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #552*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</guid>
      <description>I got home from work yesterday and sat down in my creative space, hoping to make a card. I saw the latest sketch at Freshly Made Sketches and decided to try my hand at it&amp;hellip; I really hope my mojo shows up on the rest of my days off this week&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Paper: MFT Party Time
*Images: Pink Fresh Studios Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a black and white clean and simple challenge this week at Less is More&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I used a portion of a great Poppy Stamps frame die to create the focal point on my card. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I feel about the uneven white mat around my focal point&amp;hellip; hmmmm Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #239*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</guid>
      <description>I am playing along with the STRIPES challenge at CAS on Friday&amp;hellip;. this started out being a card for last weeks Freshly Made Sketches but I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to finish it in time to play along with this. I also liked the stripes on the side instead of the bottom better so I switched things up!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, glitter paper
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Foiled Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #486*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new host this month at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; Patricia has chosen these fun colours to play with this week! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
As you will often see me say, I struggled with these colours. I don&amp;rsquo;t often put yellow on a card and certainly not with these other colours! I wanted to play with ink for this challenge so I had to pull some similar colours from my stash and I added the Mango Melody in a layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #407*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-casology-407/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-casology-407/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month which means there is a new CASology challenge. Our cue for this month is HAPPY!
The cue is easy for me as the majority of the cards I make are for birthdays&amp;hellip; I pulled out some rainbow colours and an alphabet die set and created this for you!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Poppy Parade, Daffodil Delight, Granny Apple Green, Pacific Point, Highland Heather</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Subdued Thank You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Back in early July we lost a very good friend after a short illness&amp;hellip; it was devastating to lose a friend that we loved so much. She was one of my regular customers in terms of card orders. Her husband approached me after her funeral, asking if I would please make him some thank you cards to send out to people who helped out so much during her brief illness and after her death&amp;hellip; and I said &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-04-aaacards-223/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a no layer card challenge with AAACards&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s right&amp;hellip; just the card itself! The optional twist is to make it a sympathy card.
Sympathy cards are not a card anyone wants to make&amp;hellip; but they are necessary to have in our stash. I personally like to make my sympathy cards subdued&amp;hellip; I was curious to see how the silver foil would look on grey cardstock so that&amp;rsquo;s what I played with for my challenge card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #228*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Addicted to CAS. This challenge was difficult for me&amp;hellip;. because I don&amp;rsquo;t like birds! I have a few in my stash but they don&amp;rsquo;t really get used. But something different happened when the current Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! catalogue came out and I NEEDED these sweet bird stamps and the punch that goes with it!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Bermuda Bay, Pumpkin Pie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Washi Floral*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</guid>
      <description>I am running out of cards to share with you! I lost some time with card making first with my broken wrist in the spring and then again in August with Covid. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good these days but I feel like life has been busy and the mojo is harder to come by! I sit at my craft desk but get nothing accomplished! I hope my creative block doesn&amp;rsquo;t last too long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Super Simple*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-01-super-simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-01-super-simple/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the simplicity of this card&amp;hellip; a little foam tape to make the white on white layer pop a little and voila! And who doesn&amp;rsquo;t love that sparkly paper?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #485*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 5th Tuesday of the month so we have a double challenge for you at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! We&amp;rsquo;ve taken some retired Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! colours and an old sketch and want to see you combine the two to create something beautiful!
I had to move the sentiment on my card as it just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right floating up there in the left corner like in the sketch. I even made a square card, which I don&amp;rsquo;t do very often!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Perfectly CAS #30*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-29-perfectly-cas-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-29-perfectly-cas-30/</guid>
      <description>Happy Monday crafty friends! I am playing along with the challenge at Perfectly CAS today that wants to see a CAS card with embossing. I love the look of a hint of dry embossing on my creations and my first thought was to add a little sweater texture to a Christmas card. I embossed an entire panel and used this strip for this card and the rest on the card I posted yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #238*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time earlier this week to play along with the current TAG challenge at CAS on Friday. I have had this idea in my head for a bit and finally put it together for this card. I wanted to do it with just the tag on the card front to keep it more CAS but it just didn&amp;rsquo;t look right&amp;hellip; I had this piece of embossed cardstock on my desk, the leftovers from a previous creation, so I tried it and loved it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</guid>
      <description>The new challenge at Less is More is to use vellum. There are so many different ways to use vellum in your creations and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you all come up with! I had a few ideas in my head about how I wanted to use vellum and I decided I wanted to try foiling on it to see if it would work. I&amp;rsquo;m here to report that it works pretty well, although there are some splotchy spots so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t line art or sentiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scrappy Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Once again I used my bin of extras to create this card&amp;hellip; the flower, leaves and stitched rectangle were all already cut and unused from other projects.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Lemon Lime Twist, Berry Burst
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms: MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Embellishments: Studio Katia Arctic Breeze Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #484*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another sketch challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. You can rotate the sketch if you like, but we need to be able to see the essence of the sketch in your creation. And those rectangles? You can use any shape you want!
My card was going to be one layer&amp;hellip; until I messed up the place of my splats so I trimmed down a front panel and adhered it to a new card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Black White and Gold*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-22-black-white-and-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-22-black-white-and-gold/</guid>
      <description>The most difficult part of this card was getting the gold cord to look good&amp;hellip;. LOL! I&amp;rsquo;m still not sure I like how it turned out but after about 12 minutes of fiddling with it, I decided to leave it alone.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Concord &amp;amp; 9th Hello Sunshine
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Waffle Flower Additional Circles
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! embossing folder; gold cord</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #227*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS today&amp;hellip; time to show us your clean and simple creations featuring the colour pink!
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why but I struggled with this prompt&amp;hellip;. but then I gabbed out some stencils and had a little play with them. I stencilled the pink swirls first and then put a second stencil on top of the first stencil and used Glimmer Paste so that the sparkly circles only showed up on the pink swirls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #706*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-19-color-throwdown-706/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-19-color-throwdown-706/</guid>
      <description>I had to play along with the latest challenge at Color Throwdown because I really love the look of blue and green together. I usually choose the brighter forms of these colours to go together but I strayed from that with this card to use up a scrap of very old patterned paper I had in my stash.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Marina Mist
*Paper: My Mind&amp;rsquo;s Eye
*Images: Spellbinders Sentiments for Your</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #549*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time before work yesterday to play along with the current challenge at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to use a piece I did with my Glimmer Hot Foil machine&amp;hellip;. used the solid foiling plate to use the left over foil from another project.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Hammermill Premium Color Copy; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; Scrapbook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-17-striped-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-17-striped-flower/</guid>
      <description>This was a great way to use a little bit of patterned paper&amp;hellip; Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pattern Party
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Design Open Daisy; MFT Celebrate
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners
*Etc: foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Candles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-15-paper-candles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-15-paper-candles/</guid>
      <description>I truly have a lot of patterned paper&amp;hellip; and I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know why since it often doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit in to a clean and simple style! I think because it&amp;rsquo;s just so darn pretty! I go through periods where I use it a lot and periods where I don&amp;rsquo;t use it much. I think I need to go through a period where I don&amp;rsquo;t buy it.
Thanks so much to Nadine (@scrappinready on Instagram) for the inspiration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In Color Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I just love the 2022-24 Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours&amp;hellip;. but I don&amp;rsquo;t find I use all of them much. I am really drawn to the red, green and light blue but not the two darker colours as much. So I grabbed all five for this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, Parakeet Party, Tahitian Tide, Orchid Oasis, Starry Sky
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge over at the Less is More blog&amp;hellip;. we are looking to see your one layer cards (which means the one layer is your card base) with your favourite flower! Be sure to head over to the Less is More blog to see the beautiful creations by the rest of the design team and to share your creations with us.
You knew this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a difficult challenge for me&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-12-striped-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-12-striped-thanks/</guid>
      <description>This was a super quick card to throw together&amp;hellip;. that striped paper did all of the work!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Picture Perfect Party
*Dies: Simon Says Stamp Big Words</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencilled Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I am back to work this afternoon after my week of isolation thanks to Covid. I am feeling really good except a lingering tiredness but I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will get better with time. I really need to just take planned holidays from work instead of illness and injury!!
A friend asked for some thank you cards recently so I did up a few different designs for her. I really liked the look of using the last bit of ink on the blending brush to go over the white spots left behind by stencilling so I did a few like this one&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Black &amp; White with Sparkle*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long week away from my creative space as I&amp;rsquo;ve been isolating in the main bedroom of our home because I got Covid. Honestly I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of energy some days so I didn&amp;rsquo;t miss the creative time all that much, but as I started to feel better I wished I could sit at my desk and play. I am now feeling better and out of isolation but wearing a mask when others are around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the first clean and simple challenge of August with AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; which means you should use a few small images on your card&amp;hellip; the optional twist is (lady)bugs. The design team has some wonderful inspiration on the blog. We hope to see you playing along with us!
I love ladybugs and they are so easy to colour for someone like me who doesn&amp;rsquo;t find colouring zen-inducing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Masked Word*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</guid>
      <description>I tried something a little different (at least for me) with this card&amp;hellip; nothing earth shattering, but I masked off the word celebrate before I ink blended over a stencil. Before I removed my mask, I also blended a little more of the same colours of ink over the piece after removing the stencil to soften the look of the colours a little and to really make my word pop. I like how it all looks kind of soft and dreamy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Bright on Black*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-04-bright-on-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-04-bright-on-black/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the look of bright colours on black&amp;hellip; I just love how they POP with brightness!! These new In Color colours from Stampin&#39; Up! are perfect for this!! Card Info
*Carstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Tahitian Tide, Sweet Sorbet, Parakeet Party
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Circle in the Square*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of square cards&amp;hellip;. there&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with them, they look great, but I just don&amp;rsquo;t stray from my usual size very often. But for some reason, when I was designing this card, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working on a regular A2 card so I changed things up and LOVE how it looks on the square! I added two extra pieces from the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral Washi tape to the wreath for a little something &amp;ldquo;extra&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #481*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; and for the month of August, I am the host! We are staring off this month with a colour challenge. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what everyone creates using these great colours! Be sure to check out the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches blog to see what the rest of the design team created!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #406*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-casology-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-casology-406/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology and the cue for this month is SAND. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check out what the rest of the design team has created and maybe even share a creation of your own!! You&amp;rsquo;ll find the CASology blog HERE
Despite loving the beach, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of a things that are beach themed&amp;hellip; so I had to think about how to create something with this cue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Your Day Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-31-your-day-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-31-your-day-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>I really love this glitter paper from Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! It&amp;rsquo;s in all of the new In Color colours that I love and I love that I can use one tone of it or the ombre effect. It adds a great little &amp;ldquo;something extra&amp;rdquo; to my cards!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Sweet Sorbet, In Color ombre sparkle paper
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;. our theme for this challenge is Butterflies! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us and share your creations HERE! The design team has some beautiful butterfly cards for you to see&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to check them out!
I cut some of those gorgeous little butterflies out of glitter paper to create my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Petals*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-29-birthday-petals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-29-birthday-petals/</guid>
      <description>I used two leaf dies and some distress ink to create a rainbow flower&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Ink: Tim Holtz Picked Raspberry, Carved Pumpkin, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron, Peacock Feathers, Salty Ocean, Wilted Violet
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms
*Etc: computer generated sentiment printed on the laser printer and foiled</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #480*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches today&amp;hellip;. remember you can rotate or flip this sketch if you want, as long as the essence of the sketch is seen in your card. Share your creations with us HERE as we love to see what everyone else comes up with!
A friend asked for a bunch of thank you cards last week so I of course made her some!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We want to see your cards with the design only along the edge (you can choose which edge) with the optional twist of &amp;ldquo;in the sea&amp;rdquo;.
This was tough for me because I had two design team obligations that were a similar theme back to back! And the themes aren&amp;rsquo;t something I find easy to do in the first place!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Prayers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</guid>
      <description>I found a little relief from my shoulder issue thanks to a visit to my physical therapist and a treatment of IMS. She uses accupuncture needles to poke in to the muscles to try to get them to release. I&amp;rsquo;m still hurting but not nearly as much as I have been over the last two weeks. I see her again early next week for another treatment&amp;hellip; until then I am trying to use my right arm &amp;ldquo;properly&amp;rdquo;, stretching, using heat and ice and trying to relax that arm as much as I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #479*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! Two of these colours are not my favourites&amp;hellip; one of them I honestly only have two sheets of thanks to my friend Bonnie giving them to me! But I will admit&amp;hellip; this is a great colour combination and I am pretty happy with how my card turned out!
As I don&amp;rsquo;t have many Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! ink pads any more and I struggle with trying to find suitable matches with the inks I do have, most of my colour challenges will have cardstock as the colours instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; and that challenge is traditional Christmas. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll dig out some of your Christmas stash and play along with us!
To me, the traditional colours of Christmas are red, green and gold&amp;hellip;. and I think &amp;ldquo;sparkle&amp;rdquo; should be a Christmas colour as well LOL! I just love sparkly things, especially for Christmas cards!
Card Info
*Cardstock: assorted glitter papers
*Images: Simon Say Stamp Good Cheer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Ombre Stripes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-15-ombre-stripes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-15-ombre-stripes/</guid>
      <description>Another quick post from me as I am dealing with a seized muscle in my back and sitting at my desk might kill me&amp;hellip; thankfully I have a few cards made and ready to share since I can&amp;rsquo;t sit here long enough to craft (and creating while in pain isn&amp;rsquo;t easy&amp;hellip; creativity doesn&amp;rsquo;t flow)
I have a die by Pink Fresh that does slimline strips and I like to use that when making thin strips because I know they will be accurate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-14-time-out-challenges-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-14-time-out-challenges-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for you to be inspired by words with the latest Time Out Challenge&amp;hellip; you can see the quote in the graphic below. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook&amp;hellip; if you share your card with us you&amp;rsquo;ll have a chance at winning a prize from them!
I read this quote over and over and over again and the word that stood out to me each time was &amp;ldquo;dream&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; so I made a &amp;ldquo;dreamy&amp;rdquo; card for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #235*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip; a quick post from me today to share my creations for the current CAS on Friday challenge. The current challenge is &amp;ldquo;silhouette&amp;rdquo; and instead of stamping, I did a black die cut instead. I used my Copics to create a little rainbow and then put the die cut floral spring on top of it. Because I used Copics, I used a smaller panel and put it on top of a white card so that the ink bleeding wouldn&amp;rsquo;t show through to the inside of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #478*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday my friends&amp;hellip; and a BIG happy birthday to my big sister! It&amp;rsquo;s a milestone birthday for her today and I&amp;rsquo;m sad to not be celebrating it with her. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. Patricia came up with this fun sketch for us all to try this week! I really look forward to seeing what *you* create!
I tried a few different things with this sketch and tossed them all in the bin&amp;hellip; until I decided to turn the sketch and then I came up with something I liked on my first try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #543*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-11-freshly-made-sketches-543/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-11-freshly-made-sketches-543/</guid>
      <description>I loved the sketch the Cecile had for Freshly Made Sketches this week&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m glad I had a few minutes at my craft table to play along!
My card originally much more plain as I stamped directly on the larger white square and put the card together. The more I looked at it the more I knew it needed a little something more. I cut a smaller square and stamped on it then used my Perfect Layers tool to create a green border and then put it on top of what I had originally created&amp;hellip; and it looks SO much better in my opinion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards Challenge#219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s July, it must be Christmas in July season! AAACards has an anything CAS Christmas challenge for this week with the optional twist of pets. Pull your Christmas stash out of storage and play along with us HERE!
You know I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy colouring so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go out for my animal&amp;hellip; so I chose this cute little birdie and coloured him up very simply. I love the mostly white card with just a hint of colour on the birdie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Offset Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</guid>
      <description>I find myself always leaning towards the same layouts when I am using a circle element on my card (and squares too) so I consciously made an effort to do something different with this rainbow floral wreath.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral washi tape; foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Welcome Little One*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-07-welcome-little-one/</guid>
      <description>I had a bunch of extra white flowers sitting in my bin of extras (that makes it sound huge&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s just a Gladware sandwich sized container) and I decided to colour them up with some soft ink blending to create a little wreath of flowers to go with this new sunburst embossing folder that I purchased.
Card Info
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Limoncello, All That Jazz, Sixteen Candles, It&amp;rsquo;s a Girl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Wish Big*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-06-striped-wish-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-06-striped-wish-big/</guid>
      <description>I am in LOVE with this sparkle paper from Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! I used some thin strips of it, making sure to get the ombre to create my card today.
Card Info
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color ombre sparkle paper
*Images: Uniko Birthday Wishes
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Design Daisy
*Embellishments: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!
*Challenges: The Flower Challenge #70</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #405*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology... our cue for you for July is WINDY.
I have a funny wind story&amp;hellip; last fall we put up some security cameras over our garage. Since the trees have leafed this year, we often get alerts from the cameras of &amp;ldquo;motion&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the other day we had hundreds of alerts in the morning when we work up&amp;hellip; each one of them was the leaves on the trees thanks to the wind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #699*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</guid>
      <description>I love the inspiration photo from the current Color Throwdown challenge so I had to play along. But then I was stumped as to what I wanted to do&amp;hellip; I do much better with sketch challenges than colour challenges I think!
I pulled out a stencil I haven&amp;rsquo;t used yet and this is the result. I was going to orient my card the other way however the glitter paste made a mess in one area under the stencil so I flipped the panel and covered it with my sentiment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #342*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-03-freshly-made-sketches-342/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-03-freshly-made-sketches-342/</guid>
      <description>I loved the ease of the sketch by Kim at Freshly Made Sketches this week. I combined the idea of using patterned paper with Kim&amp;rsquo;s idea of horizontal stripes to create my card. I also used a stamp and die that I bought YEARS ago that I&amp;rsquo;ve never used!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Granny Apple Green
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pattern Party
*Images: Scrapbook &amp;amp; Cards Today; MFT Bitty Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #468*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Less is More&amp;hellip;. our cue word for challenge #468 is &amp;ldquo;emboss&amp;rdquo;. You can use any interpretation of the word in your clean and simple card.
I decided to go with an embossing folder for my card&amp;hellip; and I grabbed the etched butterflies from my pile of extras from the card I shared a few days ago as I think they look embossed as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #178*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 14:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</guid>
      <description>The current challenge at CAS on Friday is to make a thank you card. I love these open daisies by A Jillian Vance Design. I paired them with some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours to create my card for the challenge.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tahitian Tide, Parakeet Party, Sweet Sorbet, Starry Sky
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Designs Open Daisy; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*White Daisies*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-white-daisies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-white-daisies/</guid>
      <description>How on earth is it July already?!?!?! I wish the warm months could slow down just a little bit&amp;hellip;. I love the extra sunlight and warmth (especially compared to the cold and dark of winter).
I want you to click on this card so you can zoom in a little bit because no matter how hard I tried, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get my photo to look good at a small size. I LOVE how this card turned out and I just wish it looked better in a photograph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</guid>
      <description>Time Out Challenges is back with a great new challenge&amp;hellip; this time we want you to be inspired by being kind! Our sponsor for this challenge is CAS-ual Friday stamps.
I got these wonderful new dies from Paper Rose and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to play with them. I love how they look cut out of the gold foil cardstock!
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Simon Says Stamp Big Thanks Words; Stampendous Big Words Thanks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #476*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the last sketch challenge for the month of June with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; our sketch this time is a slimline card and I went for a mini-slimline as I prefer that size.
I took, a large floral stamp but only used a part of it so it would fit on my card. I even pulled out my Copics to do a little colouring (which isn&amp;rsquo;t easy as my wrist heals)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card was so super easy to put together&amp;hellip; and I love it! The hardest part was figuring out where the flowers should go!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Images: Gina K Where Flowers Bloom
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms; MFT Stitched Circles; Waffle Flower Additional Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We have a sketch for you this week with the added optional twist of flowers. Of course I did both (because I love florals!) Share your card with us HERE for a chance to be chosen as a guest designer in an upcoming challenge!
I always struggle with the placement of things like the sketch shows so I wanted to do something different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Addicted to CAS! We are playing with the code word GRID for this challenge. I will admit that I struggled with this challenge. I had no idea how to interpret this word. But then I remembered I had some patterned papers that had a grid-look to them&amp;hellip; and I went with the one that was more delicate looking to create my card for today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #698*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with the current challenge at Color Throwdown. I loved the look of the inspiration photo!
I have seen a few people do this idea of layering their die cuts to show the rainbow of colour&amp;hellip; it was harder to do than I expected, but I think it turned out OK!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Parakeet Party, Real Red, Yoyo Yellow, Pink Passion
*Dies: MFT Celebrate; Lawn Fawn Everyday Sentiment Banners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations Trees*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still some time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations June theme of TREES! This is a great challenge to help you get a few Christmas cards made throughout the year. I had promised myself to make more Christmas cards before October and while I&amp;rsquo;ve done that, it&amp;rsquo;s really only been for this challenge! Maybe I should make one day a month where I make only Christmas cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</guid>
      <description>I am so happy that Samantha chose some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for our challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches this week. I just love the new colours and especially these three! I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with this colour combination this week!
These colours are just so happy! They make me think of popsicles, and beach balls, and shovels and pails&amp;hellip; all those wonderfully fun things in the summer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</guid>
      <description>Is it good or bad that this Pink Fresh Studio stamp is one stamp with several images that you stamp, stencil and cut all at once? It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s bad because you get stuck with several cards that look similar.
The good news is that this is a LOVELY set and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create with it! And I get to play along with Color Hues again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling in the craft room in the last few days&amp;hellip; I sit there, wanting to create but nothing comes. Thankfully I have some cards already made to be able to share with you&amp;hellip; and it just so happens to fall in to the color challenge at Color Hues!
For the card today, I used the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral stamp, die and stencils&amp;hellip; but instead of using all of the layers of the stencil, I only used two to create the bit of blue on the flowers and the bit of green on the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new one layer card challenge over at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; a one layer card means there are no other pieces of cardstock other than your card base. If you want to use dies, they have to be inlaid. For me, the best way to achieve a one layer card is some simple stamping.
*you may add words as well*
I had a thought in my head but had trouble getting all of the pieces together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sweet Birthday Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-17-sweet-birthday-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-17-sweet-birthday-wishes/</guid>
      <description>A quick and easy card from me today&amp;hellip; not honestly sure where I got this colour combination. I know I didn&amp;rsquo;t come up with it on my own since I use coral and yellow so seldom! Hmmmm, I wish I could remember.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Seaside Spray, Pineapple Punch, Flirty Flamingo
*Images: MFT Bitty Birthday Wishes
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms
*Etc: bling from my stash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*The Best Day Ever*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</guid>
      <description>I worked on this card a few weeks ago while my wrist was still pretty sore and useless (instead of kind of sore and useless like it is now) and decided to play with a design that featured patterned paper. Doing this made it all a little easier for me and my wrist but still allowed for me to feel like I was being creative.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Night of Navy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Two Challenges*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with two challenges today&amp;hellip; Color Throwdown #696 and CAS on Friday #233. The colours of the first challenge fit the theme of &amp;ldquo;condolence&amp;rdquo; for the second challenge absolutely perfectly!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Very Vanilla, Crumb Cake, Pear Pizzazz
*Images: Altenew Flower Vine
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms, Spendid Stems; MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Etc: foam adhesive
*Challenges: Color Throwdown #696; CAS on Friday #233</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Pop of Red*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</guid>
      <description>For my card today, I searched through the archives at CAS Colours and Sketches to find a sketch I wanted to play with &amp;hellip; this was challenge #426 which was a colour and sketch challenge, but I only used the sketch.
What you can&amp;rsquo;t see in this photo is that I used a piercing cover plate die on the black banner which adds a little visual interest
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</guid>
      <description>Samantha is the host for the month of June at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches and she chose some great colours for our first challenge of the month! For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #404*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pop by the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done with the cue of RIDE. We love to see your clean and simple creations too&amp;hellip; share them HERE!
I almost skipped this challenge but then remembered this cute set from My Favorite Things and decided I&amp;rsquo;d give it a go. It&amp;rsquo;s not really my &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I pushed myself a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #42*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</guid>
      <description>I saw a few cards on some Facebook groups I&amp;rsquo;m on as well as on Instagram, using the current challenge from Color Hues&amp;hellip; and while I don&amp;rsquo;t often reach for yellow, I really felt like I wanted to play along with this challenge. I love black and white with a pop of colour&amp;hellip; I usually do red, but yellow sure does look happy!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Daffodil Delight, Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More! We want to see your &amp;ldquo;masculine&amp;rdquo; themed cards for the next two weeks! Share them with us HERE!!!
I always struggle with masculine cards. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much for masculine images and I tend towards purples and reds in my colour selections. I will admit, I almost skipped this challenge! I was poking around Pinterest and searched for &amp;ldquo;masculine colour combinations&amp;rdquo; and something similar to what I used popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made #538*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-freshly-made-538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-freshly-made-538/</guid>
      <description>I was able to get myself caught up with design team duties and found a little time to play with some current challenges. Today I&amp;rsquo;m sharing the card I created for the latest sketch at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to grab this flower from my bin of extras to add a pop of colour to my black and white card.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; for challenge #215 we have a wonderful prize available to be won thanks to our generous sponsor, STAMPlorations. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
For this challenge, we want you to be inspired by the photo in the card below. You can take anything from this inspiration photo and translate it on to your creation. I struggled with this photo&amp;hellip; until I remembered that inspiration can come from anything in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Belated Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</guid>
      <description>On this day, 31 years ago, my hubby and I stood in front of family and friends and said &amp;ldquo;I do&amp;rdquo;. I know we&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot, seen a lot, made it through a lot&amp;hellip; but I have no idea where 31 years have gone! Happy Anniversary, Babe!
In other news, I saw my surgeon on Monday and he says my wrist is healing well. He says my progress is a little ahead of what he&amp;rsquo;d expect at this point and while I think he said that because I said I was frustrated with how slow it all is, I will try to remember that I am improving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Wish Big*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</guid>
      <description>Well *you* can&amp;rsquo;t see that this card says &amp;ldquo;wish big&amp;rdquo;, but it does. I used black ink on the blue cardstock and it&amp;rsquo;s really subtle but it&amp;rsquo;s there. I should have done something different, but honestly, the card was all put together when I decided to stamp on the strip. It was a bad decision LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Berry Burst, Lemon Lime Twist, Starry Sky
*Images: MFT Bitty Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #216*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at AAACards! AAA Cards is a clean and simple challenge blog that posts a new challenge every two weeks. We love to share our ideas on the cue cards and, more importantly, love to see what others come up with for our challenges! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
Let me explain our graphic a bit&amp;hellip; for challenge #216, we want you to use the colours that you see in the graphic&amp;hellip; and *optionally* we&amp;rsquo;d like to see a shaker card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenged with Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; for the next two weeks, we want to see you sharing your cards featuring stripes! I am the host for this challenge, which means this theme was my idea! Please share your clean and simple cards with strips with us HERE!
I had a bit of trouble deciding on what I wanted to do for my card for this challenge&amp;hellip; I have a lot of options when it comes to stripes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another sketch with the team at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We look forward to seeing what you create this week following the sketch below. Remember to keep your creations clean and simple! You can share your cards with us HERE!
I will admit, this sketch had me scratching my head for a little bit. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what I wanted to do. I was flipping through my bin of dies and saw the balloons and decided to see what I could come up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Washi Tape*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</guid>
      <description>Happy Sunday all&amp;hellip; in true Calgary fashion, our first long weekend of &amp;ldquo;summer&amp;rdquo; has delivered us a mixed bag of weather. Friday it was really windy and wet and we had a little snow falling from the sky. Saturday was cool and mostly cloudy. So far this morning the sun is shining and it&amp;rsquo;s warming up a little. This is what you get with an elevation of 1045 m above sea level (that&amp;rsquo;s 3428 ft).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a colour challenge over at the Less is More blog. For this challenge we are playing with my favourite colour combination&amp;hellip; RAINBOW! There is some wonderful inspiration to be seen created by the rest of the design team.. click HERE to check them out!
I absolutely love creating with rainbows&amp;hellip; they can be bright, muted, pastel, jewel toned&amp;hellip; whatever you feel like! I received my new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Sympathy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 08:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-20-simple-sympathy/</guid>
      <description>I have guidelines (for myself, not for others) as to what a sympathy card should look like. I don&amp;rsquo;t judge what others create, but I do like to keep the cards I create simple and &amp;ldquo;toned down&amp;rdquo;. I needed a card for friends who recently suffered a loss and managed to create this card using some extras that were in my dish.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Old Olive
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Blue Ink*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</guid>
      <description>I had my first session at physical therapy yesterday and while things are better than they had been, I still feel like there is a very long way to go before this injury is a thing of the past. I will be working on stretches and trying to use my right hand/arm/wrist as normally as possible. There is still some swelling and the joint is extremely stiff. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a little discouraged as I write this because I just want this whole thing to be a memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Metallic Watercolours*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-18-metallic-watercolours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-18-metallic-watercolours/</guid>
      <description>I got these Kuretake watercolours for Christmas and have been too intimidated to play with them. I am not an artist. I am not artistic. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to colour. But I do know how to scribble on paper LOL
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; black watercolour paper
*Dies: MFT Celebrate
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners
*Etc: Kuretake Gem Colors Watercolours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; and this week it&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge. For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*More Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been doing a lot of crafting as my wrist has been sore again but I hope to sit in my craft room for a while today&amp;hellip; and maybe some mojo will flow.
Just a quick post from me today with more of those lovely Crafty Meraki tulips. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAACards #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a quick clean and simple card to share with you today with the new challenge at AAACards. You have two weeks to play along with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a guest designer for an upcoming challenge.
I had another idea in my head for this card but I can&amp;rsquo;t hold a pen well enough to actually colour at the moment, so I had to scrap that idea and come up with something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</guid>
      <description>Challenge #220 at Addicted to CAS is all about flowers&amp;hellip;. we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see your beautiful flower creations!
You get a bonus card from me today&amp;hellip;. I created my alcohol ink background and fit two flower dies on it &amp;hellip; and since they are so similar I decided to share them both in one post
I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your cards HERE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Special Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday the 13th crafty friends! If you&amp;rsquo;ve been here for a while, you know that my hubby and I celebrate Friday the 13th as we met (at a bar in the late 80s) on a Friday the 13th and got engaged on a Friday the 13th (our oldest son was born on the anniversary of the day Bruce proposed but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a Friday). We&amp;rsquo;ve been married 31 years (or it will be on June 1) so we figure it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty good day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Smiles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</guid>
      <description>You can see that this card looks a little similar to the one yesterday&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s another of the distress ink blending panels I did. In this one I feel like the Villainous Potion is a little too dark&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: MFT All Smiles
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Ink in Villainous Potion, Peacock Feathers, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Memories*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 09:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</guid>
      <description>Hello crafty friends. I have been crafting a little bit as I find it is good therapy. both mentally and physically. I am also working here and there without my splint on (which I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to do) and while I&amp;rsquo;m not typing as fast as I normally would, it&amp;rsquo;s not the one handed hunt and peck I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing in the last month. With things working a little more in my favour, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to blog more often again &amp;hellip; I still have cards to share that I created before my fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</guid>
      <description>Now that I have a little more mobility (and I do mean a little) with my right hand, I decided to try making a card on yesterday afternoon. Fine motor skills are still a bit of a struggle and I had to take a break part way through, but I managed to get a card done in time for the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches challenge for this week. It&amp;rsquo;s a sketch challenge this week&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations following the sketch below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! I hope that wherever you are right now that the sun is shining&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that Mother Nature got the memo that it&amp;rsquo;s now May and hopefully the spring snow will be done for the year. It&amp;rsquo;s currently pretty lovely, but here in Calgary it can change without much notice!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; for challenge #464 we want to see your clean and simple creations using a tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #403*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-03-casology-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-03-casology-403/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends&amp;hellip; I saw my surgeon yesterday and as expected, the plaster splint was removed and I now have a removable brace. I can wear the brace when I&amp;rsquo;m up and about or if the arm/wrist is fatigued. I have some stretches thatI&amp;rsquo;ve started doing that are really tough but I am told it will all get easier&amp;hellip; I am to use my arm and wrist as tolerated for anything non-weight bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</guid>
      <description>Let me tell you how long it takes me type up a blog post using only my left hand! Most of my jobs over the years have been keyboard-centric so I am a fast typer&amp;hellip; in fact, I enjoy typing&amp;hellip; but this one handed thing is frustrating!!!
If only I had a dictation app on my laptop&amp;hellip;
Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge with the team ay Addicted to CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations April 2022*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations April challenge! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your Christmas cards using plaid or tartan!
When plaid first started being popular (again), I resisted it. I honestly wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan. But over the years it&amp;rsquo;s grown on me! There&amp;rsquo;s just something about a good old red and black buffalo check&amp;hellip;.
I had fun with some Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up plaid papers and the L&amp;rsquo;il Gnome from Simon Says Stamp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really missing my creative space now&amp;hellip; I had surgery on my right wrist yesterday and am hoping things will start to feel better again soon. I&amp;rsquo;m only sharing design team creations now as typing blog posts is very slow with only one hand.
It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday so it&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with the team ay Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;
I focussed my one layer card on the bottom of my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip;. the challenge at Time Out Challenges is spring! I love spring and how the world seems to come back to life. I chose butterflies as they will be gracing our gardens soon!
I played with some white embossed Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and the awesome Birthday Brights rainbow paper from MFT on a slimline card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</guid>
      <description>As I did have some cards created for the design teams I&amp;rsquo;m on before I broke my wrist last week, I figured I&amp;rsquo;d still blog them. Typing is slow with only one hand!v I am so sad to not be creating&amp;hellip; I was on track to have a record breaking number of cards made. I haven&amp;rsquo;t gone fore more than 3 or 4 days without making cards in many weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another clean and simple challenge with the team at AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; with the optional twist of Easter or Spring. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations with us HERE!
I did a quick and easy card thanks to this wonderful Lawn Fawn strip of flowers. I stamped them, coloured them quickly with a few spring colours of Copics, stamped my greeting and then put the flowers on the card with some foam adhesive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</guid>
      <description>The team at Addicted to CAS is playing with just one layer for challenge #218. To me, a one layer card means there is no other cardstock on the card other than the card itself. You can add a few embellishments (pearls if you need to) but there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any layers or dies (unless you do an inlaid technique). It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to do&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get depth and movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Cheers On Your Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Some more fun with those Pink Fresh Studio small butterflies and Tim Holtz inks. While I love how easy it was to get a lot of butterflies stamped and cut out at once, I wonder if I should have bought a stamp set with individual stamps and dies instead so that I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the need to overload on them all at once like I did with the flowers and now the butterflies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>Some more of those Pink Fresh Studio rainbow butterflies that I cut out &amp;hellip; I added a few matted layers and a strip of black and white stripes.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Orange Marmalade, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners; Perfect Layers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches is back with another sketch challenge to inspire you. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
I stamped up a sheet of those wonderful Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and embossed them in white this time. I used a finger dauber to add colour to this butterfly after I&amp;rsquo;d cut it out, trying to keep colours in specific areas&amp;hellip; it helped that I used similar colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Butterfly Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Some more love to Pink Fresh Studio and their products&amp;hellip; but lucky for you, I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to butterflies from flowers LOL! This is a great stamp that stamps up about a dozen butterflies all at once and the die cuts them all out at once as well. I stamped up a sheet of them with black ink and then blended some Tim Holtz inks over the top before cutting them all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You Make My Heart Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</guid>
      <description>This is the last of the cards using this stamp set&amp;hellip; at least for a few days. I will admit I did something else with a few of the dies a few days ago so there will be more coming. I hope I haven&amp;rsquo;t played with them too much in the last bit and will find that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pull the set out again!
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #462*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less is More. As you can see from the graphic below, the prompt is &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo;. As always, we hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with our challenge and share your creations with us HERE!
I struggled a bit with the challenge as I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any stamps that scream &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip; so I had to think outside the box a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Another Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not quite done with the images from that Pink Fresh Studio stamp and die set&amp;hellip; I think there&amp;rsquo;s still a few more coming up. Can you tell how much I enjoyed playing with them?
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Concord Crush
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Birthday
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; MFT Stitched Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #211*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</guid>
      <description>Happy Thursday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at Time Out Challenges is back with a new photo inspiration challenge. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you create using the photo below as inspiration.
Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to not only be chosen to play along as a Guest Designer in an upcoming challenge but to win a $15 credit to shop at our sponsor, Poppystamps!
I used a layered diamond die cut pieces that I cut in half to create some blue and green and grey mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Daisy Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>I really had a lot of fun with these floral images by Pink Fresh Studio&amp;hellip; they are quick and easy to colour which makes them perfect for me. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I could do more with them to make my cards less clean and simple &amp;hellip;. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to challenge myself on that one sometime.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</guid>
      <description>Bhavya is the host at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches for the month of April. She has chosen a great &amp;lsquo;garden&amp;rsquo; themed set of colours for us to use as her first colour challenge this month. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how others interpret these colours!
For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #402*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-casology-402/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back with the design team at CASology for our April challenge. There are a lot of wonderful cards by the design team to see, so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head to the blog to see them! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see what you create as well! Share your creations with us HERE!
When I saw the cue card for this challenge, my mind automatically went to animals&amp;hellip;. but honestly, I&amp;rsquo;ve made a lot of cards with animals on them in the last little bit and I was a little tired of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Lot More Fabulous*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; just a quick post from me today to share another card with this gorgeous floral stamp set by Pink Fresh Studio.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Seaside Spray
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Memento Tuxedo Black; Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners
*Embellishments: Nuvo Aqua Shimmer; Pink &amp;amp; Main Rainbow Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAA Cards #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-03-aaa-cards-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-03-aaa-cards-212/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at AAA Cards&amp;hellip; we are a clean and simple challenge blog with challenges every two weeks. For our current challenge, we want to see your clean and simple cards that are decorated &amp;ldquo;along the edge&amp;rdquo; with the optional twist of &amp;ldquo;your country&amp;rdquo;. Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a guest designer for an upcoming challenge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I&amp;rsquo;m back with the team at Addicted to CAS with another clean and simple challenge for you all. We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your clean and simple cards featuring animals! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a CAS Perfectionist!!! I have some animal stamps in my stash that have never seen ink (at least not by me!) so I decided to pull out one of those sets to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*May All Your Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-01-may-all-your-wishes/</guid>
      <description>This is another card that I created after stamping up these wonderful floral images by Pink Fresh Studio. After I had finished the card, I decided it needed &amp;ldquo;something&amp;rdquo; so I pulled out a black marker to create the scattered dots around the image&amp;hellip; I have stamps that do this however I chose to do it after everything was already put together.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expression Simple Strips Birthday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Beautiful Blooms Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my friend Bonnie and I went to one of our favourite local stamp stores after I was done work. I will admit I bought a few things I didn&amp;rsquo;t need&amp;hellip; but I am so happy I did! This fabulous floral set from Pink Fresh is perfect for my colouring preferences&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ll see a few cards using this set in the next several days as I stamped them up at once and spent some time colouring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More Take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a few days ago, I had made another card for the current Less is More challenge but I felt it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as &amp;ldquo;clean and simple&amp;rdquo; as I wanted&amp;hellip; I still like the card so I&amp;rsquo;m sharing it with you now. Card Info
*Images: Altenew Celebrate Toay
*Ink: Versaamark; Copics
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! gold embossing powder
*Challenges: Less Is More #461</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Tuesday, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches. As it is the fifth Tuesday of a month, our challenge is a double&amp;hellip; Jeanne has chosen a past sketch and some retired colours to play with this week! Please make sure to have these three colours as the prominent colours of your clean and simple creation (but you can add neutrals as well). You are welcome to flip or rotate the sketch as long as the essence of the sketch remains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:28:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</guid>
      <description>I am so often in awe at how fast time flies by. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that we&amp;rsquo;re at the end of March already. Here in Calgary that means that the weather is unpredictable. It can be sunny and warm one day and snowing the next. Today is cloudy and cool but there is no snow on the ground&amp;hellip; so I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy about that.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use products that I don&amp;rsquo;t tent to grab for regularly&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some ink blending playing with some alcohol inks too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scraps for a Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-27-scraps-for-a-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-27-scraps-for-a-birthday/</guid>
      <description>I reached in to the bin of extras for the card today&amp;hellip; a little strip of patterned paper, an even smaller strip of cardstock and some flowers I&amp;rsquo;d cut out for something else. I love it when these cards can come together like this.
That strip of bright green cardstock was literally in my recycling bin&amp;hellip;.. it was a long skinny strip that I trimmed off for another card and I just made it the right length for the front of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #461*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I usually work on Saturdays (my work week is Wednesday thru Saturday) but I get one Saturday off each month&amp;hellip; this is that Saturday. I love my job, I really truly do&amp;hellip; but I do look forward to my Saturdays off!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less Is More&amp;hellip; our clean and simple challenge for the next two weeks is to use the colours pink and gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Floral Swag*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</guid>
      <description>I just love these floral swag stamps and dies&amp;hellip; I stamped this one, coloured it and cut it out so that it could go over the edges of the layers I placed on the front of this card. Have I told you lately how much I LOVE my perfect layers tool to create those beautiful 1/16&amp;quot; borders???
Let me tell you about another tool I am in LOVE with lately. My friend at Calgary Laser Creations is a papercrafter at heart and she has created some acrylic tools to help you get your layers on even and straight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
