<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simon Says Stamp on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/simon-says-stamp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simon Says Stamp on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/simon-says-stamp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Build Your Stash Holiday Cardmakers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-05-build-your-stash-holiday-cardmakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-05-build-your-stash-holiday-cardmakers/</guid>
      <description>I am very excited to announce that I have joined the design team at the Build Your Stash Holiday Cardmakers blog!! This is an awesome sketch challenge blog that has a new sketch each month, encouraging you to create Christmas cards each month. I will be sharing two cards each month with the monthly sketch. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check them out and join in the fun!
This is the sketch for October&amp;hellip; I LOVE that they include measurements!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a 1 of 9 rectangles challenge at AAACards with the optional twist of gnomes&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your cards where you use only one of the 9 rectangles found if you divide a rectangular card in 9ths. Be sure to keep it clean and simple and share it with us HERE!
You KNEW I&amp;rsquo;d have to use the optional twist! I used a non-Christmas gnome stamp set but added a tiny holiday wish to it to make it a Christmas card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #230*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS that starts today. The code word is Autumn. Play along with us by sharing you clean and simple cards HERE!
I had fun doing a little ink blending on a piece of cardstock and then stamping and cutting out these fun leaves. I don&amp;rsquo;t use a lot of brown in my cards but an autumn theme and these colours called for some brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Striped Corners*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</guid>
      <description>How on earth is it the end of September already? I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling to write the word September at work and now, tomorrow, I have to write October?! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a great month here weatherwise and so far haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any snow fly (we often get the first snow in September). We actually hit 28C (82F) earlier this week which is unheard of at this time of year! I worry that winter will be a lot less kind than fall has been so far!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Quick Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 09:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</guid>
      <description>When I did a stencilled background a while back I did an entire card front size and since I only used a portion of it, I had some more to play with for another card. I pulled out the leftover piece on a day I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of ideas in my head and this is what resulted.
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
Ink: Catherine Pooler Glitz, Over Coffee, Martini</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-12-striped-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-12-striped-thanks/</guid>
      <description>This was a super quick card to throw together&amp;hellip;. that striped paper did all of the work!
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Picture Perfect Party
Dies: Simon Says Stamp Big Words</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencilled Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I am back to work this afternoon after my week of isolation thanks to Covid. I am feeling really good except a lingering tiredness but I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will get better with time. I really need to just take planned holidays from work instead of illness and injury!!
A friend asked for some thank you cards recently so I did up a few different designs for her. I really liked the look of using the last bit of ink on the blending brush to go over the white spots left behind by stencilling so I did a few like this one&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #480*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches today&amp;hellip;. remember you can rotate or flip this sketch if you want, as long as the essence of the sketch is seen in your card. Share your creations with us HERE as we love to see what everyone else comes up with!
A friend asked for a bunch of thank you cards last week so I of course made her some!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Aqua on Black*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 09:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</guid>
      <description>This card started out as an experiment&amp;hellip; I wanted to see what this aqua coloured paste would look like on black&amp;hellip; and let me tell you&amp;hellip; it looks fabulous! It looked so nice I had to make a card with it, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not my usual clean and simple style.
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: Uniko Birthday Wishes
Ink: Verasfine Clair Nocturne
Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tasteful Labels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; and that challenge is traditional Christmas. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll dig out some of your Christmas stash and play along with us!
To me, the traditional colours of Christmas are red, green and gold&amp;hellip;. and I think &amp;ldquo;sparkle&amp;rdquo; should be a Christmas colour as well LOL! I just love sparkly things, especially for Christmas cards!
Card Info
Cardstock: assorted glitter papers
Images: Simon Say Stamp Good Cheer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</guid>
      <description>Time Out Challenges is back with a great new challenge&amp;hellip; this time we want you to be inspired by being kind! Our sponsor for this challenge is CAS-ual Friday stamps.
I got these wonderful new dies from Paper Rose and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to play with them. I love how they look cut out of the gold foil cardstock!
Card Info
Cardstock: gold mirror; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: Simon Says Stamp Big Thanks Words; Stampendous Big Words Thanks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations Trees*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still some time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations June theme of TREES! This is a great challenge to help you get a few Christmas cards made throughout the year. I had promised myself to make more Christmas cards before October and while I&amp;rsquo;ve done that, it&amp;rsquo;s really only been for this challenge! Maybe I should make one day a month where I make only Christmas cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #42*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</guid>
      <description>I saw a few cards on some Facebook groups I&amp;rsquo;m on as well as on Instagram, using the current challenge from Color Hues&amp;hellip; and while I don&amp;rsquo;t often reach for yellow, I really felt like I wanted to play along with this challenge. I love black and white with a pop of colour&amp;hellip; I usually do red, but yellow sure does look happy!
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Daffodil Delight, Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #695*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</guid>
      <description>I pulled out a stencil that I purchased right before I broke my wrist. Ink blending still isn&amp;rsquo;t easy (and honestly it can hurt) but this was quick and I was able to get through it. I loved the look of the colours in the current Color Throwdown Challenge so that&amp;rsquo;s what I went with for this card.
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; silver mirror
Images: MFT Big Birthday Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations April 2022*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations April challenge! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your Christmas cards using plaid or tartan!
When plaid first started being popular (again), I resisted it. I honestly wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan. But over the years it&amp;rsquo;s grown on me! There&amp;rsquo;s just something about a good old red and black buffalo check&amp;hellip;.
I had fun with some Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up plaid papers and the L&amp;rsquo;il Gnome from Simon Says Stamp</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
