<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nuvo Paste on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/nuvo-paste/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nuvo Paste on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/nuvo-paste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #227*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS today&amp;hellip; time to show us your clean and simple creations featuring the colour pink!
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why but I struggled with this prompt&amp;hellip;. but then I gabbed out some stencils and had a little play with them. I stencilled the pink swirls first and then put a second stencil on top of the first stencil and used Glimmer Paste so that the sparkly circles only showed up on the pink swirls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #699*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</guid>
      <description>I love the inspiration photo from the current Color Throwdown challenge so I had to play along. But then I was stumped as to what I wanted to do&amp;hellip; I do much better with sketch challenges than colour challenges I think!
I pulled out a stencil I haven&amp;rsquo;t used yet and this is the result. I was going to orient my card the other way however the glitter paste made a mess in one area under the stencil so I flipped the panel and covered it with my sentiment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
