<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alcohol Inks on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/alcohol-inks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alcohol Inks on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/alcohol-inks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #229*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another Addicted to CAS challenge&amp;hellip;
Just a quick post for me before I head off to work. I usually do my blogging on Wednesday mornings before work and I lost Wednesday morning to Urgent Care (see yesterdays post) so I am feeling more than a little behind!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Yupo
*Images: Studio Katia Birthday Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Alcohol Inks in Raspberry, Glacier, Alchemy (pearl)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Blue Ink*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</guid>
      <description>I had my first session at physical therapy yesterday and while things are better than they had been, I still feel like there is a very long way to go before this injury is a thing of the past. I will be working on stretches and trying to use my right hand/arm/wrist as normally as possible. There is still some swelling and the joint is extremely stiff. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a little discouraged as I write this because I just want this whole thing to be a memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</guid>
      <description>Challenge #220 at Addicted to CAS is all about flowers&amp;hellip;. we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see your beautiful flower creations!
You get a bonus card from me today&amp;hellip;. I created my alcohol ink background and fit two flower dies on it &amp;hellip; and since they are so similar I decided to share them both in one post
I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your cards HERE!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
