<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AlteNew on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/altenew/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AlteNew on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/altenew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #490*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how you all create with the colours below!
I&amp;rsquo;ve said it before&amp;hellip; I struggled with these three colours. This was a new level of struggle for me. If I wasn&amp;rsquo;t on the design team, I probably would have passed it up. I just could not do anything that I liked with these colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Subdued Thank You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Back in early July we lost a very good friend after a short illness&amp;hellip; it was devastating to lose a friend that we loved so much. She was one of my regular customers in terms of card orders. Her husband approached me after her funeral, asking if I would please make him some thank you cards to send out to people who helped out so much during her brief illness and after her death&amp;hellip; and I said &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scrappy Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Once again I used my bin of extras to create this card&amp;hellip; the flower, leaves and stitched rectangle were all already cut and unused from other projects.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Lemon Lime Twist, Berry Burst
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms: MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Embellishments: Studio Katia Arctic Breeze Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In Color Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-14-in-color-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I just love the 2022-24 Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours&amp;hellip;. but I don&amp;rsquo;t find I use all of them much. I am really drawn to the red, green and light blue but not the two darker colours as much. So I grabbed all five for this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, Parakeet Party, Tahitian Tide, Orchid Oasis, Starry Sky
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Black &amp; White with Sparkle*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long week away from my creative space as I&amp;rsquo;ve been isolating in the main bedroom of our home because I got Covid. Honestly I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of energy some days so I didn&amp;rsquo;t miss the creative time all that much, but as I started to feel better I wished I could sit at my desk and play. I am now feeling better and out of isolation but wearing a mask when others are around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #476*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the last sketch challenge for the month of June with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; our sketch this time is a slimline card and I went for a mini-slimline as I prefer that size.
I took, a large floral stamp but only used a part of it so it would fit on my card. I even pulled out my Copics to do a little colouring (which isn&amp;rsquo;t easy as my wrist heals)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new one layer card challenge over at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; a one layer card means there are no other pieces of cardstock other than your card base. If you want to use dies, they have to be inlaid. For me, the best way to achieve a one layer card is some simple stamping.
*you may add words as well*
I had a thought in my head but had trouble getting all of the pieces together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Two Challenges*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with two challenges today&amp;hellip; Color Throwdown #696 and CAS on Friday #233. The colours of the first challenge fit the theme of &amp;ldquo;condolence&amp;rdquo; for the second challenge absolutely perfectly!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Very Vanilla, Crumb Cake, Pear Pizzazz
*Images: Altenew Flower Vine
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms, Spendid Stems; MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Etc: foam adhesive
*Challenges: Color Throwdown #696; CAS on Friday #233</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Pop of Red*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</guid>
      <description>For my card today, I searched through the archives at CAS Colours and Sketches to find a sketch I wanted to play with &amp;hellip; this was challenge #426 which was a colour and sketch challenge, but I only used the sketch.
What you can&amp;rsquo;t see in this photo is that I used a piercing cover plate die on the black banner which adds a little visual interest
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Thoughts*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-08-in-my-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back without another washi tape creation. The stamp and die with this Pink Fresh Studio set are one piece so it makes more sense to stamp it all and then cut it all&amp;hellip; the same goes with the washi tape. When I cut out the wreath for the card a few days ago, it only made sense to do it all. These were the other pieces I had so I threw them all on a panel to create a card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; for challenge #215 we have a wonderful prize available to be won thanks to our generous sponsor, STAMPlorations. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
For this challenge, we want you to be inspired by the photo in the card below. You can take anything from this inspiration photo and translate it on to your creation. I struggled with this photo&amp;hellip; until I remembered that inspiration can come from anything in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAACards #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a quick clean and simple card to share with you today with the new challenge at AAACards. You have two weeks to play along with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a guest designer for an upcoming challenge.
I had another idea in my head for this card but I can&amp;rsquo;t hold a pen well enough to actually colour at the moment, so I had to scrap that idea and come up with something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really missing my creative space now&amp;hellip; I had surgery on my right wrist yesterday and am hoping things will start to feel better again soon. I&amp;rsquo;m only sharing design team creations now as typing blog posts is very slow with only one hand.
It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday so it&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with the team ay Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;
I focussed my one layer card on the bottom of my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip;. the challenge at Time Out Challenges is spring! I love spring and how the world seems to come back to life. I chose butterflies as they will be gracing our gardens soon!
I played with some white embossed Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and the awesome Birthday Brights rainbow paper from MFT on a slimline card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #462*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less is More. As you can see from the graphic below, the prompt is &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo;. As always, we hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with our challenge and share your creations with us HERE!
I struggled a bit with the challenge as I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any stamps that scream &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip; so I had to think outside the box a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More Take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a few days ago, I had made another card for the current Less is More challenge but I felt it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as &amp;ldquo;clean and simple&amp;rdquo; as I wanted&amp;hellip; I still like the card so I&amp;rsquo;m sharing it with you now. Card Info
*Images: Altenew Celebrate Toay
*Ink: Versaamark; Copics
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! gold embossing powder
*Challenges: Less Is More #461</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #461*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I usually work on Saturdays (my work week is Wednesday thru Saturday) but I get one Saturday off each month&amp;hellip; this is that Saturday. I love my job, I really truly do&amp;hellip; but I do look forward to my Saturdays off!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less Is More&amp;hellip; our clean and simple challenge for the next two weeks is to use the colours pink and gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Floral Swag*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</guid>
      <description>I just love these floral swag stamps and dies&amp;hellip; I stamped this one, coloured it and cut it out so that it could go over the edges of the layers I placed on the front of this card. Have I told you lately how much I LOVE my perfect layers tool to create those beautiful 1/16&amp;quot; borders???
Let me tell you about another tool I am in LOVE with lately. My friend at Calgary Laser Creations is a papercrafter at heart and she has created some acrylic tools to help you get your layers on even and straight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
