<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Colorful Life Designs on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/a-colorful-life-designs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A Colorful Life Designs on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 09:47:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/a-colorful-life-designs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 09:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</guid>
      <description>We have a colour challenge for you at AAACards this week&amp;hellip; with the optional twist of spots and dots. Use the graphic below to get your colour inspiration for your clean and simple cards.
The colours were a bit tough for me because while they look fine on this graphic, I had trouble getting them together on a card. I tried three different things before this one stuck&amp;hellip;
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #227*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS today&amp;hellip; time to show us your clean and simple creations featuring the colour pink!
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why but I struggled with this prompt&amp;hellip;. but then I gabbed out some stencils and had a little play with them. I stencilled the pink swirls first and then put a second stencil on top of the first stencil and used Glimmer Paste so that the sparkly circles only showed up on the pink swirls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Masked Word*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-05-masked-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-05-masked-word/</guid>
      <description>I tried something a little different (at least for me) with this card&amp;hellip; nothing earth shattering, but I masked off the word celebrate before I ink blended over a stencil. Before I removed my mask, I also blended a little more of the same colours of ink over the piece after removing the stencil to soften the look of the colours a little and to really make my word pop. I like how it all looks kind of soft and dreamy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Softened the Look*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</guid>
      <description>I will admit that I love stencils&amp;hellip; and I have a few dozen&amp;hellip; but I hardly use them because I feel intimidated by them. I think it&amp;rsquo;s because I prefer the clean and simple style for my creations and stencils tend to be pretty busy. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to pull them out to play with a little more often&amp;hellip; For this card I used the ink through the stencil and then the same colours of inks over top without the stencil to soften the look a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Aqua on Black*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 09:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</guid>
      <description>This card started out as an experiment&amp;hellip; I wanted to see what this aqua coloured paste would look like on black&amp;hellip; and let me tell you&amp;hellip; it looks fabulous! It looked so nice I had to make a card with it, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not my usual clean and simple style.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Uniko Birthday Wishes
*Ink: Verasfine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tasteful Labels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #699*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</guid>
      <description>I love the inspiration photo from the current Color Throwdown challenge so I had to play along. But then I was stumped as to what I wanted to do&amp;hellip; I do much better with sketch challenges than colour challenges I think!
I pulled out a stencil I haven&amp;rsquo;t used yet and this is the result. I was going to orient my card the other way however the glitter paste made a mess in one area under the stencil so I flipped the panel and covered it with my sentiment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #695*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-05-color-throwdown-695/</guid>
      <description>I pulled out a stencil that I purchased right before I broke my wrist. Ink blending still isn&amp;rsquo;t easy (and honestly it can hurt) but this was quick and I was able to get through it. I loved the look of the colours in the current Color Throwdown Challenge so that&amp;rsquo;s what I went with for this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; silver mirror
*Images: MFT Big Birthday Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
