<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Studio Katia on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/studio-katia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Studio Katia on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/studio-katia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Gold and Black Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/10/posts/2022-10-03-gold-and-black-wishes/</guid>
      <description>I am loving my new Glimmer Foil Machine and I just know I&amp;rsquo;m going to use it a lot during my Christmas card making season (which I think will begin very shortly!). The plate I used for this card is supposed to go across the card to create &amp;ldquo;lights&amp;rdquo; but I liked how it gave a neat background to play with going vertically instead.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Free Form Frame*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</guid>
      <description>Another card from the bin of extras&amp;hellip;. I used a die as a guide to draw a rectangle on my card front with pencil&amp;hellip; and then went over it a few times with a thin black marker, not even trying to make straight lines. Once it had set for a bit I erased the pencil lines and then added in the hash marks and dots. I stamped my sentiment and added to my ink blended butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #229*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another Addicted to CAS challenge&amp;hellip;
Just a quick post for me before I head off to work. I usually do my blogging on Wednesday mornings before work and I lost Wednesday morning to Urgent Care (see yesterdays post) so I am feeling more than a little behind!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Yupo
*Images: Studio Katia Birthday Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Alcohol Inks in Raspberry, Glacier, Alchemy (pearl)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Peekaboo Flowers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-16-peekaboo-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 08:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-16-peekaboo-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Have today off after picking up my coworkers shift on Tuesday. Feels strange. I do go back for a half day tomorrow. I am off in a few minutes for a massage and to head to one of my favourite creative stores to pick up a few things I ordered. A few other things might also make it in to my basket! I hope to come home and create as I&amp;rsquo;m way behind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*TIme Out Challenges #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a word prompt challenge at Time Out Challenges. We have a $25 gift card to Lawn Fawn up for grabs for one lucky player!!
This is such a beautiful quote by Maya Angelou&amp;hellip;. and it&amp;rsquo;s something I try to do when I&amp;rsquo;m at work. I work at the front desk of a chiropractic clinic and we often see people who are in a lot of pain. I try had to be a bright spot in their day, maybe help them feel a little better for a few minutes while they have to interact with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #485*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-30-cas-colours-sketches-485/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the 5th Tuesday of the month so we have a double challenge for you at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! We&amp;rsquo;ve taken some retired Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! colours and an old sketch and want to see you combine the two to create something beautiful!
I had to move the sentiment on my card as it just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right floating up there in the left corner like in the sketch. I even made a square card, which I don&amp;rsquo;t do very often!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scrappy Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Once again I used my bin of extras to create this card&amp;hellip; the flower, leaves and stitched rectangle were all already cut and unused from other projects.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Lemon Lime Twist, Berry Burst
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms: MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Embellishments: Studio Katia Arctic Breeze Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Black &amp; White with Sparkle*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-08-black-white-with-sparkle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long week away from my creative space as I&amp;rsquo;ve been isolating in the main bedroom of our home because I got Covid. Honestly I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of energy some days so I didn&amp;rsquo;t miss the creative time all that much, but as I started to feel better I wished I could sit at my desk and play. I am now feeling better and out of isolation but wearing a mask when others are around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the first clean and simple challenge of August with AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; which means you should use a few small images on your card&amp;hellip; the optional twist is (lady)bugs. The design team has some wonderful inspiration on the blog. We hope to see you playing along with us!
I love ladybugs and they are so easy to colour for someone like me who doesn&amp;rsquo;t find colouring zen-inducing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #406*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-02-casology-406/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-02-casology-406/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology and the cue for this month is SAND. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll check out what the rest of the design team has created and maybe even share a creation of your own!! You&amp;rsquo;ll find the CASology blog HERE
Despite loving the beach, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of a things that are beach themed&amp;hellip; so I had to think about how to create something with this cue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Every two weeks we have a challenge of a different type complete with prizes for our winners! For this week, Varada Sharma is offering us two $15 vouchers to give to our winners!! To win, simply share your creations inspired by the photo below! You can see all of the information and share them HERE.
I was inspired by the sunset and the silhouette of the grasses on the shore for my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Softened the Look*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-25-softened-the-look/</guid>
      <description>I will admit that I love stencils&amp;hellip; and I have a few dozen&amp;hellip; but I hardly use them because I feel intimidated by them. I think it&amp;rsquo;s because I prefer the clean and simple style for my creations and stencils tend to be pretty busy. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to pull them out to play with a little more often&amp;hellip; For this card I used the ink through the stencil and then the same colours of inks over top without the stencil to soften the look a little bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #479*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! Two of these colours are not my favourites&amp;hellip; one of them I honestly only have two sheets of thanks to my friend Bonnie giving them to me! But I will admit&amp;hellip; this is a great colour combination and I am pretty happy with how my card turned out!
As I don&amp;rsquo;t have many Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! ink pads any more and I struggle with trying to find suitable matches with the inks I do have, most of my colour challenges will have cardstock as the colours instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #699*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</guid>
      <description>I love the inspiration photo from the current Color Throwdown challenge so I had to play along. But then I was stumped as to what I wanted to do&amp;hellip; I do much better with sketch challenges than colour challenges I think!
I pulled out a stencil I haven&amp;rsquo;t used yet and this is the result. I was going to orient my card the other way however the glitter paste made a mess in one area under the stencil so I flipped the panel and covered it with my sentiment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*White Daisies*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-01-white-daisies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-01-white-daisies/</guid>
      <description>How on earth is it July already?!?!?! I wish the warm months could slow down just a little bit&amp;hellip;. I love the extra sunlight and warmth (especially compared to the cold and dark of winter).
I want you to click on this card so you can zoom in a little bit because no matter how hard I tried, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get my photo to look good at a small size. I LOVE how this card turned out and I just wish it looked better in a photograph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We have a sketch for you this week with the added optional twist of flowers. Of course I did both (because I love florals!) Share your card with us HERE for a chance to be chosen as a guest designer in an upcoming challenge!
I always struggle with the placement of things like the sketch shows so I wanted to do something different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Belated Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-01-belated-birthday/</guid>
      <description>On this day, 31 years ago, my hubby and I stood in front of family and friends and said &amp;ldquo;I do&amp;rdquo;. I know we&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot, seen a lot, made it through a lot&amp;hellip; but I have no idea where 31 years have gone! Happy Anniversary, Babe!
In other news, I saw my surgeon on Monday and he says my wrist is healing well. He says my progress is a little ahead of what he&amp;rsquo;d expect at this point and while I think he said that because I said I was frustrated with how slow it all is, I will try to remember that I am improving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenged with Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; for the next two weeks, we want to see you sharing your cards featuring stripes! I am the host for this challenge, which means this theme was my idea! Please share your clean and simple cards with strips with us HERE!
I had a bit of trouble deciding on what I wanted to do for my card for this challenge&amp;hellip; I have a lot of options when it comes to stripes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Washi Tape Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-26-washi-tape-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-26-washi-tape-background/</guid>
      <description>I had so much fun playing with ink on washi tape, that I decided to play again. This is a great technique. You just ink up the sticky side of the washi tape and put it down on your cardstock and then pull it up again. It really gives some fun texture to your card. This is great for me as I have some washi tapes that I will probably never use on cards so I can do something creative with it (instead of just using it as repositionable adhesive)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Awesome Daisy Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-25-awesome-daisy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-25-awesome-daisy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe we&amp;rsquo;re looking at the end of May already&amp;hellip; next week we&amp;rsquo;ll be in to June! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t help that the weather hasn&amp;rsquo;t been consistently warm here in Calgary so I haven&amp;rsquo;t switched the furnace from heat to cool. It&amp;rsquo;s sad, really.
I really love the look of this pretty blue with the white flowers on top&amp;hellip; I added a little yellow to make it all pop!
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*April 2022 Sheetload*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-23-april-2022-sheetload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-23-april-2022-sheetload/</guid>
      <description>Before I broke my wrist, I played along with the April 2022 Sheetload of Cards&amp;hellip; The way it worked out trying to make one card, it made more sense to make two since what I cut off was exactly what I needed for the second piece. These two cards are the same, but different
I really do love the size of a mini slimline!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Cherry Cobbler, Lucky Limeade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! I hope that wherever you are right now that the sun is shining&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that Mother Nature got the memo that it&amp;rsquo;s now May and hopefully the spring snow will be done for the year. It&amp;rsquo;s currently pretty lovely, but here in Calgary it can change without much notice!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; for challenge #464 we want to see your clean and simple creations using a tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</guid>
      <description>As I did have some cards created for the design teams I&amp;rsquo;m on before I broke my wrist last week, I figured I&amp;rsquo;d still blog them. Typing is slow with only one hand!v I am so sad to not be creating&amp;hellip; I was on track to have a record breaking number of cards made. I haven&amp;rsquo;t gone fore more than 3 or 4 days without making cards in many weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches is back with another sketch challenge to inspire you. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
I stamped up a sheet of those wonderful Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and embossed them in white this time. I used a finger dauber to add colour to this butterfly after I&amp;rsquo;d cut it out, trying to keep colours in specific areas&amp;hellip; it helped that I used similar colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Butterfly Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Some more love to Pink Fresh Studio and their products&amp;hellip; but lucky for you, I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to butterflies from flowers LOL! This is a great stamp that stamps up about a dozen butterflies all at once and the die cuts them all out at once as well. I stamped up a sheet of them with black ink and then blended some Tim Holtz inks over the top before cutting them all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Floral Swag*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/03/posts/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/03/posts/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</guid>
      <description>I just love these floral swag stamps and dies&amp;hellip; I stamped this one, coloured it and cut it out so that it could go over the edges of the layers I placed on the front of this card. Have I told you lately how much I LOVE my perfect layers tool to create those beautiful 1/16&amp;quot; borders???
Let me tell you about another tool I am in LOVE with lately. My friend at Calgary Laser Creations is a papercrafter at heart and she has created some acrylic tools to help you get your layers on even and straight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
