<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scrapbook.com on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/scrapbook.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scrapbook.com on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/scrapbook.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</guid>
      <description>October 1st is World Cardmaking Day and here at Less is More, we are celebrating a little early with a friendship themed challenge! We think making a card for a friend is a great way to celebrate World Cardmaking Day! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of very good friends who are always there for me&amp;hellip; to listen, to provide support, to make me laugh, to distract me, to do social things with&amp;hellip; so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make a card that I could give to one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #549*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-18-freshly-made-sketches-549/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time before work yesterday to play along with the current challenge at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to use a piece I did with my Glimmer Hot Foil machine&amp;hellip;. used the solid foiling plate to use the left over foil from another project.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Hammermill Premium Color Copy; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; Scrapbook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Addicted to CAS! We are playing with the code word GRID for this challenge. I will admit that I struggled with this challenge. I had no idea how to interpret this word. But then I remembered I had some patterned papers that had a grid-look to them&amp;hellip; and I went with the one that was more delicate looking to create my card for today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenged with Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; for the next two weeks, we want to see you sharing your cards featuring stripes! I am the host for this challenge, which means this theme was my idea! Please share your clean and simple cards with strips with us HERE!
I had a bit of trouble deciding on what I wanted to do for my card for this challenge&amp;hellip; I have a lot of options when it comes to stripes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
