<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GinaK on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/ginak/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GinaK on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 09:05:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/ginak/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*A Quick Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 09:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-28-a-quick-thanks/</guid>
      <description>When I did a stencilled background a while back I did an entire card front size and since I only used a portion of it, I had some more to play with for another card. I pulled out the leftover piece on a day I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of ideas in my head and this is what resulted.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Ink: Catherine Pooler Glitz, Over Coffee, Martini</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Fall Failure*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/09/posts/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</guid>
      <description>I was trying to do a more fall looking card with this but my colours (especially the yellow) were too bright. Of course I did a full 6X6 panel so I will be sharing another card with my too bright for fall flowers in the coming days.
I did a get well card because these colours looked so happy.
Card Info
*Images: MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Glitz, Martini, Over Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card was so super easy to put together&amp;hellip; and I love it! The hardest part was figuring out where the flowers should go!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Images: Gina K Where Flowers Bloom
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms; MFT Stitched Circles; Waffle Flower Additional Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling in the craft room in the last few days&amp;hellip; I sit there, wanting to create but nothing comes. Thankfully I have some cards already made to be able to share with you&amp;hellip; and it just so happens to fall in to the color challenge at Color Hues!
For the card today, I used the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral stamp, die and stencils&amp;hellip; but instead of using all of the layers of the stencil, I only used two to create the bit of blue on the flowers and the bit of green on the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new one layer card challenge over at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; a one layer card means there are no other pieces of cardstock other than your card base. If you want to use dies, they have to be inlaid. For me, the best way to achieve a one layer card is some simple stamping.
*you may add words as well*
I had a thought in my head but had trouble getting all of the pieces together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sunny Thoughts*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-27-sunny-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/05/posts/2022-05-27-sunny-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday crafty friends&amp;hellip; I thought a bright and happy card might help my mood. It&amp;rsquo;s been 6 weeks since the fall that broke my wrist and I am feeling frustrated at how much pain and limited mobility I still have. I see my surgeon on Monday and will talk about trying to get back to work which will be good&amp;hellip; but even then I think going back to work will be a few hours a few days a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</guid>
      <description>Bhavya is the host at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches for the month of April. She has chosen a great &amp;lsquo;garden&amp;rsquo; themed set of colours for us to use as her first colour challenge this month. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how others interpret these colours!
For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
