<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Holtz Distress Inks on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/tim-holtz-distress-inks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tim Holtz Distress Inks on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:10:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/tim-holtz-distress-inks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Free Form Frame*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-29-free-form-frame/</guid>
      <description>Another card from the bin of extras&amp;hellip;. I used a die as a guide to draw a rectangle on my card front with pencil&amp;hellip; and then went over it a few times with a thin black marker, not even trying to make straight lines. Once it had set for a bit I erased the pencil lines and then added in the hash marks and dots. I stamped my sentiment and added to my ink blended butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 09:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</guid>
      <description>We have a colour challenge for you at AAACards this week&amp;hellip; with the optional twist of spots and dots. Use the graphic below to get your colour inspiration for your clean and simple cards.
The colours were a bit tough for me because while they look fine on this graphic, I had trouble getting them together on a card. I tried three different things before this one stuck&amp;hellip;
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #484*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another sketch challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. You can rotate the sketch if you like, but we need to be able to see the essence of the sketch in your creation. And those rectangles? You can use any shape you want!
My card was going to be one layer&amp;hellip; until I messed up the place of my splats so I trimmed down a front panel and adhered it to a new card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #227*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS today&amp;hellip; time to show us your clean and simple creations featuring the colour pink!
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why but I struggled with this prompt&amp;hellip;. but then I gabbed out some stencils and had a little play with them. I stencilled the pink swirls first and then put a second stencil on top of the first stencil and used Glimmer Paste so that the sparkly circles only showed up on the pink swirls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Masked Word*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</guid>
      <description>I tried something a little different (at least for me) with this card&amp;hellip; nothing earth shattering, but I masked off the word celebrate before I ink blended over a stencil. Before I removed my mask, I also blended a little more of the same colours of ink over the piece after removing the stencil to soften the look of the colours a little and to really make my word pop. I like how it all looks kind of soft and dreamy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Petals*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-29-birthday-petals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-29-birthday-petals/</guid>
      <description>I used two leaf dies and some distress ink to create a rainbow flower&amp;hellip;
Card Info
Ink: Tim Holtz Picked Raspberry, Carved Pumpkin, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron, Peacock Feathers, Salty Ocean, Wilted Violet
Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms
Etc: computer generated sentiment printed on the laser printer and foiled</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Every two weeks we have a challenge of a different type complete with prizes for our winners! For this week, Varada Sharma is offering us two $15 vouchers to give to our winners!! To win, simply share your creations inspired by the photo below! You can see all of the information and share them HERE.
I was inspired by the sunset and the silhouette of the grasses on the shore for my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-24-aaacards-220/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We want to see your cards with the design only along the edge (you can choose which edge) with the optional twist of &amp;ldquo;in the sea&amp;rdquo;.
This was tough for me because I had two design team obligations that were a similar theme back to back! And the themes aren&amp;rsquo;t something I find easy to do in the first place!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*When It Rains...*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</guid>
      <description>My blog title has nothing to do with my card today&amp;hellip; but it has to do with what&amp;rsquo;s going on in my world. As you know, I broke my right wrist in April. While I am getting mobility and strength back in that wrist, it would appear that the muscles around my right shoulder don&amp;rsquo;t like that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the arm in awkward ways and they have now seized up making it near impossible to sit upright at my desk, let alone create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #699*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-04-color-throwdown-699/</guid>
      <description>I love the inspiration photo from the current Color Throwdown challenge so I had to play along. But then I was stumped as to what I wanted to do&amp;hellip; I do much better with sketch challenges than colour challenges I think!
I pulled out a stencil I haven&amp;rsquo;t used yet and this is the result. I was going to orient my card the other way however the glitter paste made a mess in one area under the stencil so I flipped the panel and covered it with my sentiment!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Stencil Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-29-stencil-background/</guid>
      <description>I had fun with some light stencilling for my card today. I wanted some pretty colour without it being overwhelming. I love layering stencils since it&amp;rsquo;s so easy to do one colour at a time&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s achievable with a regular stencil but you have to be careful with the masking! I actually used two different stencils for this card but only used a small portion of each, moving it around to fill my background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 3*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-23-color-hues-43-take-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-23-color-hues-43-take-3/</guid>
      <description>When you find a colour combination you just love, sometimes you have to go with it. That&amp;rsquo;s me with the colours blue and green&amp;hellip; specifically Tim Holtz Twisted Citron and Salty Ocean. Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Parakeet Party and Tahitian Tide are right up there for me too!
And of course, I get to play along one more time with the challenge at Color Hues
I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve *ever* entered one challenge more than one time&amp;hellip; and this is my third entry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</guid>
      <description>Is it good or bad that this Pink Fresh Studio stamp is one stamp with several images that you stamp, stencil and cut all at once? It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s bad because you get stuck with several cards that look similar.
The good news is that this is a LOVELY set and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create with it! And I get to play along with Color Hues again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-19-color-hues-43/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling in the craft room in the last few days&amp;hellip; I sit there, wanting to create but nothing comes. Thankfully I have some cards already made to be able to share with you&amp;hellip; and it just so happens to fall in to the color challenge at Color Hues!
For the card today, I used the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral stamp, die and stencils&amp;hellip; but instead of using all of the layers of the stencil, I only used two to create the bit of blue on the flowers and the bit of green on the leaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
Cardstock: gold mirror
Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for popping by today! I&amp;rsquo;m sharing with you, my card for the current clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards. We want you to use only 1 of the 9 rectangles on the front of your A2 card when you divide it up evenly (or 1/9 of any card size you like to use) with the optional twist of Butterflies.
The 1/9th is the hard part for this card&amp;hellip; I decided to use a little ink blending to create the rectangle to help me envision it&amp;hellip; to create a little dimension, I used glue along the body of the butterfly and foam adhesive on the wings to make them pop up a bit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #404*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pop by the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done with the cue of RIDE. We love to see your clean and simple creations too&amp;hellip; share them HERE!
I almost skipped this challenge but then remembered this cute set from My Favorite Things and decided I&amp;rsquo;d give it a go. It&amp;rsquo;s not really my &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I pushed myself a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Craft Crew #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-paper-craft-crew-473/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling Pinterest yesterday and found a card sketch I liked&amp;hellip; clicked the link and found a new to me challenge page called Paper Craft Crew. I had a little mojo this morning so I decided to play with their sketch.
I dipped in to my bin of extra die cuts and put together this card&amp;hellip;
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Balmy Balmy Blue
Images: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Washi Tape Background*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-26-washi-tape-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-26-washi-tape-background/</guid>
      <description>I had so much fun playing with ink on washi tape, that I decided to play again. This is a great technique. You just ink up the sticky side of the washi tape and put it down on your cardstock and then pull it up again. It really gives some fun texture to your card. This is great for me as I have some washi tapes that I will probably never use on cards so I can do something creative with it (instead of just using it as repositionable adhesive)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Washi Tape*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</guid>
      <description>Happy Sunday all&amp;hellip; in true Calgary fashion, our first long weekend of &amp;ldquo;summer&amp;rdquo; has delivered us a mixed bag of weather. Friday it was really windy and wet and we had a little snow falling from the sky. Saturday was cool and mostly cloudy. So far this morning the sun is shining and it&amp;rsquo;s warming up a little. This is what you get with an elevation of 1045 m above sea level (that&amp;rsquo;s 3428 ft).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*More Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-16-more-tulips/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been doing a lot of crafting as my wrist has been sore again but I hope to sit in my craft room for a while today&amp;hellip; and maybe some mojo will flow.
Just a quick post from me today with more of those lovely Crafty Meraki tulips. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Special Tulips*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-13-special-tulips/</guid>
      <description>Happy Friday the 13th crafty friends! If you&amp;rsquo;ve been here for a while, you know that my hubby and I celebrate Friday the 13th as we met (at a bar in the late 80s) on a Friday the 13th and got engaged on a Friday the 13th (our oldest son was born on the anniversary of the day Bruce proposed but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a Friday). We&amp;rsquo;ve been married 31 years (or it will be on June 1) so we figure it&amp;rsquo;s a pretty good day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Smiles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</guid>
      <description>You can see that this card looks a little similar to the one yesterday&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s another of the distress ink blending panels I did. In this one I feel like the Villainous Potion is a little too dark&amp;hellip;
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: MFT All Smiles
Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Ink in Villainous Potion, Peacock Feathers, Twisted Citron
Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Memories*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 09:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</guid>
      <description>Hello crafty friends. I have been crafting a little bit as I find it is good therapy. both mentally and physically. I am also working here and there without my splint on (which I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to do) and while I&amp;rsquo;m not typing as fast as I normally would, it&amp;rsquo;s not the one handed hunt and peck I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing in the last month. With things working a little more in my favour, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to blog more often again &amp;hellip; I still have cards to share that I created before my fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m here with the latest challenge from Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; we want you to share your cards inspired by being on vacation! We have a prize from Lawn Fawn up for grabs!! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE!
My favourite vacations have been to the sun and water&amp;hellip; so I created a sunset across the water for you&amp;hellip;
Be sure to share your vacation inspired creations with us here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really missing my creative space now&amp;hellip; I had surgery on my right wrist yesterday and am hoping things will start to feel better again soon. I&amp;rsquo;m only sharing design team creations now as typing blog posts is very slow with only one hand.
It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday so it&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with the team ay Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;
I focussed my one layer card on the bottom of my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-16-addicted-to-cas-218/</guid>
      <description>The team at Addicted to CAS is playing with just one layer for challenge #218. To me, a one layer card means there is no other cardstock on the card other than the card itself. You can add a few embellishments (pearls if you need to) but there shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be any layers or dies (unless you do an inlaid technique). It&amp;rsquo;s a difficult thing to do&amp;hellip; and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get depth and movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Unicorn Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-15-unicorn-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-15-unicorn-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>I knew when I bought this Whittle Unicorn die that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t all that &amp;ldquo;whittle&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; but I sure wish it was. This is just a little too large for me, but as you can see, I bought it anyway!
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! shimmer white, Basic Black; Lawn Fawn holographic
Images: Pink Fresh Studio Happy Birthday Sentiments
Ink: Versamark; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Mustard Seed, Spiced Marmalade, Twisted Citron, Salty Ocean</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Cheers On Your Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-14-cheers-on-your-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Some more fun with those Pink Fresh Studio small butterflies and Tim Holtz inks. While I love how easy it was to get a lot of butterflies stamped and cut out at once, I wonder if I should have bought a stamp set with individual stamps and dies instead so that I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel the need to overload on them all at once like I did with the flowers and now the butterflies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>Some more of those Pink Fresh Studio rainbow butterflies that I cut out &amp;hellip; I added a few matted layers and a strip of black and white stripes.
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies, Happy Birthday Sentiments
Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Orange Marmalade, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron
Tools: Fricken Square Corners; Perfect Layers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches is back with another sketch challenge to inspire you. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
I stamped up a sheet of those wonderful Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and embossed them in white this time. I used a finger dauber to add colour to this butterfly after I&amp;rsquo;d cut it out, trying to keep colours in specific areas&amp;hellip; it helped that I used similar colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Butterfly Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-11-butterfly-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>Some more love to Pink Fresh Studio and their products&amp;hellip; but lucky for you, I&amp;rsquo;ve switched to butterflies from flowers LOL! This is a great stamp that stamps up about a dozen butterflies all at once and the die cuts them all out at once as well. I stamped up a sheet of them with black ink and then blended some Tim Holtz inks over the top before cutting them all out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I&amp;rsquo;m back with the team at Addicted to CAS with another clean and simple challenge for you all. We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your clean and simple cards featuring animals! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a CAS Perfectionist!!! I have some animal stamps in my stash that have never seen ink (at least not by me!) so I decided to pull out one of those sets to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:28:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</guid>
      <description>I am so often in awe at how fast time flies by. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that we&amp;rsquo;re at the end of March already. Here in Calgary that means that the weather is unpredictable. It can be sunny and warm one day and snowing the next. Today is cloudy and cool but there is no snow on the ground&amp;hellip; so I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy about that.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use products that I don&amp;rsquo;t tent to grab for regularly&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some ink blending playing with some alcohol inks too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
