<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CC&amp;S on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/ccs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CC&amp;S on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/ccs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #490*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-cas-colours-sketches-490/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how you all create with the colours below!
I&amp;rsquo;ve said it before&amp;hellip; I struggled with these three colours. This was a new level of struggle for me. If I wasn&amp;rsquo;t on the design team, I probably would have passed it up. I just could not do anything that I liked with these colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #489*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the sketch this week at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! My card went together pretty quickly once I decided on what elements I wanted to use. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
My card uses a few pieces from my bin of extras that I kept overlooking. I had used just two of the layering stencils and these two pieces had very little colour on them&amp;hellip; so I grabbed my Copics and gave them a bit more colour before adding them to my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #488*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-20-cas-colours-sketches-488/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; we have some wonderfully fall colours to challenge you with this week. I will admit I was even thinking about some Christmas card ideas when I was first looking at these colours.
I decided to create a fall wreath and added a little hot foiling to finish it off.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Merry Merlot, Calypso Coral, Mossy Meadow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #487*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. This is a great sketch to showcase a little bit of patterned paper or an embossed panel&amp;hellip; or keep it just a solid colour. There are so many options!
I saw this sketch and immediately wanted to use this beautiful Stampin&#39; Up! paper from last year. It took a while for me to decide what to do with the other element on the card but I landed on the gnome and I like how it turned out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #486*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-cas-colours-sketches-486/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new host this month at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; Patricia has chosen these fun colours to play with this week! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
As you will often see me say, I struggled with these colours. I don&amp;rsquo;t often put yellow on a card and certainly not with these other colours! I wanted to play with ink for this challenge so I had to pull some similar colours from my stash and I added the Mango Melody in a layer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #484*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-23-cas-colours-sketches-484/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another sketch challenge at CAS Colours and Sketches. You can rotate the sketch if you like, but we need to be able to see the essence of the sketch in your creation. And those rectangles? You can use any shape you want!
My card was going to be one layer&amp;hellip; until I messed up the place of my splats so I trimmed down a front panel and adhered it to a new card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #483*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-16-cas-colours-sketches-483/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-16-cas-colours-sketches-483/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches that starts today&amp;hellip;. these colours are PERFECT to use on a black background if you like that sort of popping neon appearance. We always love to see what others do with our sketches and colour combinations so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your card with us!
I absolutely LOVE how some colours just POP off of a black background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #481*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-02-cas-colours-sketches-481/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; and for the month of August, I am the host! We are staring off this month with a colour challenge. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what everyone creates using these great colours! Be sure to check out the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches blog to see what the rest of the design team created!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #480*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-26-cas-colours-sketches-480/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches today&amp;hellip;. remember you can rotate or flip this sketch if you want, as long as the essence of the sketch is seen in your card. Share your creations with us HERE as we love to see what everyone else comes up with!
A friend asked for a bunch of thank you cards last week so I of course made her some!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #479*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-19-cas-colours-sketches-479/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! Two of these colours are not my favourites&amp;hellip; one of them I honestly only have two sheets of thanks to my friend Bonnie giving them to me! But I will admit&amp;hellip; this is a great colour combination and I am pretty happy with how my card turned out!
As I don&amp;rsquo;t have many Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! ink pads any more and I struggle with trying to find suitable matches with the inks I do have, most of my colour challenges will have cardstock as the colours instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #478*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday my friends&amp;hellip; and a BIG happy birthday to my big sister! It&amp;rsquo;s a milestone birthday for her today and I&amp;rsquo;m sad to not be celebrating it with her. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. Patricia came up with this fun sketch for us all to try this week! I really look forward to seeing what *you* create!
I tried a few different things with this sketch and tossed them all in the bin&amp;hellip; until I decided to turn the sketch and then I came up with something I liked on my first try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #476*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the last sketch challenge for the month of June with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; our sketch this time is a slimline card and I went for a mini-slimline as I prefer that size.
I took, a large floral stamp but only used a part of it so it would fit on my card. I even pulled out my Copics to do a little colouring (which isn&amp;rsquo;t easy as my wrist heals)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</guid>
      <description>I am so happy that Samantha chose some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for our challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches this week. I just love the new colours and especially these three! I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with this colour combination this week!
These colours are just so happy! They make me think of popsicles, and beach balls, and shovels and pails&amp;hellip; all those wonderfully fun things in the summer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-14-cas-colours-sketches-474/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us this week by posting your creation HERE!
I changed the sketch just a little bit, making the hexagon a little smaller. I just purchased these dies from Scrapbook.com and am so happy I did! I love the little hint of shiny gold on this card.
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies; Studio Katia Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</guid>
      <description>Samantha is the host for the month of June at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches and she chose some great colours for our first challenge of the month! For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-31-cas-colours-sketches-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-31-cas-colours-sketches-472/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the last challenge of the moth for CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. As it is the fifth challenge this month, we have both a sketch and a colour combination for you to use!
I will admit, I am not thrilled with my card. Maybe my border is too wide? It just feels like the Island Indigo overwhelms the rest of the card. The rest of the design team has inspiration for you HERE and I hope that you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another sketch with the team at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We look forward to seeing what you create this week following the sketch below. Remember to keep your creations clean and simple! You can share your cards with us HERE!
I will admit, this sketch had me scratching my head for a little bit. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what I wanted to do. I was flipping through my bin of dies and saw the balloons and decided to see what I could come up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-17-cas-colours-sketches-470/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; and this week it&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge. For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</guid>
      <description>Now that I have a little more mobility (and I do mean a little) with my right hand, I decided to try making a card on yesterday afternoon. Fine motor skills are still a bit of a struggle and I had to take a break part way through, but I managed to get a card done in time for the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches challenge for this week. It&amp;rsquo;s a sketch challenge this week&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations following the sketch below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-19-cas-colours-sketches-466/</guid>
      <description>As I did have some cards created for the design teams I&amp;rsquo;m on before I broke my wrist last week, I figured I&amp;rsquo;d still blog them. Typing is slow with only one hand!v I am so sad to not be creating&amp;hellip; I was on track to have a record breaking number of cards made. I haven&amp;rsquo;t gone fore more than 3 or 4 days without making cards in many weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-12-cas-colours-sketches-465/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches is back with another sketch challenge to inspire you. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
I stamped up a sheet of those wonderful Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and embossed them in white this time. I used a finger dauber to add colour to this butterfly after I&amp;rsquo;d cut it out, trying to keep colours in specific areas&amp;hellip; it helped that I used similar colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-05-cas-colours-sketches-464/</guid>
      <description>Bhavya is the host at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches for the month of April. She has chosen a great &amp;lsquo;garden&amp;rsquo; themed set of colours for us to use as her first colour challenge this month. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see how others interpret these colours!
For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-29-cas-colours-sketches-463/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a Tuesday, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with CAS Colours and Sketches. As it is the fifth Tuesday of a month, our challenge is a double&amp;hellip; Jeanne has chosen a past sketch and some retired colours to play with this week! Please make sure to have these three colours as the prominent colours of your clean and simple creation (but you can add neutrals as well). You are welcome to flip or rotate the sketch as long as the essence of the sketch remains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
