<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Copics on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/copics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Copics on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/copics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a 1 of 9 rectangles challenge at AAACards with the optional twist of gnomes&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your cards where you use only one of the 9 rectangles found if you divide a rectangular card in 9ths. Be sure to keep it clean and simple and share it with us HERE!
You KNEW I&amp;rsquo;d have to use the optional twist! I used a non-Christmas gnome stamp set but added a tiny holiday wish to it to make it a Christmas card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #489*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-27-cas-colours-sketches-489/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the sketch this week at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches! My card went together pretty quickly once I decided on what elements I wanted to use. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
My card uses a few pieces from my bin of extras that I kept overlooking. I had used just two of the layering stencils and these two pieces had very little colour on them&amp;hellip; so I grabbed my Copics and gave them a bit more colour before adding them to my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #487*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-13-cas-colours-sketches-487/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. This is a great sketch to showcase a little bit of patterned paper or an embossed panel&amp;hellip; or keep it just a solid colour. There are so many options!
I saw this sketch and immediately wanted to use this beautiful Stampin&#39; Up! paper from last year. It took a while for me to decide what to do with the other element on the card but I landed on the gnome and I like how it turned out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-21-aaacards-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-21-aaacards-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a moodboard challenge at AAACards&amp;hellip; you can take inspiration from any portion of the moodboard and create a clean and simple card to share with us!
I simply chose the health care part of the moodboard and made a get well card with a sweet puppy.
Card Info
*Images: Little Paper Shop Puppy Love; MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: MFT Stitched Rectangles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #482*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-09-cas-colours-sketches-482/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m hosting this month so this is a sketch I came up with. As always, you can rotate or flip the sketch but you need to make sure that the essence of the sketch remains true&amp;hellip; and remember to keep your card clean and simple!
Be sure to head over to the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches Blog to see how the rest of the design team interpreted the sketch and to share your creation with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the first clean and simple challenge of August with AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; which means you should use a few small images on your card&amp;hellip; the optional twist is (lady)bugs. The design team has some wonderful inspiration on the blog. We hope to see you playing along with us!
I love ladybugs and they are so easy to colour for someone like me who doesn&amp;rsquo;t find colouring zen-inducing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #235*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip; a quick post from me today to share my creations for the current CAS on Friday challenge. The current challenge is &amp;ldquo;silhouette&amp;rdquo; and instead of stamping, I did a black die cut instead. I used my Copics to create a little rainbow and then put the die cut floral spring on top of it. Because I used Copics, I used a smaller panel and put it on top of a white card so that the ink bleeding wouldn&amp;rsquo;t show through to the inside of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards Challenge#219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s July, it must be Christmas in July season! AAACards has an anything CAS Christmas challenge for this week with the optional twist of pets. Pull your Christmas stash out of storage and play along with us HERE!
You know I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy colouring so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go out for my animal&amp;hellip; so I chose this cute little birdie and coloured him up very simply. I love the mostly white card with just a hint of colour on the birdie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #476*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-28-cas-colours-sketches-476/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the last sketch challenge for the month of June with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; our sketch this time is a slimline card and I went for a mini-slimline as I prefer that size.
I took, a large floral stamp but only used a part of it so it would fit on my card. I even pulled out my Copics to do a little colouring (which isn&amp;rsquo;t easy as my wrist heals)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #404*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pop by the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done with the cue of RIDE. We love to see your clean and simple creations too&amp;hellip; share them HERE!
I almost skipped this challenge but then remembered this cute set from My Favorite Things and decided I&amp;rsquo;d give it a go. It&amp;rsquo;s not really my &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I pushed myself a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</guid>
      <description>Let me tell you how long it takes me type up a blog post using only my left hand! Most of my jobs over the years have been keyboard-centric so I am a fast typer&amp;hellip; in fact, I enjoy typing&amp;hellip; but this one handed thing is frustrating!!!
If only I had a dictation app on my laptop&amp;hellip;
Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge with the team ay Addicted to CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-17-aaacards-213/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for another clean and simple challenge with the team at AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; with the optional twist of Easter or Spring. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations with us HERE!
I did a quick and easy card thanks to this wonderful Lawn Fawn strip of flowers. I stamped them, coloured them quickly with a few spring colours of Copics, stamped my greeting and then put the flowers on the card with some foam adhesive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You Make My Heart Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</guid>
      <description>This is the last of the cards using this stamp set&amp;hellip; at least for a few days. I will admit I did something else with a few of the dies a few days ago so there will be more coming. I hope I haven&amp;rsquo;t played with them too much in the last bit and will find that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pull the set out again!
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Another Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not quite done with the images from that Pink Fresh Studio stamp and die set&amp;hellip; I think there&amp;rsquo;s still a few more coming up. Can you tell how much I enjoyed playing with them?
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Concord Crush
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Birthday
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; MFT Stitched Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Daisy Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>I really had a lot of fun with these floral images by Pink Fresh Studio&amp;hellip; they are quick and easy to colour which makes them perfect for me. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I could do more with them to make my cards less clean and simple &amp;hellip;. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to challenge myself on that one sometime.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Lot More Fabulous*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-04-a-lot-more-fabulous/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; just a quick post from me today to share another card with this gorgeous floral stamp set by Pink Fresh Studio.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Seaside Spray
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Memento Tuxedo Black; Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners
*Embellishments: Nuvo Aqua Shimmer; Pink &amp;amp; Main Rainbow Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I&amp;rsquo;m back with the team at Addicted to CAS with another clean and simple challenge for you all. We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your clean and simple cards featuring animals! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a CAS Perfectionist!!! I have some animal stamps in my stash that have never seen ink (at least not by me!) so I decided to pull out one of those sets to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Beautiful Blooms Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-31-beautiful-blooms-birthday/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my friend Bonnie and I went to one of our favourite local stamp stores after I was done work. I will admit I bought a few things I didn&amp;rsquo;t need&amp;hellip; but I am so happy I did! This fabulous floral set from Pink Fresh is perfect for my colouring preferences&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;ll see a few cards using this set in the next several days as I stamped them up at once and spent some time colouring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More Take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a few days ago, I had made another card for the current Less is More challenge but I felt it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as &amp;ldquo;clean and simple&amp;rdquo; as I wanted&amp;hellip; I still like the card so I&amp;rsquo;m sharing it with you now. Card Info
*Images: Altenew Celebrate Toay
*Ink: Versaamark; Copics
*Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! gold embossing powder
*Challenges: Less Is More #461</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #461*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I usually work on Saturdays (my work week is Wednesday thru Saturday) but I get one Saturday off each month&amp;hellip; this is that Saturday. I love my job, I really truly do&amp;hellip; but I do look forward to my Saturdays off!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less Is More&amp;hellip; our clean and simple challenge for the next two weeks is to use the colours pink and gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Floral Swag*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-25-floral-swag/</guid>
      <description>I just love these floral swag stamps and dies&amp;hellip; I stamped this one, coloured it and cut it out so that it could go over the edges of the layers I placed on the front of this card. Have I told you lately how much I LOVE my perfect layers tool to create those beautiful 1/16&amp;quot; borders???
Let me tell you about another tool I am in LOVE with lately. My friend at Calgary Laser Creations is a papercrafter at heart and she has created some acrylic tools to help you get your layers on even and straight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
