<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paper Rose on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/paper-rose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paper Rose on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:13:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/paper-rose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Stencilled Thanks*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 09:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/08/posts/2022-08-10-stencilled-thanks/</guid>
      <description>I am back to work this afternoon after my week of isolation thanks to Covid. I am feeling really good except a lingering tiredness but I&amp;rsquo;m sure that will get better with time. I really need to just take planned holidays from work instead of illness and injury!!
A friend asked for some thank you cards recently so I did up a few different designs for her. I really liked the look of using the last bit of ink on the blending brush to go over the white spots left behind by stencilling so I did a few like this one&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;. our theme for this challenge is Butterflies! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us and share your creations HERE! The design team has some beautiful butterfly cards for you to see&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to check them out!
I cut some of those gorgeous little butterflies out of glitter paper to create my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #468*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/07/posts/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Less is More&amp;hellip;. our cue word for challenge #468 is &amp;ldquo;emboss&amp;rdquo;. You can use any interpretation of the word in your clean and simple card.
I decided to go with an embossing folder for my card&amp;hellip; and I grabbed the etched butterflies from my pile of extras from the card I shared a few days ago as I think they look embossed as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/06/posts/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</guid>
      <description>Time Out Challenges is back with a great new challenge&amp;hellip; this time we want you to be inspired by being kind! Our sponsor for this challenge is CAS-ual Friday stamps.
I got these wonderful new dies from Paper Rose and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to play with them. I love how they look cut out of the gold foil cardstock!
Card Info
*Cardstock: gold mirror; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: Simon Says Stamp Big Thanks Words; Stampendous Big Words Thanks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</guid>
      <description>Let me tell you how long it takes me type up a blog post using only my left hand! Most of my jobs over the years have been keyboard-centric so I am a fast typer&amp;hellip; in fact, I enjoy typing&amp;hellip; but this one handed thing is frustrating!!!
If only I had a dictation app on my laptop&amp;hellip;
Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge with the team ay Addicted to CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #462*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/2022/04/posts/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less is More. As you can see from the graphic below, the prompt is &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo;. As always, we hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with our challenge and share your creations with us HERE!
I struggled a bit with the challenge as I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any stamps that scream &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip; so I had to think outside the box a little.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
