<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uniko on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/uniko/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uniko on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/uniko/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Washi Floral*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-02-rainbow-washi-floral/</guid>
      <description>I am running out of cards to share with you! I lost some time with card making first with my broken wrist in the spring and then again in August with Covid. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good these days but I feel like life has been busy and the mojo is harder to come by! I sit at my craft desk but get nothing accomplished! I hope my creative block doesn&amp;rsquo;t last too long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Circle in the Square*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-03-circle-in-the-square/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t make a lot of square cards&amp;hellip;. there&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with them, they look great, but I just don&amp;rsquo;t stray from my usual size very often. But for some reason, when I was designing this card, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t working on a regular A2 card so I changed things up and LOVE how it looks on the square! I added two extra pieces from the Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral Washi tape to the wreath for a little something &amp;ldquo;extra&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Aqua on Black*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 09:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-17-aqua-on-black/</guid>
      <description>This card started out as an experiment&amp;hellip; I wanted to see what this aqua coloured paste would look like on black&amp;hellip; and let me tell you&amp;hellip; it looks fabulous! It looked so nice I had to make a card with it, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not my usual clean and simple style.
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: Uniko Birthday Wishes
Ink: Verasfine Clair Nocturne
Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tasteful Labels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #543*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-11-freshly-made-sketches-543/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-11-freshly-made-sketches-543/</guid>
      <description>I loved the sketch the Cecile had for Freshly Made Sketches this week&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m glad I had a few minutes at my craft table to play along!
My card originally much more plain as I stamped directly on the larger white square and put the card together. The more I looked at it the more I knew it needed a little something more. I cut a smaller square and stamped on it then used my Perfect Layers tool to create a green border and then put it on top of what I had originally created&amp;hellip; and it looks SO much better in my opinion!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Wish Big*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-06-striped-wish-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-06-striped-wish-big/</guid>
      <description>I am in LOVE with this sparkle paper from Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! I used some thin strips of it, making sure to get the ombre to create my card today.
Card Info
Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color ombre sparkle paper
Images: Uniko Birthday Wishes
Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
Dies: A Jillian Vance Design Daisy
Embellishments: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!
Challenges: The Flower Challenge #70</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*A Pop of Red*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-10-a-pop-of-red/</guid>
      <description>For my card today, I searched through the archives at CAS Colours and Sketches to find a sketch I wanted to play with &amp;hellip; this was challenge #426 which was a colour and sketch challenge, but I only used the sketch.
What you can&amp;rsquo;t see in this photo is that I used a piercing cover plate die on the black banner which adds a little visual interest
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Washi Tape*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 09:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-22-washi-tape/</guid>
      <description>Happy Sunday all&amp;hellip; in true Calgary fashion, our first long weekend of &amp;ldquo;summer&amp;rdquo; has delivered us a mixed bag of weather. Friday it was really windy and wet and we had a little snow falling from the sky. Saturday was cool and mostly cloudy. So far this morning the sun is shining and it&amp;rsquo;s warming up a little. This is what you get with an elevation of 1045 m above sea level (that&amp;rsquo;s 3428 ft).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AAACards #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-15-aaacards-215/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a quick clean and simple card to share with you today with the new challenge at AAACards. You have two weeks to play along with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a guest designer for an upcoming challenge.
I had another idea in my head for this card but I can&amp;rsquo;t hold a pen well enough to actually colour at the moment, so I had to scrap that idea and come up with something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Memories*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 09:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-11-birthday-memories/</guid>
      <description>Hello crafty friends. I have been crafting a little bit as I find it is good therapy. both mentally and physically. I am also working here and there without my splint on (which I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to do) and while I&amp;rsquo;m not typing as fast as I normally would, it&amp;rsquo;s not the one handed hunt and peck I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing in the last month. With things working a little more in my favour, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to blog more often again &amp;hellip; I still have cards to share that I created before my fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m here with the latest challenge from Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; we want you to share your cards inspired by being on vacation! We have a prize from Lawn Fawn up for grabs!! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE!
My favourite vacations have been to the sun and water&amp;hellip; so I created a sunset across the water for you&amp;hellip;
Be sure to share your vacation inspired creations with us here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #403*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-03-casology-403/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-03-casology-403/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday creative friends&amp;hellip; I saw my surgeon yesterday and as expected, the plaster splint was removed and I now have a removable brace. I can wear the brace when I&amp;rsquo;m up and about or if the arm/wrist is fatigued. I have some stretches thatI&amp;rsquo;ve started doing that are really tough but I am told it will all get easier&amp;hellip; I am to use my arm and wrist as tolerated for anything non-weight bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
