<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CAS on Friday on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/cas-on-friday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CAS on Friday on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/cas-on-friday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #239*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-07-cas-on-friday-239/</guid>
      <description>I am playing along with the STRIPES challenge at CAS on Friday&amp;hellip;. this started out being a card for last weeks Freshly Made Sketches but I didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to finish it in time to play along with this. I also liked the stripes on the side instead of the bottom better so I switched things up!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, glitter paper
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Foiled Sentiments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #238*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-28-cas-on-friday-238/</guid>
      <description>I found a little time earlier this week to play along with the current TAG challenge at CAS on Friday. I have had this idea in my head for a bit and finally put it together for this card. I wanted to do it with just the tag on the card front to keep it more CAS but it just didn&amp;rsquo;t look right&amp;hellip; I had this piece of embossed cardstock on my desk, the leftovers from a previous creation, so I tried it and loved it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #235*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip; a quick post from me today to share my creations for the current CAS on Friday challenge. The current challenge is &amp;ldquo;silhouette&amp;rdquo; and instead of stamping, I did a black die cut instead. I used my Copics to create a little rainbow and then put the die cut floral spring on top of it. Because I used Copics, I used a smaller panel and put it on top of a white card so that the ink bleeding wouldn&amp;rsquo;t show through to the inside of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #178*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 14:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-01-cas-on-friday-178/</guid>
      <description>The current challenge at CAS on Friday is to make a thank you card. I love these open daisies by A Jillian Vance Design. I paired them with some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours to create my card for the challenge.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Tahitian Tide, Parakeet Party, Sweet Sorbet, Starry Sky
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Designs Open Daisy; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Two Challenges*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-13-two-challenges/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with two challenges today&amp;hellip; Color Throwdown #696 and CAS on Friday #233. The colours of the first challenge fit the theme of &amp;ldquo;condolence&amp;rdquo; for the second challenge absolutely perfectly!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Very Vanilla, Crumb Cake, Pear Pizzazz
*Images: Altenew Flower Vine
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms, Spendid Stems; MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Etc: foam adhesive
*Challenges: Color Throwdown #696; CAS on Friday #233</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
