<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MFT on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/mft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MFT on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/mft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; we are playing with a one layer card which means we want ONLY ink on paper&amp;hellip; no added die cuts, no layers. The twist for this challenge is to draw your own frame. Please share your creations with us HERE!
I shared my first creation for this challenge a few days ago&amp;hellip; but then realized that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use the die cut butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</guid>
      <description>October is Breast Cancer Awareness Month and the team at Time Out had originally had our challenge today as a Breast Cancer challenge&amp;hellip; as a colon cancer survivor (x2), I respectfully asked if we could change it to a cancer awareness challenge&amp;hellip; everyone knows about and talks about breast cancer, but no one talks about colon cancer (and many other cancers). It&amp;rsquo;s SO important to me that we talk about all forms of cancer, that we not be embarrassed about talking about our health, our bodies and the changes we are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-02-aaacards-225/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a 1 of 9 rectangles challenge at AAACards with the optional twist of gnomes&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your cards where you use only one of the 9 rectangles found if you divide a rectangular card in 9ths. Be sure to keep it clean and simple and share it with us HERE!
You KNEW I&amp;rsquo;d have to use the optional twist! I used a non-Christmas gnome stamp set but added a tiny holiday wish to it to make it a Christmas card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Rainbow Striped Corners*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-30-rainbow-striped-corners/</guid>
      <description>How on earth is it the end of September already? I&amp;rsquo;m still struggling to write the word September at work and now, tomorrow, I have to write October?! We&amp;rsquo;ve had a great month here weatherwise and so far haven&amp;rsquo;t seen any snow fly (we often get the first snow in September). We actually hit 28C (82F) earlier this week which is unheard of at this time of year! I worry that winter will be a lot less kind than fall has been so far!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*So Very Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 09:12:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-26-so-very-happy/</guid>
      <description>I took a few days off from blogging&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t have a lot of non-design team cards to share and honestly haven&amp;rsquo;t been feeling very creative lately. I am in my creative space for a while today and after I post this card I hope to have a little mojo flowing to create some stuff to share with you. I&amp;rsquo;m struggling to find my own ideas and am not feeling inspired by any of the cards I&amp;rsquo;ve pinned and saved to try to put my own spin on them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</guid>
      <description>October 1st is World Cardmaking Day and here at Less is More, we are celebrating a little early with a friendship themed challenge! We think making a card for a friend is a great way to celebrate World Cardmaking Day! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of very good friends who are always there for me&amp;hellip; to listen, to provide support, to make me laugh, to distract me, to do social things with&amp;hellip; so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make a card that I could give to one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook and as always, we thank them for their generousity!
This is such a lovely image to get inspiration from. I used the tree along the side of the photo along with some silver and grey for my inspiration
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; Lawn Fawn Silver Holograpic
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Fall Failure*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 11:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-19-fall-failure/</guid>
      <description>I was trying to do a more fall looking card with this but my colours (especially the yellow) were too bright. Of course I did a full 6X6 panel so I will be sharing another card with my too bright for fall flowers in the coming days.
I did a get well card because these colours looked so happy.
Card Info
*Images: MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Catherine Pooler Glitz, Martini, Over Coffee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 09:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-18-aaacards-224/</guid>
      <description>We have a colour challenge for you at AAACards this week&amp;hellip; with the optional twist of spots and dots. Use the graphic below to get your colour inspiration for your clean and simple cards.
The colours were a bit tough for me because while they look fine on this graphic, I had trouble getting them together on a card. I tried three different things before this one stuck&amp;hellip;
Card Info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Just Under The Wire*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-15-just-under-the-wire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 08:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-15-just-under-the-wire/</guid>
      <description>I had every intention of getting this post up yesterday but after a fall on Sunday (I missed the last step) I decided to take myself to Urgent Care yesterday before work. I managed to break the 5th metatarsal in my left foot and am now in a fancy boot/air cast. Sigh&amp;hellip;. If I didn&amp;rsquo;t have bad luck I&amp;rsquo;d have no luck at all!
Anyway&amp;hellip; I found a new to me challenge and decided to play along!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #552*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-11-freshly-made-sketches-552/</guid>
      <description>I got home from work yesterday and sat down in my creative space, hoping to make a card. I saw the latest sketch at Freshly Made Sketches and decided to try my hand at it&amp;hellip; I really hope my mojo shows up on the rest of my days off this week&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Paper: MFT Party Time
*Images: Pink Fresh Studios Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #407*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-casology-407/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-06-casology-407/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the first Tuesday of the month which means there is a new CASology challenge. Our cue for this month is HAPPY!
The cue is easy for me as the majority of the cards I make are for birthdays&amp;hellip; I pulled out some rainbow colours and an alphabet die set and created this for you!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Poppy Parade, Daffodil Delight, Granny Apple Green, Pacific Point, Highland Heather</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Scrappy Birthday*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-26-scrappy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Once again I used my bin of extras to create this card&amp;hellip; the flower, leaves and stitched rectangle were all already cut and unused from other projects.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Lemon Lime Twist, Berry Burst
*Images: Altenew Sincere Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms: MFT Stitched Rectangles
*Embellishments: Studio Katia Arctic Breeze Pearls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations August*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-24-christmas-craft-creations-august/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the latest challenge at Christmas Craft Creations! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
My winter activity is playing in the snow&amp;hellip;. you can see I had fun building an igloo and decorating it! In reality, I had more fun playing with my Glimmer Hot Foil Machine to create my snowy background LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Smokey Slate
*Images: Mama Elephant Merry Greetings; MFT Polar Penguins</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-21-aaacards-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-21-aaacards-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a moodboard challenge at AAACards&amp;hellip; you can take inspiration from any portion of the moodboard and create a clean and simple card to share with us!
I simply chose the health care part of the moodboard and made a get well card with a sweet puppy.
Card Info
*Images: Little Paper Shop Puppy Love; MFT Essential Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: MFT Stitched Rectangles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Striped Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-17-striped-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-17-striped-flower/</guid>
      <description>This was a great way to use a little bit of patterned paper&amp;hellip; Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pattern Party
*Dies: A Jillian Vance Design Open Daisy; MFT Celebrate
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners
*Etc: foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Paper Candles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-15-paper-candles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-15-paper-candles/</guid>
      <description>I truly have a lot of patterned paper&amp;hellip; and I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know why since it often doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit in to a clean and simple style! I think because it&amp;rsquo;s just so darn pretty! I go through periods where I use it a lot and periods where I don&amp;rsquo;t use it much. I think I need to go through a period where I don&amp;rsquo;t buy it.
Thanks so much to Nadine (@scrappinready on Instagram) for the inspiration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-07-aaacards-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for the first clean and simple challenge of August with AAACards. Our challenge for the next two weeks is &amp;ldquo;small and few&amp;rdquo; which means you should use a few small images on your card&amp;hellip; the optional twist is (lady)bugs. The design team has some wonderful inspiration on the blog. We hope to see you playing along with us!
I love ladybugs and they are so easy to colour for someone like me who doesn&amp;rsquo;t find colouring zen-inducing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Masked Word*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-05-masked-word/</guid>
      <description>I tried something a little different (at least for me) with this card&amp;hellip; nothing earth shattering, but I masked off the word celebrate before I ink blended over a stencil. Before I removed my mask, I also blended a little more of the same colours of ink over the piece after removing the stencil to soften the look of the colours a little and to really make my word pop. I like how it all looks kind of soft and dreamy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*In My Prayers*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-21-in-my-prayers/</guid>
      <description>I found a little relief from my shoulder issue thanks to a visit to my physical therapist and a treatment of IMS. She uses accupuncture needles to poke in to the muscles to try to get them to release. I&amp;rsquo;m still hurting but not nearly as much as I have been over the last two weeks. I see her again early next week for another treatment&amp;hellip; until then I am trying to use my right arm &amp;ldquo;properly&amp;rdquo;, stretching, using heat and ice and trying to relax that arm as much as I can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*When It Rains...*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-18-when-it-rains/</guid>
      <description>My blog title has nothing to do with my card today&amp;hellip; but it has to do with what&amp;rsquo;s going on in my world. As you know, I broke my right wrist in April. While I am getting mobility and strength back in that wrist, it would appear that the muscles around my right shoulder don&amp;rsquo;t like that I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the arm in awkward ways and they have now seized up making it near impossible to sit upright at my desk, let alone create.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; and that challenge is traditional Christmas. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll dig out some of your Christmas stash and play along with us!
To me, the traditional colours of Christmas are red, green and gold&amp;hellip;. and I think &amp;ldquo;sparkle&amp;rdquo; should be a Christmas colour as well LOL! I just love sparkly things, especially for Christmas cards!
Card Info
*Cardstock: assorted glitter papers
*Images: Simon Say Stamp Good Cheer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS on Friday #235*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-13-cas-on-friday-235/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip; a quick post from me today to share my creations for the current CAS on Friday challenge. The current challenge is &amp;ldquo;silhouette&amp;rdquo; and instead of stamping, I did a black die cut instead. I used my Copics to create a little rainbow and then put the die cut floral spring on top of it. Because I used Copics, I used a smaller panel and put it on top of a white card so that the ink bleeding wouldn&amp;rsquo;t show through to the inside of the card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #478*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-12-cas-colours-sketches-478/</guid>
      <description>Happy Tuesday my friends&amp;hellip; and a BIG happy birthday to my big sister! It&amp;rsquo;s a milestone birthday for her today and I&amp;rsquo;m sad to not be celebrating it with her. It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new sketch challenge with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. Patricia came up with this fun sketch for us all to try this week! I really look forward to seeing what *you* create!
I tried a few different things with this sketch and tossed them all in the bin&amp;hellip; until I decided to turn the sketch and then I came up with something I liked on my first try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards Challenge#219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-10-aaacards-challenge-219/</guid>
      <description>If it&amp;rsquo;s July, it must be Christmas in July season! AAACards has an anything CAS Christmas challenge for this week with the optional twist of pets. Pull your Christmas stash out of storage and play along with us HERE!
You know I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy colouring so I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go out for my animal&amp;hellip; so I chose this cute little birdie and coloured him up very simply. I love the mostly white card with just a hint of colour on the birdie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Offset Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-08-offset-wreath/</guid>
      <description>I find myself always leaning towards the same layouts when I am using a circle element on my card (and squares too) so I consciously made an effort to do something different with this rainbow floral wreath.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
*Etc: Pink Fresh Studio Rainbow Floral washi tape; foam adhesive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #405*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology... our cue for you for July is WINDY.
I have a funny wind story&amp;hellip; last fall we put up some security cameras over our garage. Since the trees have leafed this year, we often get alerts from the cameras of &amp;ldquo;motion&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the other day we had hundreds of alerts in the morning when we work up&amp;hellip; each one of them was the leaves on the trees thanks to the wind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #342*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-03-freshly-made-sketches-342/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-03-freshly-made-sketches-342/</guid>
      <description>I loved the ease of the sketch by Kim at Freshly Made Sketches this week. I combined the idea of using patterned paper with Kim&amp;rsquo;s idea of horizontal stripes to create my card. I also used a stamp and die that I bought YEARS ago that I&amp;rsquo;ve never used!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Granny Apple Green
*Paper: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pattern Party
*Images: Scrapbook &amp;amp; Cards Today; MFT Bitty Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #468*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Less is More&amp;hellip;. our cue word for challenge #468 is &amp;ldquo;emboss&amp;rdquo;. You can use any interpretation of the word in your clean and simple card.
I decided to go with an embossing folder for my card&amp;hellip; and I grabbed the etched butterflies from my pile of extras from the card I shared a few days ago as I think they look embossed as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Simple Wreath*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-27-simple-wreath/</guid>
      <description>This card was so super easy to put together&amp;hellip; and I love it! The hardest part was figuring out where the flowers should go!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green
*Images: Gina K Where Flowers Bloom
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Copics
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms; MFT Stitched Circles; Waffle Flower Additional Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-26-aaacards-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards! We have a sketch for you this week with the added optional twist of flowers. Of course I did both (because I love florals!) Share your card with us HERE for a chance to be chosen as a guest designer in an upcoming challenge!
I always struggle with the placement of things like the sketch shows so I wanted to do something different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Throwdown #698*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-24-color-throwdown-698/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m playing along with the current challenge at Color Throwdown. I loved the look of the inspiration photo!
I have seen a few people do this idea of layering their die cuts to show the rainbow of colour&amp;hellip; it was harder to do than I expected, but I think it turned out OK!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Parakeet Party, Real Red, Yoyo Yellow, Pink Passion
*Dies: MFT Celebrate; Lawn Fawn Everyday Sentiment Banners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 3*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-23-color-hues-43-take-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-23-color-hues-43-take-3/</guid>
      <description>When you find a colour combination you just love, sometimes you have to go with it. That&amp;rsquo;s me with the colours blue and green&amp;hellip; specifically Tim Holtz Twisted Citron and Salty Ocean. Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Parakeet Party and Tahitian Tide are right up there for me too!
And of course, I get to play along one more time with the challenge at Color Hues
I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve *ever* entered one challenge more than one time&amp;hellip; and this is my third entry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations Trees*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-22-christmas-craft-creations-trees/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still some time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations June theme of TREES! This is a great challenge to help you get a few Christmas cards made throughout the year. I had promised myself to make more Christmas cards before October and while I&amp;rsquo;ve done that, it&amp;rsquo;s really only been for this challenge! Maybe I should make one day a month where I make only Christmas cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-21-cas-colours-sketches-475/</guid>
      <description>I am so happy that Samantha chose some of the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for our challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches this week. I just love the new colours and especially these three! I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with this colour combination this week!
These colours are just so happy! They make me think of popsicles, and beach balls, and shovels and pails&amp;hellip; all those wonderfully fun things in the summer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #43... take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-20-color-hues-43-take-2/</guid>
      <description>Is it good or bad that this Pink Fresh Studio stamp is one stamp with several images that you stamp, stencil and cut all at once? It&amp;rsquo;s good because it&amp;rsquo;s easy, it&amp;rsquo;s bad because you get stuck with several cards that look similar.
The good news is that this is a LOVELY set and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create with it! And I get to play along with Color Hues again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sweet Birthday Wishes*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-17-sweet-birthday-wishes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-17-sweet-birthday-wishes/</guid>
      <description>A quick and easy card from me today&amp;hellip; not honestly sure where I got this colour combination. I know I didn&amp;rsquo;t come up with it on my own since I use coral and yellow so seldom! Hmmmm, I wish I could remember.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Seaside Spray, Pineapple Punch, Flirty Flamingo
*Images: MFT Bitty Birthday Wishes
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne
*Dies: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Pierced Blooms
*Etc: bling from my stash</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*The Best Day Ever*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-15-the-best-day-ever/</guid>
      <description>I worked on this card a few weeks ago while my wrist was still pretty sore and useless (instead of kind of sore and useless like it is now) and decided to play with a design that featured patterned paper. Doing this made it all a little easier for me and my wrist but still allowed for me to feel like I was being creative.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Night of Navy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-12-aaacards-217/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for popping by today! I&amp;rsquo;m sharing with you, my card for the current clean and simple challenge at AAA Cards. We want you to use only 1 of the 9 rectangles on the front of your A2 card when you divide it up evenly (or 1/9 of any card size you like to use) with the optional twist of Butterflies.
The 1/9th is the hard part for this card&amp;hellip; I decided to use a little ink blending to create the rectangle to help me envision it&amp;hellip; to create a little dimension, I used glue along the body of the butterfly and foam adhesive on the wings to make them pop up a bit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made Sketches #539</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-09-freshly-made-sketches-539/</guid>
      <description>I created a quick card to play along with the current sketch at Freshly Made Sketches&amp;hellip; I had the card all put together and ready to photograph and I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it. So I used my stitched rectangle die to cut off the front of the card and layered it on to another card and I like it so much better. The extra panel and the stitched lines really helped to make this card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-cas-colours-sketches-473/</guid>
      <description>Samantha is the host for the month of June at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches and she chose some great colours for our first challenge of the month! For our colour challenges, you must use all of the stated challenge colours. You may also use neutral colours; however, the challenge colours should be the most noticeable ones featured on your card. We use Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up colour names for reference, but you are welcome to use any other companies&amp;rsquo; products as long as you match the challenge colours as closely as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #404*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-07-casology-404/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pop by the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done with the cue of RIDE. We love to see your clean and simple creations too&amp;hellip; share them HERE!
I almost skipped this challenge but then remembered this cute set from My Favorite Things and decided I&amp;rsquo;d give it a go. It&amp;rsquo;s not really my &amp;ldquo;style&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I pushed myself a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Color Hues #42*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-06-color-hues-42/</guid>
      <description>I saw a few cards on some Facebook groups I&amp;rsquo;m on as well as on Instagram, using the current challenge from Color Hues&amp;hellip; and while I don&amp;rsquo;t often reach for yellow, I really felt like I wanted to play along with this challenge. I love black and white with a pop of colour&amp;hellip; I usually do red, but yellow sure does look happy!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Daffodil Delight, Basic Black</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More! We want to see your &amp;ldquo;masculine&amp;rdquo; themed cards for the next two weeks! Share them with us HERE!!!
I always struggle with masculine cards. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much for masculine images and I tend towards purples and reds in my colour selections. I will admit, I almost skipped this challenge! I was poking around Pinterest and searched for &amp;ldquo;masculine colour combinations&amp;rdquo; and something similar to what I used popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Freshly Made #538*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-freshly-made-538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-03-freshly-made-538/</guid>
      <description>I was able to get myself caught up with design team duties and found a little time to play with some current challenges. Today I&amp;rsquo;m sharing the card I created for the latest sketch at Freshly Made Sketches.
I was able to grab this flower from my bin of extras to add a pop of colour to my black and white card.
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-31-cas-colours-sketches-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-31-cas-colours-sketches-472/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the last challenge of the moth for CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches. As it is the fifth challenge this month, we have both a sketch and a colour combination for you to use!
I will admit, I am not thrilled with my card. Maybe my border is too wide? It just feels like the Island Indigo overwhelms the rest of the card. The rest of the design team has inspiration for you HERE and I hope that you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Wish Big*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-30-wish-big/</guid>
      <description>Well *you* can&amp;rsquo;t see that this card says &amp;ldquo;wish big&amp;rdquo;, but it does. I used black ink on the blue cardstock and it&amp;rsquo;s really subtle but it&amp;rsquo;s there. I should have done something different, but honestly, the card was all put together when I decided to stamp on the strip. It was a bad decision LOL!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Berry Burst, Lemon Lime Twist, Starry Sky
*Images: MFT Bitty Birthday Greetings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*AAACards #216*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-29-aaacards-216/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at AAACards! AAA Cards is a clean and simple challenge blog that posts a new challenge every two weeks. We love to share our ideas on the cue cards and, more importantly, love to see what others come up with for our challenges! I sure hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your creations with us HERE!
Let me explain our graphic a bit&amp;hellip; for challenge #216, we want you to use the colours that you see in the graphic&amp;hellip; and *optionally* we&amp;rsquo;d like to see a shaker card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenged with Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; for the next two weeks, we want to see you sharing your cards featuring stripes! I am the host for this challenge, which means this theme was my idea! Please share your clean and simple cards with strips with us HERE!
I had a bit of trouble deciding on what I wanted to do for my card for this challenge&amp;hellip; I have a lot of options when it comes to stripes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-24-cas-colours-sketches-471/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another sketch with the team at CAS Colours and Sketches&amp;hellip; We look forward to seeing what you create this week following the sketch below. Remember to keep your creations clean and simple! You can share your cards with us HERE!
I will admit, this sketch had me scratching my head for a little bit. I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out what I wanted to do. I was flipping through my bin of dies and saw the balloons and decided to see what I could come up with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*April 2022 Sheetload*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-23-april-2022-sheetload/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-23-april-2022-sheetload/</guid>
      <description>Before I broke my wrist, I played along with the April 2022 Sheetload of Cards&amp;hellip; The way it worked out trying to make one card, it made more sense to make two since what I cut off was exactly what I needed for the second piece. These two cards are the same, but different
I really do love the size of a mini slimline!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Cherry Cobbler, Lucky Limeade</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Blue Ink*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-19-blue-ink/</guid>
      <description>I had my first session at physical therapy yesterday and while things are better than they had been, I still feel like there is a very long way to go before this injury is a thing of the past. I will be working on stretches and trying to use my right hand/arm/wrist as normally as possible. There is still some swelling and the joint is extremely stiff. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a little discouraged as I write this because I just want this whole thing to be a memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Metallic Watercolours*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-18-metallic-watercolours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-18-metallic-watercolours/</guid>
      <description>I got these Kuretake watercolours for Christmas and have been too intimidated to play with them. I am not an artist. I am not artistic. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to colour. But I do know how to scribble on paper LOL
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; black watercolour paper
*Dies: MFT Celebrate
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners
*Etc: Kuretake Gem Colors Watercolours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Birthday Smiles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-12-birthday-smiles/</guid>
      <description>You can see that this card looks a little similar to the one yesterday&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s another of the distress ink blending panels I did. In this one I feel like the Villainous Potion is a little too dark&amp;hellip;
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
*Images: MFT All Smiles
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Ink in Villainous Potion, Peacock Feathers, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Perfect Layers; Fricken Square Corners</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-10-cas-colours-sketches-469/</guid>
      <description>Now that I have a little more mobility (and I do mean a little) with my right hand, I decided to try making a card on yesterday afternoon. Fine motor skills are still a bit of a struggle and I had to take a break part way through, but I managed to get a card done in time for the CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches challenge for this week. It&amp;rsquo;s a sketch challenge this week&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us by sharing your clean and simple creations following the sketch below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! I hope that wherever you are right now that the sun is shining&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that Mother Nature got the memo that it&amp;rsquo;s now May and hopefully the spring snow will be done for the year. It&amp;rsquo;s currently pretty lovely, but here in Calgary it can change without much notice!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; for challenge #464 we want to see your clean and simple creations using a tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Happy Birthday AAA Cards!*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-01-happy-birthday-aaa-cards/</guid>
      <description>AAACards is celebrating it&amp;rsquo;s 8th birthday!! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll celebrate along with us by creating a clean and simple birthday card and sharing with us HERE. No birthday would be complete without presents so there are some prizes to be won as well! Head to the AAACards blog for all of the details!
Someone posted about an easy interactive card idea that Jennifer McGuire did a video on&amp;hellip; so I watched the video and decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</guid>
      <description>Let me tell you how long it takes me type up a blog post using only my left hand! Most of my jobs over the years have been keyboard-centric so I am a fast typer&amp;hellip; in fact, I enjoy typing&amp;hellip; but this one handed thing is frustrating!!!
If only I had a dictation app on my laptop&amp;hellip;
Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge with the team ay Addicted to CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Christmas Craft Creations April 2022*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 02:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-27-christmas-craft-creations-april-2022/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s still time to play along with the Christmas Craft Creations April challenge! We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your Christmas cards using plaid or tartan!
When plaid first started being popular (again), I resisted it. I honestly wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan. But over the years it&amp;rsquo;s grown on me! There&amp;rsquo;s just something about a good old red and black buffalo check&amp;hellip;.
I had fun with some Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up plaid papers and the L&amp;rsquo;il Gnome from Simon Says Stamp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really missing my creative space now&amp;hellip; I had surgery on my right wrist yesterday and am hoping things will start to feel better again soon. I&amp;rsquo;m only sharing design team creations now as typing blog posts is very slow with only one hand.
It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday so it&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with the team ay Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;
I focussed my one layer card on the bottom of my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip;. the challenge at Time Out Challenges is spring! I love spring and how the world seems to come back to life. I chose butterflies as they will be gracing our gardens soon!
I played with some white embossed Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and the awesome Birthday Brights rainbow paper from MFT on a slimline card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>Some more of those Pink Fresh Studio rainbow butterflies that I cut out &amp;hellip; I added a few matted layers and a strip of black and white stripes.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Orange Marmalade, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners; Perfect Layers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You Make My Heart Happy*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-10-you-make-my-heart-happy/</guid>
      <description>This is the last of the cards using this stamp set&amp;hellip; at least for a few days. I will admit I did something else with a few of the dies a few days ago so there will be more coming. I hope I haven&amp;rsquo;t played with them too much in the last bit and will find that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to pull the set out again!
Card Info
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Another Flower*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-08-another-flower/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not quite done with the images from that Pink Fresh Studio stamp and die set&amp;hellip; I think there&amp;rsquo;s still a few more coming up. Can you tell how much I enjoyed playing with them?
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Concord Crush
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Birthday
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics
*Dies: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms; Taylored Expressions Simple Strips; MFT Stitched Circles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Daisy Celebrate*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-06-daisy-celebrate/</guid>
      <description>I really had a lot of fun with these floral images by Pink Fresh Studio&amp;hellip; they are quick and easy to colour which makes them perfect for me. I&amp;rsquo;m sure I could do more with them to make my cards less clean and simple &amp;hellip;. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to challenge myself on that one sometime.
Card Info
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Beautiful Blooms, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Memento Tuxedo Black; Copics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-02-addicted-to-cas-217/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I&amp;rsquo;m back with the team at Addicted to CAS with another clean and simple challenge for you all. We&amp;rsquo;d love to see your clean and simple cards featuring animals! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE for your chance to be chosen as a CAS Perfectionist!!! I have some animal stamps in my stash that have never seen ink (at least not by me!) so I decided to pull out one of those sets to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 11:28:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-28-you/</guid>
      <description>I am so often in awe at how fast time flies by. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe that we&amp;rsquo;re at the end of March already. Here in Calgary that means that the weather is unpredictable. It can be sunny and warm one day and snowing the next. Today is cloudy and cool but there is no snow on the ground&amp;hellip; so I&amp;rsquo;ll be happy about that.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use products that I don&amp;rsquo;t tent to grab for regularly&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing some ink blending playing with some alcohol inks too.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
