<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ATCAS on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/atcas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ATCAS on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/atcas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #230*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-01-addicted-to-cas-230/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS that starts today. The code word is Autumn. Play along with us by sharing you clean and simple cards HERE!
I had fun doing a little ink blending on a piece of cardstock and then stamping and cutting out these fun leaves. I don&amp;rsquo;t use a lot of brown in my cards but an autumn theme and these colours called for some brown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #229*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-17-addicted-to-cas-229/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back with another Addicted to CAS challenge&amp;hellip;
Just a quick post for me before I head off to work. I usually do my blogging on Wednesday mornings before work and I lost Wednesday morning to Urgent Care (see yesterdays post) so I am feeling more than a little behind!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Yupo
*Images: Studio Katia Birthday Greetings
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Alcohol Inks in Raspberry, Glacier, Alchemy (pearl)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #228*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-03-addicted-to-cas-228/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Addicted to CAS. This challenge was difficult for me&amp;hellip;. because I don&amp;rsquo;t like birds! I have a few in my stash but they don&amp;rsquo;t really get used. But something different happened when the current Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! catalogue came out and I NEEDED these sweet bird stamps and the punch that goes with it!
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Granny Apple Green, Bermuda Bay, Pumpkin Pie</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #227*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-20-addicted-to-cas-227/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new challenge at Addicted to CAS today&amp;hellip; time to show us your clean and simple creations featuring the colour pink!
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why but I struggled with this prompt&amp;hellip;. but then I gabbed out some stencils and had a little play with them. I stencilled the pink swirls first and then put a second stencil on top of the first stencil and used Glimmer Paste so that the sparkly circles only showed up on the pink swirls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #226*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-06-addicted-to-cas-226/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll head over to the blog to see what the design team has come up with for this challenge as there&amp;rsquo;s always some great inspiration by my team mates! And we&amp;rsquo;d love to see you play along with us too!
As I recently had another challenge that was a tropical theme (where I did florals) I decided to turn my focus to a tropical drink instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #225*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-23-addicted-to-cas-225/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-23-addicted-to-cas-225/</guid>
      <description>The code word at Addicted to CAS is Nautical&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along. The design team has created some fun ideas that you can see HERE.
I had a bit in my stash that would have been ok for this challenge but nothing that was speaking to me&amp;hellip; so I used some dies to create my nautical themed card instead.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Sweet Sorbet, Starry Sky</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-09-addicted-to-cas-224/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Addicted to CAS! For the next two weeks we&amp;rsquo;d like you share how you interpret the code word of &amp;ldquo;kids&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to see what the rest of the design team has done because there are some other fabulous cards!
I went with a new baby card, partly because I needed a few in my stash!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-25-addicted-to-cas-223/</guid>
      <description>Good morning crafty friends&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Addicted to CAS! We are playing with the code word GRID for this challenge. I will admit that I struggled with this challenge. I had no idea how to interpret this word. But then I remembered I had some patterned papers that had a grid-look to them&amp;hellip; and I went with the one that was more delicate looking to create my card for today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-11-addicted-to-cas-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-11-addicted-to-cas-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; the code word for challenge #222 is DOTS! There are so many wonderfully fun ideas on the challenge blog by the design team&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll go check them out. And then you need to create your own dotted masterpieces to share with us! I wanted to have some fun with the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! In Color colours for 2022-2024&amp;hellip; so I used some old circle punches and cut out a bunch in three different colours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-28-addicted-to-cas-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenged with Addicted to CAS&amp;hellip; for the next two weeks, we want to see you sharing your cards featuring stripes! I am the host for this challenge, which means this theme was my idea! Please share your clean and simple cards with strips with us HERE!
I had a bit of trouble deciding on what I wanted to do for my card for this challenge&amp;hellip; I have a lot of options when it comes to stripes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-14-addicted-to-cas-220/</guid>
      <description>Challenge #220 at Addicted to CAS is all about flowers&amp;hellip;. we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see your beautiful flower creations!
You get a bonus card from me today&amp;hellip;. I created my alcohol ink background and fit two flower dies on it &amp;hellip; and since they are so similar I decided to share them both in one post
I really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your cards HERE!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Addicted to CAS #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-30-addicted-to-cas-219/</guid>
      <description>Let me tell you how long it takes me type up a blog post using only my left hand! Most of my jobs over the years have been keyboard-centric so I am a fast typer&amp;hellip; in fact, I enjoy typing&amp;hellip; but this one handed thing is frustrating!!!
If only I had a dictation app on my laptop&amp;hellip;
Anyway, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge with the team ay Addicted to CAS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
