<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Picket Fence Studios on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/picket-fence-studios/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Picket Fence Studios on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/picket-fence-studios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #408*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-04-casology-408/</guid>
      <description>It is with some sadness that I am here with the final challenge at CASology... after many years of wonderful clean and simple challenges, Melissa has decided it is time to retire the CASology Challenge. I think it would be an awesome send off to have a lot of cards submitted for this final challenge&amp;hellip; an awesome tribute to a great challenge and to a great team of inspiring CAS creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Subdued Thank You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Back in early July we lost a very good friend after a short illness&amp;hellip; it was devastating to lose a friend that we loved so much. She was one of my regular customers in terms of card orders. Her husband approached me after her funeral, asking if I would please make him some thank you cards to send out to people who helped out so much during her brief illness and after her death&amp;hellip; and I said &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #483*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-16-cas-colours-sketches-483/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-16-cas-colours-sketches-483/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new colour challenge at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches that starts today&amp;hellip;. these colours are PERFECT to use on a black background if you like that sort of popping neon appearance. We always love to see what others do with our sketches and colour combinations so I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along and share your card with us!
I absolutely LOVE how some colours just POP off of a black background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Every two weeks we have a challenge of a different type complete with prizes for our winners! For this week, Varada Sharma is offering us two $15 vouchers to give to our winners!! To win, simply share your creations inspired by the photo below! You can see all of the information and share them HERE.
I was inspired by the sunset and the silhouette of the grasses on the shore for my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CASology #405*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-casology-405/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at CASology... our cue for you for July is WINDY.
I have a funny wind story&amp;hellip; last fall we put up some security cameras over our garage. Since the trees have leafed this year, we often get alerts from the cameras of &amp;ldquo;motion&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; the other day we had hundreds of alerts in the morning when we work up&amp;hellip; each one of them was the leaves on the trees thanks to the wind!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
