<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TO on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TO on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #224*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-06-time-out-challenges-224/</guid>
      <description>October is Breast Cancer Awareness Month and the team at Time Out had originally had our challenge today as a Breast Cancer challenge&amp;hellip; as a colon cancer survivor (x2), I respectfully asked if we could change it to a cancer awareness challenge&amp;hellip; everyone knows about and talks about breast cancer, but no one talks about colon cancer (and many other cancers). It&amp;rsquo;s SO important to me that we talk about all forms of cancer, that we not be embarrassed about talking about our health, our bodies and the changes we are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #223*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-22-time-out-223/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook and as always, we thank them for their generousity!
This is such a lovely image to get inspiration from. I used the tree along the side of the photo along with some silver and grey for my inspiration
Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black; Lawn Fawn Silver Holograpic
Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*TIme Out Challenges #222*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-08-time-out-challenges-222/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a word prompt challenge at Time Out Challenges. We have a $25 gift card to Lawn Fawn up for grabs for one lucky player!!
This is such a beautiful quote by Maya Angelou&amp;hellip;. and it&amp;rsquo;s something I try to do when I&amp;rsquo;m at work. I work at the front desk of a chiropractic clinic and we often see people who are in a lot of pain. I try had to be a bright spot in their day, maybe help them feel a little better for a few minutes while they have to interact with me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #221*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-25-time-out-challenges-221/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges with a wonderful prize from Birch Press Designs to be won!! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along, sharing your FESTIVE cards!!
I know that Festive can refer to a lot of different things, but to me, festive is Christmas&amp;hellip; so I made a Christmas Card using a product I bought at the end of the season last year and hadn&amp;rsquo;t yet played with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #220*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-11-time-out-challenges-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-11-time-out-challenges-220/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back as part of the design team at Time Out Challenges with a new challenge to get your creative juices flowing! This is one of two non-clean and simple blogs that I design for so let your creativity flow as much as you want with these challenges!
For the next two weeks, we want to see you create your own backgrounds! We have an awesome prize from Stamplorations available to be won as well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #219*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-28-time-out-challenges-219/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new photo inspiration challenge at Time Out Challenges. Every two weeks we have a challenge of a different type complete with prizes for our winners! For this week, Varada Sharma is offering us two $15 vouchers to give to our winners!! To win, simply share your creations inspired by the photo below! You can see all of the information and share them HERE.
I was inspired by the sunset and the silhouette of the grasses on the shore for my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #218*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-14-time-out-challenges-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-14-time-out-challenges-218/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for you to be inspired by words with the latest Time Out Challenge&amp;hellip; you can see the quote in the graphic below. Our sponsor for this challenge is Newton&amp;rsquo;s Nook&amp;hellip; if you share your card with us you&amp;rsquo;ll have a chance at winning a prize from them!
I read this quote over and over and over again and the word that stood out to me each time was &amp;ldquo;dream&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; so I made a &amp;ldquo;dreamy&amp;rdquo; card for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #217*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-30-time-out-challenges-217/</guid>
      <description>Time Out Challenges is back with a great new challenge&amp;hellip; this time we want you to be inspired by being kind! Our sponsor for this challenge is CAS-ual Friday stamps.
I got these wonderful new dies from Paper Rose and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to play with them. I love how they look cut out of the gold foil cardstock!
Card Info
Cardstock: gold mirror; Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: Simon Says Stamp Big Thanks Words; Stampendous Big Words Thanks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #216*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-16-time-out-challenges-216/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-16-time-out-challenges-216/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; up for grabs this week is a $25 credit at Top Flight Stamps! Play along with us by sharing your card HERE. Our prompt for this challenge is &amp;ldquo;tropical&amp;rdquo;.
I had some fun with the new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Colours and an old stamp and die set. Some of the leaves are stamped, some are cut out&amp;hellip; I was able to create a little more dimension this way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out Challenges #215*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-02-time-out-challenges-215/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; for challenge #215 we have a wonderful prize available to be won thanks to our generous sponsor, STAMPlorations. We really hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us!
For this challenge, we want you to be inspired by the photo in the card below. You can take anything from this inspiration photo and translate it on to your creation. I struggled with this photo&amp;hellip; until I remembered that inspiration can come from anything in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #213*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-05-time-out-213/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m here with the latest challenge from Time Out Challenges&amp;hellip; we want you to share your cards inspired by being on vacation! We have a prize from Lawn Fawn up for grabs!! Be sure to share your creations with us HERE!
My favourite vacations have been to the sun and water&amp;hellip; so I created a sunset across the water for you&amp;hellip;
Be sure to share your vacation inspired creations with us here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #212*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-21-time-out-212/</guid>
      <description>Good morning friends&amp;hellip;. the challenge at Time Out Challenges is spring! I love spring and how the world seems to come back to life. I chose butterflies as they will be gracing our gardens soon!
I played with some white embossed Pink Fresh Studio butterflies and the awesome Birthday Brights rainbow paper from MFT on a slimline card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Time Out #211*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-07-time-out-211/</guid>
      <description>Happy Thursday crafty friends&amp;hellip; the team at Time Out Challenges is back with a new photo inspiration challenge. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you create using the photo below as inspiration.
Share your creations with us HERE for your chance to not only be chosen to play along as a Guest Designer in an upcoming challenge but to win a $15 credit to shop at our sponsor, Poppystamps!
I used a layered diamond die cut pieces that I cut in half to create some blue and green and grey mountains.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
