<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LessIsMore on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/lessismore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LessIsMore on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/lessismore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #475*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/10/2022-10-08-less-is-more-475/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; we are playing with a one layer card which means we want ONLY ink on paper&amp;hellip; no added die cuts, no layers. The twist for this challenge is to draw your own frame. Please share your creations with us HERE!
I shared my first creation for this challenge a few days ago&amp;hellip; but then realized that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use the die cut butterfly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #474*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-24-less-is-more-474/</guid>
      <description>October 1st is World Cardmaking Day and here at Less is More, we are celebrating a little early with a friendship themed challenge! We think making a card for a friend is a great way to celebrate World Cardmaking Day! We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I&amp;rsquo;ve got a couple of very good friends who are always there for me&amp;hellip; to listen, to provide support, to make me laugh, to distract me, to do social things with&amp;hellip; so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d make a card that I could give to one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #473*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-10-less-is-more-473/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a black and white clean and simple challenge this week at Less is More&amp;hellip; I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along!
I used a portion of a great Poppy Stamps frame die to create the focal point on my card. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how I feel about the uneven white mat around my focal point&amp;hellip; hmmmm Card Info
Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black
Images: Taylored Expressions Simple Strips
Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #472*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-27-less-is-more-472/</guid>
      <description>The new challenge at Less is More is to use vellum. There are so many different ways to use vellum in your creations and I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what you all come up with! I had a few ideas in my head about how I wanted to use vellum and I decided I wanted to try foiling on it to see if it would work. I&amp;rsquo;m here to report that it works pretty well, although there are some splotchy spots so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend doing anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t line art or sentiments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #471*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/08/2022-08-13-less-is-more-471/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge over at the Less is More blog&amp;hellip;. we are looking to see your one layer cards (which means the one layer is your card base) with your favourite flower! Be sure to head over to the Less is More blog to see the beautiful creations by the rest of the design team and to share your creations with us.
You knew this wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a difficult challenge for me&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #470*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-30-less-is-more-470/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new clean and simple challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;. our theme for this challenge is Butterflies! I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with us and share your creations HERE! The design team has some beautiful butterfly cards for you to see&amp;hellip; be sure to go to the blog to check them out!
I cut some of those gorgeous little butterflies out of glitter paper to create my card&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #469*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-16-less-is-more-469/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a colour challenge at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; and that challenge is traditional Christmas. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll dig out some of your Christmas stash and play along with us!
To me, the traditional colours of Christmas are red, green and gold&amp;hellip;. and I think &amp;ldquo;sparkle&amp;rdquo; should be a Christmas colour as well LOL! I just love sparkly things, especially for Christmas cards!
Card Info
Cardstock: assorted glitter papers
Images: Simon Say Stamp Good Cheer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #468*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-02-less-is-more-468/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with Less is More&amp;hellip;. our cue word for challenge #468 is &amp;ldquo;emboss&amp;rdquo;. You can use any interpretation of the word in your clean and simple card.
I decided to go with an embossing folder for my card&amp;hellip; and I grabbed the etched butterflies from my pile of extras from the card I shared a few days ago as I think they look embossed as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-18-less-is-more-467/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new one layer card challenge over at Simply Less is More&amp;hellip; a one layer card means there are no other pieces of cardstock other than your card base. If you want to use dies, they have to be inlaid. For me, the best way to achieve a one layer card is some simple stamping.
you may add words as well* I had a thought in my head but had trouble getting all of the pieces together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #466*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/06/2022-06-04-less-is-more-466/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More! We want to see your &amp;ldquo;masculine&amp;rdquo; themed cards for the next two weeks! Share them with us HERE!!!
I always struggle with masculine cards. I don&amp;rsquo;t have much for masculine images and I tend towards purples and reds in my colour selections. I will admit, I almost skipped this challenge! I was poking around Pinterest and searched for &amp;ldquo;masculine colour combinations&amp;rdquo; and something similar to what I used popped up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #465*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-21-less-is-more-465/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a colour challenge over at the Less is More blog. For this challenge we are playing with my favourite colour combination&amp;hellip; RAINBOW! There is some wonderful inspiration to be seen created by the rest of the design team.. click HERE to check them out!
I absolutely love creating with rainbows&amp;hellip; they can be bright, muted, pastel, jewel toned&amp;hellip; whatever you feel like! I received my new Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #464*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/05/2022-05-07-less-is-more-464/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday!! I hope that wherever you are right now that the sun is shining&amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that Mother Nature got the memo that it&amp;rsquo;s now May and hopefully the spring snow will be done for the year. It&amp;rsquo;s currently pretty lovely, but here in Calgary it can change without much notice!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new clean and simple challenge at Less is More&amp;hellip; for challenge #464 we want to see your clean and simple creations using a tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #463*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-23-less-is-more-463/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m really missing my creative space now&amp;hellip; I had surgery on my right wrist yesterday and am hoping things will start to feel better again soon. I&amp;rsquo;m only sharing design team creations now as typing blog posts is very slow with only one hand.
It&amp;rsquo;s Saturday so it&amp;rsquo;s time for another challenge with the team ay Simply Less is More&amp;hellip;
I focussed my one layer card on the bottom of my card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More #462*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-09-less-is-more-462/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less is More. As you can see from the graphic below, the prompt is &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo;. As always, we hope you&amp;rsquo;ll play along with our challenge and share your creations with us HERE!
I struggled a bit with the challenge as I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any stamps that scream &amp;ldquo;occupations&amp;rdquo; to me&amp;hellip; so I had to think outside the box a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less is More Take 2*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-30-less-is-more-take-2/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned a few days ago, I had made another card for the current Less is More challenge but I felt it wasn&amp;rsquo;t as &amp;ldquo;clean and simple&amp;rdquo; as I wanted&amp;hellip; I still like the card so I&amp;rsquo;m sharing it with you now. Card Info
Images: Altenew Celebrate Toay
Ink: Versaamark; Copics
Etc: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! gold embossing powder
Challenges: Less Is More #461</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Less Is More #461*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/03/2022-03-26-less-is-more-461/</guid>
      <description>Happy Saturday crafty friends! I usually work on Saturdays (my work week is Wednesday thru Saturday) but I get one Saturday off each month&amp;hellip; this is that Saturday. I love my job, I really truly do&amp;hellip; but I do look forward to my Saturdays off!
It&amp;rsquo;s time for a new challenge with the team at Less Is More&amp;hellip; our clean and simple challenge for the next two weeks is to use the colours pink and gold.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
