<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Perfect Layers on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</title>
    <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/perfect-layers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Perfect Layers on Nancy&#39;s Creative Mess</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nauntie.ca/tags/perfect-layers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*Subdued Thank You*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/09/2022-09-05-subdued-thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Back in early July we lost a very good friend after a short illness&amp;hellip; it was devastating to lose a friend that we loved so much. She was one of my regular customers in terms of card orders. Her husband approached me after her funeral, asking if I would please make him some thank you cards to send out to people who helped out so much during her brief illness and after her death&amp;hellip; and I said &amp;ldquo;of course&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #477*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/07/2022-07-05-cas-colours-sketches-477/</guid>
      <description>Patricia is our host for the month of July at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; she chose this wonderfully right colour palette for our first challenge this month.
Being a part of this design team, I have discovered that I am much better at sketch challenges than I am with colour challenges. When I was only playing along, if the colours didn&amp;rsquo;t speak to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play. If the colours were at all challenging to me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*CAS Colours &amp; Sketches #467*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-26-cas-colours-sketches-467/</guid>
      <description>This will be my last post with CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches until my wrist heals enough to craft again. My surgery on Friday went well and I&amp;rsquo;m in less pain than I was before surgery. I have no idea when I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do things with the right hand again&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m guessing I&amp;rsquo;ll have some answers after my surgical follow up on the 2nd.
But for today, my card using the current sketch at CAS Colours &amp;amp; Sketches&amp;hellip; I wanted to leave my background white but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*Sparkles*</title>
      <link>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nauntie.ca/posts/2022/04/2022-04-13-sparkles/</guid>
      <description>Some more of those Pink Fresh Studio rainbow butterflies that I cut out &amp;hellip; I added a few matted layers and a strip of black and white stripes.
Card Info
*Cardstock: Stampin&amp;rsquo; Up! Basic Black, Lemon Lime Twist
*Paper: MFT Black &amp;amp; White Stripes
*Images: Pink Fresh Studio Small Butterflies, Happy Birthday Sentiments
*Ink: Versafine Clair Nocturne; Tim Holtz Distress Picked Raspberry, Orange Marmalade, Mustard Seed, Twisted Citron
*Tools: Fricken Square Corners; Perfect Layers</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
